<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 04:33:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: The claim that 100 companies produce 71% of carbon emissions is highly misleading, and doesn't really tell us anything interesting.]]></title><description><![CDATA[You'll often hear the that 100 companies produce 71% of carbon emissions. This
is technically true given a couple of definitions. You'll also usually hear
people say that because of that, we really just need to get those 100 companies
to clean up and we'll solve climate change. This, however, is…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qjsvwa/cmv_the_claim_that_100_companies_produce_71_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qjsvwa/cmv_the_claim_that_100_companies_produce_71_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 21:37:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;ll often hear the that 100 companies produce 71% of carbon emissions.  This is technically true given a couple of definitions.   You&amp;#39;ll also usually hear people say that because of that,  we really just need to get those 100 companies to clean up and we&amp;#39;ll solve climate change.  This, however, is complete nonsense. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://b8f65cb373b1b7b15feb-c70d8ead6ced550b4d987d7c03fcdd1d.ssl.cf3.rackcdn.com/cms/reports/documents/000/002/327/original/Carbon-Majors-Report-2017.pdf?1499691240#page=6&quot;&gt;The source for that claim, the Carbon Majors Report, &lt;/a&gt; attributes carbon to the supplier.  So when you drive your car, the carbon footprint of your gas tank is accounted against whatever oil company you bought it from:  Shell or Exxon or BP or Chevron, etc.  Similarly,  when you heat your house or cook with natural gas, that counts against the gas company.  And when you turn on the light, the power plants fuel counts against the gas company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it&amp;#39;s no surprise that nearly all of those top 100 producers are oil, gas, and coal producers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How is that interesting or useful?  If you cap Exxon&amp;#39;s carbon footprint, all that means is that gas prices skyrocket.  Regulating Exxon is the same as regulating consumers, and will only have an effect by getting people to drive less. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, we should account things on the demand side,  particularly to the organization that could have abated the emissions.   You should account the carbon emissions of electricity to the utility company,  because they could have used wind/solar/nuclear/hydro/etc; they could have built pumped storage hydro, etc.  The gas you fill your car with should be accounted to you,  since you didn&amp;#39;t walk,  bike,  use a scooter or electric car. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Solutions for carbon emissions have to target the demand side of things by introducing and incentivising low carbon alternatives.  And a revenue neutral carbon tax and rebate wouldn&amp;#39;t hurt, either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accounting things based on demand gives us a much better idea of what things are big problems,  and where we should spend our resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Employers abuse immigration visas instead of hiring and training up citizens.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Recently there has been a lot of talks about the shrinking middle class, lower
wages in relation to cost of living, and not enough "educated" Americans for
certain positions.

I am of the opinion that this has all been the caused by corporations no longer
looking to train up or spend time on local…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qjr0r7/cmv_employers_abuse_immigration_visas_instead_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qjr0r7/cmv_employers_abuse_immigration_visas_instead_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 19:30:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently there has been a lot of talks about the shrinking middle class, lower wages in relation to cost of living, and not enough &amp;quot;educated&amp;quot; Americans for certain positions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am of the opinion that this has all been the caused by corporations no longer looking to train up or spend time on local talent. For example, any engineer or tech individual looking to find an entry level position will be met with ridiculous requirements like 2 years of experience or mastery of wide ranging topics. This is most egregious in the STEM fields. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People like to argue that &amp;quot;this helps make America competitive in the world stage&amp;quot;. No, all it does is give normal Americans no opportunity for career advancement and options. For example, there is a cap on the number of med school admission in the US causing a shrotage of doctors. Solution? Hire more foreign doctors. Its actually ridiculous&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We really need to end these programs as automation continues to abolish various traditional jobs. We need to set up training camps to teach people how to code, or be a technician, draftsmen, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would either eliminate these visa&amp;#39;s, or if a company really needed the expertise of a foreign worker, they have to pay 50% higher than the BLS median average. There is really no reason American&amp;#39;s cannot or should not be trained up for these positions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: The classical high paying office/technical jobs that built up America and the middle class, are starting to feel the pains of globalization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EXAMPLE: &lt;a href=&quot;https://thehill.com/policy/technology/577397-facebook-settles-with-doj-to-resolve-allegations-of-discriminating-against&quot;&gt;https://thehill.com/policy/technology/577397-facebook-settles-with-doj-to-resolve-allegations-of-discriminating-against&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: in the western world, there is no point in complaining about declining fertility rates as there is nothing we can do unless we either make people lose their freedoms or change our entire economics]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'll limit it to Canada and USA, but I am sure this applies to others.

When I hear people being concerned about low birth rates, I think, even if
that's a problem, what can we do about it. I would like my view changed because
right now I'm a pessimist. Please note that this post isn't about…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qjr7dt/cmv_in_the_western_world_there_is_no_point_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qjr7dt/cmv_in_the_western_world_there_is_no_point_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 18:46:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll limit it to Canada and USA, but I am sure this applies to others. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I hear people being concerned about low birth rates, I think, even if that&amp;#39;s a problem, what can we do about it. I would like my view changed because right now I&amp;#39;m a pessimist. Please note that this post isn&amp;#39;t about lowering population (as that can be changed with immigration) but rather with &amp;#39;born on the soil&amp;#39; declining birth rate. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;#39;t speak for everyone else, but I would think there are plenty who are just like me. I don&amp;#39;t want kids because I don&amp;#39;t think its justified to make a kid go through what I go through, worrying about finances in this really expensive country. (Canada) 
Secondly, kids are expensive. We can&amp;#39;t incentivize people like me to have kids. Now, people compare this to people in Zimbabwe or Nigeria. The difference however is, having a kid is an investment that has a higher guarantee of return. (While I hate that people use kids as tools to better their lives, I&amp;#39;m gonna try being objective) in other countries, despite being in poverty, people have kids. I mention the guarantee return because society pressures people to take care of their parents. In Canada, I don&amp;#39;t feel as much of it. People dump their (asshole) parents. Justified or not, there is no guarantee they will help out. The money spent on kids can be spent on saving for retirement homes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also can&amp;#39;t artificially make prices go down without sacrificing freedom that a lot of people like. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The difference in Canada and other countries is also the laws. Its illegal and enforced to starve your kid. Why would I have a kid, even if i was selfish, if I knew that any moment and my &amp;#39;investment&amp;#39; would be gone. And I speak as someone who had family that grew up third world poverty. (my family is Chinese) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is also no incentive for me as an incel (male or female) to put up with shitty partners to make a baby. I don&amp;#39;t need a man to work and fund me. So unless we are going back to women can&amp;#39;t work laws, I think its inevitable there will be more single people. I don&amp;#39;t mean to sound edgy, but I pretty much don&amp;#39;t need a man, economically speaking. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope I&amp;#39;m not all over the place, but basically, unless we address the high cost of living, there&amp;#39;s just no incentive to raise a kid. We also need to address how to incentivize people to get into relationships and make babies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in the past women had to put up with men&amp;#39;s bad behaviour. Now? Why should I put up with shitty men? (Not saying all men) let&amp;#39;s say I have high standards. If it means that I may ignore 90% of the population, so what? There&amp;#39;s no incentive. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tldr: there just isn&amp;#39;t anyway to incentivize people to have kids unless we are OK being authoritarian or giving up our economic model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I sort of changed my view that we should talk about it and try, but as of yet, I see no solution that would get people to have kids unless it makes their life better. Such as, as sick as it is, allowing people to profit in having kids. That to my view has always been why humans have kids. It makes life happier when those who want have kids. Some others use kids to help with the farm. If having kids is a negative (ie spending money etc) then people will not have kids&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: The definition of asexuality is too broad and invites more ridicule and less acceptance of the LGBTQ+ community as a whole]]></title><description><![CDATA[I started thinking of this after seeing this tweet. It's an asexual model
advertising an asexual-themed lingerie line.
https://twitter.com/SophNar0747/status/1453702975222919168?t=2zXdqNmFzX5C8xV7pUL99A&s=09

Apparently the accepted definition of asexual has broadened to include people
that enjoy…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qjapxt/cmv_the_definition_of_asexuality_is_too_broad_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qjapxt/cmv_the_definition_of_asexuality_is_too_broad_and/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 04:42:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started thinking of this after seeing this tweet. It&amp;#39;s an asexual model advertising an asexual-themed lingerie line. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SophNar0747/status/1453702975222919168?t=2zXdqNmFzX5C8xV7pUL99A&amp;amp;s=09&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/SophNar0747/status/1453702975222919168?t=2zXdqNmFzX5C8xV7pUL99A&amp;amp;s=09&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently the accepted definition of asexual has broadened to include people that enjoy sex, seek out sex, yet say they feel no sexual attraction. That they feel sex as an asexual person is essentially like masturbation, just involving another person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/what-is-asexual&quot;&gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/what-is-asexual&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I have a friend that identifies as asexual, is married but has never had sex with her husband. She&amp;#39;s sex repulsed, which is what I think most people think of when they see the term asexual. I understand that kind of asexuality being included in the broader LGBTQ+ community. It&amp;#39;s unusual and opens you to ridicule in a society that pressures people to lose their virginity and advertising often with sexual themes. I can see that being surrounded by sex when you&amp;#39;re repulsed by sex would be distressing, like when your friends family and coworkers talk about sex. I can see that the other kind of asexuality, where you&amp;#39;re simply not interested in sex, would also contribute to reduced acceptance in society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I don&amp;#39;t see the functional difference in how you&amp;#39;re treated in society and conform to societal expectations if you label yourself as asexual but regularly engage in sex, whether casually or in a relationship. People with strict paraphilias can only be aroused when non-human elements are present and are attracted to those non-human elements (like leather, shoes, food, etc). They&amp;#39;re not considered automatically part of the queer community. They engage in sex and enjoy it when their partner accommodates those fetishes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this new broad definition of asexuality is confusing to the average person, and contributes to the perception that being LGBTQ+ is &amp;quot;trendy&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;attention seeking.&amp;quot; This attitude contributes to queer issues being taken less seriously, like discrimination and violence on the basis of your sexuality or gender identity. I just don&amp;#39;t see any example of, and can&amp;#39;t imagine, oppression that would be leveled against a person that identifies as asexual yet regularly engages in sex with other people. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My argument is that the definition of asexuality should be limited to people that are not interested in sex, either because of repulsion or simply non-interest. I&amp;#39;m not setting the bar that they all have to be virgins, because there are plenty of gay people that married and had children with people of the opposite sex to fit in and avoid discrimination. I can see someone not fully accepting that they don&amp;#39;t feel sexual attraction until they try it out. I&amp;#39;m not suggesting the label of asexual should be ruled out for masturbation either, as it&amp;#39;s very different than sex with another person. But, I think actively seeking sex should be disqualifying for labeling yourself as asexual. There&amp;#39;s no functional difference between having sex because you&amp;#39;re attracted to someone and having sex just because it feels good. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: The label of asexual makes no sense for someone that actively seeks out sexual partners, and engages regularly in sex. Asexuality is understandably being included in the broader LGBTQ+ community, but I think people that identify as asexual yet engage in sex shouldn&amp;#39;t be included in that. It&amp;#39;s confusing and leads to people taking queer issues less seriously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: What would change my view is if someone could provide an example of discrimination or distress a person would experience if they identify as asexual yet still engage in sex regularly and actively seek it out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: "Capitalism" and "Socialism" Have Become Meaningless Buzzwords]]></title><description><![CDATA[When people claim to oppose capitalism or socialism, they typically don't know
what they are talking about. I'm all for questioning the status quo, but these
words get thrown around so much that they've lost all meaning. So, why not be
more precise? Let's have discussions about economics, human…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qjdyxs/cmv_capitalism_and_socialism_have_become/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qjdyxs/cmv_capitalism_and_socialism_have_become/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 03:38:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When people claim to oppose capitalism or socialism, they typically don&amp;#39;t know what they are talking about. I&amp;#39;m all for questioning the status quo, but  these words get thrown around so much that they&amp;#39;ve lost all meaning. So, why not be more precise? Let&amp;#39;s have discussions about economics, human rights, markets, and government regulation without reducing everything to capitalism versus socialism. Capitalism and socialism are better thought of as immutable forces endemic to every society, rather than conflicting ideologies. We should be seeking balance instead of exacerbating polarization and avoiding nuance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: The mass resignations and push for higher wages is going to eliminate the middle class who aren't getting raises]]></title><description><![CDATA[I went to college and worked hard and got a 4 year degree. I then got a job
paying the equivalent of 25 or so an hour, with small raises each year.

Now that the service industry is spiking wages over 20 an hour, middle class
wages already in the 20s per hour have not gone up and probably will…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qj7xcv/cmv_the_mass_resignations_and_push_for_higher/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qj7xcv/cmv_the_mass_resignations_and_push_for_higher/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 21:36:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I went to college and worked hard and got a 4 year degree. I then got a job paying the equivalent of 25 or so an hour, with small raises each year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the service industry is spiking wages over 20 an hour, middle class wages already in the 20s per hour have not gone up and probably will slowly if at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this has done is eliminate the middle class as both the burger flippers and mid level office jobs will make near the same amount of money, with food and other service prices (already increasing) while the rich hardly notice the tiny increase in spending as it is a much larger portion of the (now combined lower class) income versus theirs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really would like to change my view and have some hope the middle class weren&amp;#39;t totally fucked by this, but I doubt that&amp;#39;s possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: most influencers are just random attention whores]]></title><description><![CDATA[Note this comment applies to 99% of so-called influencers. While there are
certainly a few who actually sell product and get people to copy their style /
fashion (sports stars, Hollywood icons etc), the vast majority of people calling
themselves influencers are just extroverts from Podunk…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qj9jbx/cmv_most_influencers_are_just_random_attention/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qj9jbx/cmv_most_influencers_are_just_random_attention/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 21:36:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note this comment applies to 99% of so-called influencers. While there are certainly a few who actually sell product and get people to copy their style / fashion (sports stars, Hollywood icons etc), the vast majority of people calling themselves influencers are just extroverts from Podunk  shamelessly prostrating themselves online. They’ll never amount to anything and their 100 followers are also losers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the concept of a celebrity pitchman/woman is long established, I&amp;#39;ve never bought anything pitched by a celebrity, or social media app. You were paid to promote something? Good for you, I ain&amp;#39;t buying it. Good product? Don&amp;#39;t care, it&amp;#39;s a cheesy way to reach people. And why should I trust your opinion anyway? If the product was that good and actually something I needed, I&amp;#39;d have heard about it by other means. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are people so gullible these days they&amp;#39;ll shell out for anything pitched by a Kardashian? Maybe, but the 100,000 Kim/Kylie wannabes out there? Get a fucking job because your TikTok is never gonna pay your bills. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your work is cut out for you peeps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Freddy Krueger is the greatest horror movie character of all time.]]></title><description><![CDATA[He's an all original character with a fantastic backstory and the idea of his
existence is far more disturbing then any of his decade counterparts like Jason,
Micheal, or Chucky. My man Freddy has the best style of dress, the best methods
of killing, and the best dialog one liners (winning out…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qixmg2/cmv_freddy_krueger_is_the_greatest_horror_movie/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qixmg2/cmv_freddy_krueger_is_the_greatest_horror_movie/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 17:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;He&amp;#39;s an all original character with a fantastic backstory and the idea of his existence is far more disturbing then any of his decade counterparts like Jason, Micheal, or Chucky. My man Freddy has the best style of dress, the best methods of killing, and the best dialog one liners (winning out against Chucky by just a little).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea of Freddy attacking you in your dreams to kill you in real life is spine chilling, it&amp;#39;s not just mindless bloodshed there&amp;#39;s real mental anguish and physiological warfare in his madness. Even stacked up against the great Pennywise, Freddy wins by a nose (pun intended).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modern day horror characters fail in comparison as well as most of them are just rewashed possessed toys and dolls or occultic driven spirits. There&amp;#39;s no flair or effort and their methods are stale in comparison. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I vote to make Halloween eve National Freddy Krueger Day in honor of the king of horror.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Spelling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Circumcision for children should be illegal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Circumcision is not only almost always medically unnecessary, but it is a clear
violation of the rights of the child. If somebody who is at an age capable of
consenting, then sure, let them do it.
Being allowed to mutilate our children in the name of religion is completely
insane, and should not at…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhtxyb/cmv_circumcision_for_children_should_be_illegal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhtxyb/cmv_circumcision_for_children_should_be_illegal/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 18:30:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Circumcision is not only almost always medically unnecessary, but it is a clear violation of the rights of the child. If somebody who is at an age capable of consenting, then sure, let them do it.&lt;br/&gt;
Being allowed to mutilate our children in the name of religion is completely insane, and should not at all be tolerated. Female genital mutilation is abhorrent, but why are we allowed to do it to men? Religion should not be a defense for such acts.&lt;br/&gt;
We&amp;#39;d never tolerate FGM in western countries like America (even though it still happens), so why do we tolerate this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Passion (trusting your feelings) should be encouraged less and dispassionate logic should be encouraged more, when making non trivial decisions on behalf of others.]]></title><description><![CDATA[If a million kings made a million decisions for their subjects with a mindset of
"trust your feelings", and another million kings made a million decisions for
their subjects with a dispassionate mindset (Vulcan style), the latter group
would have more success more often.

Whenever someone defends a…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qibiiy/cmv_passion_trusting_your_feelings_should_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qibiiy/cmv_passion_trusting_your_feelings_should_be/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 17:30:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a million kings made a million decisions for their subjects with a mindset of &amp;quot;trust your feelings&amp;quot;, and another million kings made a million decisions for their subjects with a dispassionate mindset (Vulcan style), the latter group would have more success more often. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever someone defends a passion oriented decision, they typically point to things like motivation. Pure logic won&amp;#39;t get you out of bed, but once you&amp;#39;re out of bed it can get you to your goals better. I&amp;#39;m not suggesting you pretend that feelings don&amp;#39;t exist, but they should be part of the equation. I  could dispassionately decide which hobby I will be most passionate about balanced against the costs, for example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone will tell me that you can&amp;#39;t always tell the difference and psychologically they&amp;#39;re mixed. Sure, but insofar it&amp;#39;s possible to differentiate you know what I&amp;#39;m talking about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t abandon med school to be a singer. Lose a battle to win a war. Hold your temper even though it would feel very good to let it go. Use the damn targeting computer to shoot the death star rather than your feelings (it worked for luke because he&amp;#39;s a space wizard and the writers contrived it).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes the passionate approach works, it&amp;#39;s probably better than utter randomness, but the odds favor the dispassionate approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Returning your shopping cart is ALWAYS the right decision]]></title><description><![CDATA[No matter the rush, no matter the circumstance, assuring that your grocery cart
is returned is the right thing to do in every instance. I absolutely hate it
when I go to pull into a spot and someone left their cart in it. It seems to me
like there’s no excuse. Parking lots are already accident prone…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qif42b/cmv_returning_your_shopping_cart_is_always_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qif42b/cmv_returning_your_shopping_cart_is_always_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 16:35:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;No matter the rush, no matter the circumstance, assuring that your grocery cart is returned is the right thing to do in every instance. I absolutely hate it when I go to pull into a spot and someone left their cart in it. It seems to me like there’s no excuse. Parking lots are already accident prone and unreturned carts are an extra hazard. If you don’t want to walk it back into the store then don’t use it. Toddlers are taught to clean up what they take out to use. If you cannot physically return a cart you can notify a staff member and they will assist you. Often times they’ll offer before you even need to ask. Leaving it on the curb is a d*ck move; and a red flag for me when I make friends/consider partners. The only “valid” explanation I consider for leaving a cart in a parking spot is that you’re either lazy, inconsiderate, or both.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: Buying expensive diamond wedding/engagement rings is a waste of money.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The act of buying an expensive, timeless diamond ring is perpetuated by the De
Beers company, that suppresses the supply of diamonds to retain an artificially
high price.

The utility obtained from the diamond ring is completely detached from the
price. This is also true for other day-to-day things…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qi6oud/cmv_buying_expensive_diamond_weddingengagement/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qi6oud/cmv_buying_expensive_diamond_weddingengagement/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 11:31:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The act of buying an expensive, timeless diamond ring is perpetuated by the De Beers company, that suppresses the supply of diamonds to retain an artificially high price. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The utility obtained from the diamond ring is completely detached from the price. This is also true for other day-to-day things we use, however in the case of diamond rings, it is especially true to a frustrating extent. Why not buy a ring with a nice gem-stone, or zircon or any other replacement that might not last millions of years like a diamond, but will still certainly last thousands of years and outlast your marriage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea that you must spend a lot of money to confirm your commitment to your partner is just wrong, and is the product of some very clever marketing. The act of asking your partner to marry you should be confirmation of commitment in-and-of itself. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, the spending part isn&amp;#39;t my issue. It&amp;#39;s the spending of so much, in something that will yield so little to you. Why not buy your partner a reasonable ring, and then spend the rest on something they need, like a car, or use that money towards a down payment etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If someone makes the argument that it is an investment, then it should be pointed out that diamonds to not appreciate over time. Why not invest the money in the S&amp;amp;P 500 then?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV:I don't have to respect your culture or religion , but I have to respect your choice to follow them]]></title><description><![CDATA[As the title suggests , I don't believe that I have to respect every
culture/religion. Since they can be promoting ideas that don't align with my
moral values ( misogyny ,sexism,inequality,racism , pedophilia...). What I do
have to respect is one's choice to follow a desired religion and practice…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhx7f5/cmvi_dont_have_to_respect_your_culture_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhx7f5/cmvi_dont_have_to_respect_your_culture_or/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 09:34:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the title suggests , I don&amp;#39;t believe that I have to respect every culture/religion. Since they can be promoting ideas that don&amp;#39;t align with my moral values ( misogyny ,sexism,inequality,racism , pedophilia...). What I do have to respect is one&amp;#39;s choice to follow a desired religion and practice the culture , as long as they are not hurting anyone else in the process .Because following a specific religion/ culture doesn&amp;#39;t inherently mean you are practicing all the &amp;quot;bad&amp;quot; parts as well .The reason i hold this view is because I have been exposed to a few  different cultures and I noticed a lot of bizarre practices that are either normalized culturally or religiously . for example , forbidding your mother and sisters from working ,early child marriage ,honor killing, self harm and sacrifice , female genital mutilation ...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Science cannot "tell you to do something", trying to use science as a means of telling people to do something is an is-ought fallacy.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Disclaimer: Since I'm probably going to be called an anti-vaxxer for making this
argument, I want to make it clear that I have taken the vaccine and would
encourage anyone who is medically fit to do so also take it.

With that out of the way, I see a lot of pro-vaccine and pro-mandate…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qi278p/cmv_science_cannot_tell_you_to_do_something/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qi278p/cmv_science_cannot_tell_you_to_do_something/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 08:42:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer: Since I&amp;#39;m probably going to be called an anti-vaxxer for making this argument, I want to make it clear that I have taken the vaccine and would encourage anyone who is medically fit to do so also take it.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that out of the way, I see a lot of pro-vaccine and pro-mandate advocates arguing that anti-vaxxers are &amp;quot;contradicting the science&amp;quot; when they choose to not get vaccinated. I think this argument reveals a lack of understanding about what science is and what science is not. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Science is a set of positive/descriptive statements about what &lt;em&gt;is.&lt;/em&gt; F=ma or e=mc&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt; are merely statements which describe reality. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Science &lt;strong&gt;is not&lt;/strong&gt; a set of normative/prescriptive about what &lt;em&gt;should be&lt;/em&gt;. Newton&amp;#39;s laws of motion or Einstein&amp;#39;s theory of relativity do not provide us with knowledge about how we &lt;em&gt;should behave&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The statement &amp;quot;COVID-19 vaccines improve your chances of survival by x, and the probability of you having complications due to the vaccine is y&amp;quot; is a scientific statement. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The statement &amp;quot;the vaccine is safe, therefore you should take it&amp;quot; is &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; a scientific statement. Embedded within this statement is a value judgement being made by a human actor according to their ethical or philosophical position, which is &lt;strong&gt;outside the purview of scientific inquiry.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hume&amp;#39;s is-ought gap &amp;quot;arises when one makes claims about what ought to be that are based solely on statements about what is&amp;quot;, and this example is a perfect exemplification of that fallacy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be sure, people might incorporate scientific data into their decision-making process, however, that in and of itself is a value judgement which claims the information provided by the scientific method &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; be incorporated into such a process. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: Science is descriptive, not prescriptive, therefore stating &amp;quot;the science tells us we should do x&amp;quot; is simply a category error and constitutes an is-ought fallacy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: It’s disingenuous to tell someone to “love your natural self” when you make aesthetic alterations to yourself]]></title><description><![CDATA[I see this with celebrities and “influencers” but also in general. Many people
promote this message of “loving yourself for who you are” while they themselves
are refuse to be seen without makeup, use filters and photoshop and get
surgeries to look better.

I think one of the goofiest things I’ve…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qi1j3a/cmv_its_disingenuous_to_tell_someone_to_love_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qi1j3a/cmv_its_disingenuous_to_tell_someone_to_love_your/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 06:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see this with celebrities and “influencers” but also in general. Many people promote this message of “loving yourself for who you are” while they themselves are refuse to be seen without makeup, use filters and photoshop and get surgeries to look better. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think one of the goofiest things I’ve seen is an influencer talking about how you should love your natural skin...so buy this make up that looks like natural skin but covers up flaws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are people who get surgery, wear makeup and use filters all at the same time. There’s no way youre making all these changes and “love your natural self”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s just disingenuous and hypocritical to me and it creates a harmful message for young people and adults as well&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: There's no reason for me to put my pronouns in my email signature]]></title><description><![CDATA[Many of my colleagues include their pronouns in their email signature and in
other types of professional correspondence. I am totally fine with them doing
that. I have no complaints about the practice at all.

I don't, however, feel any need to follow suit and put my pronouns in my email
signature.…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhx1iz/cmv_theres_no_reason_for_me_to_put_my_pronouns_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhx1iz/cmv_theres_no_reason_for_me_to_put_my_pronouns_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 23:39:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of my colleagues include their pronouns in their email signature and in other types of professional correspondence. I am totally fine with them doing that. I have no complaints about the practice at all. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t, however, feel any need to follow suit and put my pronouns in my email signature. My reasoning:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the rare or almost unimaginable circumstance where someone would not be sure because they are blind, don&amp;#39;t speak my language, etc., I am not going to be the least bit troubled, offended, or confused. Confusion is possible, I suppose, but it would be so short-lived that it wouldn&amp;#39;t be a problem, and the chances that the email sig would prevent that confusion are next to impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If someone prefers to use a non-gendered pronoun like &amp;quot;they&amp;quot; or whatever, I&amp;#39;m totally fine with that too. I use &amp;quot;they&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;them&amp;quot; when I refer to anyone I don&amp;#39;t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my professional contexts, it shouldn&amp;#39;t matter what my gender is. You don&amp;#39;t need to know my pronoun to know whether you should listen to me, read my email, etc. You don&amp;#39;t need to know my pronoun to contact me because my title, first name, and last name are all there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I imagine that a common counterargument will be something along the lines of, &amp;quot;for some folks, it&amp;#39;s not so obvious what their pronouns will be and/or they care much more than I do about people getting their pronouns right, so they have to put their pronouns in their email signature. And because they have to, I should as well for some kind of show of solidarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s important to me to get their pronouns right, especially if it&amp;#39;s important to them, so I&amp;#39;m glad they&amp;#39;re letting me know in advance. And that&amp;#39;s how I show solidarity--that I care about getting pronouns right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I&amp;#39;m missing some piece of the puzzle. I&amp;#39;m hoping someone can walk me through why they&amp;#39;d feel better if I had my pronouns visible all over the place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or, if I&amp;#39;ve completely misread this trend, and no one cares whether I display my pronouns, let me know that too. Am I only imagining this societal/cultural pressure to display my pronouns whether or not there is a concrete practical purpose? (e.g., I put my business phone number in my email sig so people can call me if they need to. That&amp;#39;s what I mean by concrete, practical reason.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Money does buy happiness. It’s literally the whole point of modern society.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Money doesn't buy happiness. Its a statement that is a complete and udder lie
that is only used to keep the poor from feeling bad about their current
situations. Of course money buys happiness. The world was literally built on the
idea of currency. You'd have to be an absolute buffoons' to assume…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhpfuy/cmv_money_does_buy_happiness_its_literally_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhpfuy/cmv_money_does_buy_happiness_its_literally_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 17:33:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Money doesn&amp;#39;t buy happiness. Its a statement that is a complete and udder lie that is only used to keep the poor from feeling bad about their current situations. Of course money buys happiness. The world was literally built on the idea of currency. You&amp;#39;d have to be an absolute buffoons&amp;#39; to assume anything different. Cause as any sane human being would understand and see, money is the one thing we need to survive. Due to the absolutely disgusting thing we call human greed, we&amp;#39;ve created system where life without money leads to nothing buy unhappiness and hardship. Really think about it for a second. Have you ever seen an happy homeless person? Just a person who isn&amp;#39;t begging for money or sitting on the corner while directly looking into your eyes only for you to ignore them like they were the scum of the earth. Exactly. They beg for money out of desperation, not because there happy with their current situation.  Look, i get it. The saying is supposed to talk about how experiences can&amp;#39;t be bought and how good memories aren&amp;#39;t made with money. However, you must understand that money has and always will play a role in your happiness. That trip to Florida didn&amp;#39;t pay itself and neither did the people who enjoyed it with you. Call me pessimistic all you want, but if you really want true happiness, you might as well be willing to drop a few dollars in order to enjoy yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: People should stop referring to American culture as “white culture” and start referring to it as “American culture” instead.]]></title><description><![CDATA[“White culture” is synonymous with American culture because most Americans are
white and “white culture” is the dominant culture in the USA. People should stop
referring to American culture as “white culture” and start referring to it as
“American culture” because it doesn’t let nonwhites assimilate…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhl9p7/cmv_people_should_stop_referring_to_american/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhl9p7/cmv_people_should_stop_referring_to_american/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 14:37:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“White culture” is synonymous with American culture because most Americans are white and “white culture” is the dominant culture in the USA. People should stop referring to American culture as “white culture” and start referring to it as “American culture” because it doesn’t let nonwhites assimilate into Americans. People calling American culture “white culture” constantly reminds nonwhite Americans that the culture of their country can’t be theirs or that they can’t be American simply for not having white skin. People calling American culture “white culture” only lets white people assimilate into Americans while excluding everyone else when the USA is a country of immigrants and was supposed to be for any immigrant that decided to live their home country for a better place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hear no country name their culture after a skin color. Germans call their culture “German culture” and not “white culture.” Nigerians calls their culture “Nigerian culture” and not “black culture.” The USA is weird for being the only country call their culture after a skin color rather than region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The term “White culture” also gives the idea that white people worldwide are homogenous or a monolith when they are not. A white person from Ireland won’t act the same as a white person from the USA. Another reason why people should start referring to American culture as American culture and not “white culture.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People might say “But ‘African American’ culture is a subculture of American culture, so people should say ‘white culture’ in order to not confuse it with African American culture.” I already disagree with you because indigenous people in Mexico have their own culture too and it’s separate from mainstream Mexican culture. But guess what. Both the indigenous cultures in Mexico and the mainstream Mexican culture are Mexican. But people still call mainstream Mexican culture “Mexican culture” rather than “mestizo culture.” Why can’t the USA do the same, stop focusing on skin color, and call their mainstream American culture “American culture” rather than “white culture?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One more thing. Skin color is so insignificant as hair color or eye color or the length of someone’s finger. Why should we worry about the color of someone’s skin? We should look past that because it’s so insignificant. What color someone is doesn’t make them any other different. They’re still human like everyone else. We shouldn’t be obsessed with what someone’s skin color is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: I think it should be okay to criticize people for their unethical behavior even if their circumstances/conditions/culture led them to it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[A lot of times, we hear people in the West defending atrocities committed by
other cultures/nations, saying that "We are not in a position to judge them for
their wrongdoings, since we are a product of Western culture and we have been
indoctrinated with Western values." I think this sentiment is…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhfig1/cmv_i_think_it_should_be_okay_to_criticize_people/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qhfig1/cmv_i_think_it_should_be_okay_to_criticize_people/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 07:36:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of times, we hear people in the West defending atrocities committed by other cultures/nations, saying that &amp;quot;We are not in a position to judge them for their wrongdoings, since we are a product of Western culture and we have been indoctrinated with Western values.&amp;quot; I think this sentiment is dangerous as it can lead to a relativist dystopia. Our world is growing smaller and smaller in the 21st century, we are more interconnected than ever. We must subject all cultures to the same level of criticism if we wish to build a healthy global community which aims for all human well-being. I think it&amp;#39;s of utmost importance to consider our shared humanity as the highest value, above our cultural differences. I think it is deplorable to consider the notion of &amp;quot;human rights&amp;quot; as a form of Eurocentrism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: There is a shortage of workers because the pandemic has taught us that the economy doesnt need us; and over the last year & a half we have individually found ways to minimize or even eliminate our dependence on abusive employers.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am a professional chef and the pandemic and lockdown hit the food scene like
the fist of an angry god. Many restaurants immediately shut down to wait it out.
Many restaurants shut down and went out of business. Some restaurants were able
to stay in business by effectively converting to a dine-out…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qh2us4/cmv_there_is_a_shortage_of_workers_because_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qh2us4/cmv_there_is_a_shortage_of_workers_because_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 20:40:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am a professional chef and the pandemic and lockdown hit the food scene like the fist of an angry god. Many restaurants immediately shut down to wait it out. Many restaurants shut down and went out of business. Some restaurants were able to stay in business by effectively converting to a dine-out-only model. Overall, the ability to secure employment as a chef or cook was essentially impossible. The restaurants that stayed open &amp;amp; serviced the delivery scene pared their staff down to minimal, absolutely essential, most senior staff. There were unemployed cooks everywhere. Now that we&amp;#39;re back to 100% seating capacity and guests can even fill the bar, there are no cooks to be found. This is just one example, but the media is saturated with news of labor shortages. There is a reason and it&amp;#39;s not that everyone who was unemployed during lockdown instantly became successful software developers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Pronouns other than he/she/they defeat the purpose of a pronoun and shouldn’t be used]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have no issue with inclusivity and couldn’t care less why you identify as/who
you’re attracted to, that’s totally your business. But the point of a pronoun is
to be a general term used to identify/refer to someone. There are currently 78
gender pronouns… 78. At that point, wouldn’t it make more…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgjxeu/cmv_pronouns_other_than_heshethey_defeat_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgjxeu/cmv_pronouns_other_than_heshethey_defeat_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have no issue with inclusivity and couldn’t care less why you identify as/who you’re attracted to, that’s totally your business. But the point of a pronoun is to be a general term used to identify/refer to someone. There are currently 78 gender pronouns… 78. At that point, wouldn’t it make more sense to refer to everyone as ‘they/them’ or, better yet, by their name instead of memorizing dozens of new pronouns that are constantly being changed/added to? Just seems like a lot of work to stay up to date with an ever changing list of pronouns rather than just sticking with 3 that are applicable to literally everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: "Cancel culture" is a conservative dogwhistle used to make leftists feel that fighting for social justice is somehow a bad thing.]]></title><description><![CDATA[A phrase I've seen used a lot recently in internet discourse is this idea of
"cancel culture", moreso in the last few weeks because of controversy
surrounding Dave Chappelle's new comedy special. Interestingly it seems like
this idea has become popular even among the center-left (which I feel are…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgyjwf/cmv_cancel_culture_is_a_conservative_dogwhistle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgyjwf/cmv_cancel_culture_is_a_conservative_dogwhistle/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A phrase I&amp;#39;ve seen used a lot recently in internet discourse is this idea of &amp;quot;cancel culture&amp;quot;, moreso in the last few weeks because of controversy surrounding Dave Chappelle&amp;#39;s new comedy special. Interestingly it seems like this idea has become popular even among the center-left (which I feel are fairly dominate on reddit) which I find odd. I often seem comments saying something along the lines of &amp;quot;Oh I&amp;#39;m a big liberal/democrat and I support LGBTQ+ rights and yada yada, but damn I really hate what cancel culture has done to our society.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally think that cancel culture isn&amp;#39;t even really much of a real thing, let alone a serious issue facing our society. I believe it is a dogwhistle used by the right to indirectly attack leftist activists that has successfully poisoned leftist discourse. I mean, seriously, let&amp;#39;s take a look at some of the people who were &amp;quot;cancelled&amp;quot; recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-- R Kelly: Abused vulnerable women on mass, exhibited predatory behavior, basically ran a deranged abusive sex cult for years. Dose this person not deserve to be &amp;quot;cancelled?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;--Chris Pratt. Supposedly attended anti-LGBTQ church meetings. Is still immensely popular and is still getting work in a major motion picture. Was this person really &amp;quot;cancelled?&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-- Dave Chappelle. Mocked the Me-Too movement, repeatedly made jokes punching down at the trans and gay communities. Again, Dave still has a major platform, tons of dedicate followers, and is a multi-millionaire. He acts as if his &amp;quot;free speech&amp;quot; has somehow been restricted yet he was and still is now free to say whatever he wants and has consistently been given a platform to do so. How has he in any way been &amp;quot;cancelled?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;--Billy Cosby. A literal rapist. Dose this person deserve to have a platform?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People often use the cancel culture phrase in relation to comedy, as according to them the problem somehow disproportionally affects comedians. I don&amp;#39;t see why people seem to think that comedians are entitled to a platform? People act as if comedy is somehow immune to criticism of its content. That comedy must be &amp;quot;protected speech&amp;quot; in some capacity. I really don&amp;#39;t agree with this, I think comedians should be as open to anyone else is for criticism of the social impact of their content. At the end of the day a comedian&amp;#39;s goal is to make people laugh, and if someone who is trans or gay or otherwise disadvantaged finds a piece of comedy distasteful they&amp;#39;re perfectly justified in saying &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t find this funny and I don&amp;#39;t think this person deserves a platform like this.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps I&amp;#39;m just rambling at this point but I think some people have this odd view in their heads of &amp;quot;free speech.&amp;quot; They think that free speech means that every single person is entitled to a platform that they can use to broadcast their message to others. That every single person has an inalienable human right to use twitter, reddit, youtube, or stand up comedy to spout their views out to the world. In my opinion that&amp;#39;s simply not the case, free speech only entitles you to protection from the federal government in relation to your speech, it doesn&amp;#39;t mean that private institutions such as Netflix or Twitter or whoever has an obligation to use their platform to publish whatever you say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Every social media site would be like 4chan if they all abandoned moderation.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Everybody likes to delude themselves that 4chan is some sort of aberration, a
disgusting pimple on the face of the internet, and that the "real" internet is a
welcoming and wholesome place.

But 4chan is the ONLY place on the internet where all legally protected speech
is permissible, and only…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgq4k1/cmv_every_social_media_site_would_be_like_4chan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgq4k1/cmv_every_social_media_site_would_be_like_4chan/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 16:48:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everybody likes to delude themselves that 4chan is some sort of aberration, a disgusting pimple on the face of the internet, and that the &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; internet is a welcoming and wholesome place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But 4chan is the ONLY place on the internet where all legally protected speech is permissible, and only criminal speech is moderated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4chan is the internet sans additives. It&amp;#39;s actually the rest of the internet that is artificial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the counter argument would be that if a free speech policy became mainstream, then maybe an more polite equilibrium would be reached, but I&amp;#39;m doubtful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think we need to get real with ourselves. Maybe 4chan is really not as abhorrent as we tell ourselves. That&amp;#39;s my view anyway, that 4chan is what the internet was always supposed to be, and it&amp;#39;s actually the normie internet that&amp;#39;s abomination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Waking up early doesn't necessarily mean that you are productive and disciplined and similarly waking up late doesn't necessarily mean that you are unproductive and undisciplined]]></title><description><![CDATA[I don't understand why waking up early is considered a great thing and people
look down on those who wake up late (atleast in my country, India)

I wake up late because I start my work at 10 and if I wake up at 5 in the
morning, I would just be draining my energy till 10. Waking up at 9 and…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgvk0h/cmv_waking_up_early_doesnt_necessarily_mean_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgvk0h/cmv_waking_up_early_doesnt_necessarily_mean_that/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 14:37:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t understand why waking up early is considered a great thing and people look down on those who wake up late (atleast in my country, India)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wake up late because I start my work at 10 and if I wake up at 5 in the morning, I would just be draining my energy till 10. Waking up at 9 and getting ready till 10 makes more sense to me as I need some time for myself after work and as a result I sleep after 1 AM. Similarly, there are people who work in different timezone and start their day at a completely different time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just because someone wakes up earlier doesn&amp;#39;t mean they are disciplined or productive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Abortion is a red herring political issue and gets a disproportionate attention for its impact]]></title><description><![CDATA[It's pretty easy to find abortion advocates, on either side, who treat this as
the ONE issue that will dominate political discourse.

The US has ~610,000 abortions/year. For comparison, heart disease kills
~650K/year and cancer kills ~ 600K/year. We all agree cancer and heart disease
are bad, but…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgjnc9/cmv_abortion_is_a_red_herring_political_issue_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgjnc9/cmv_abortion_is_a_red_herring_political_issue_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 01:12:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s pretty easy to find abortion advocates, on either side, who treat this as the ONE issue that will dominate political discourse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The US has ~610,000 abortions/year. For comparison, heart disease kills ~650K/year and cancer kills ~ 600K/year. We all agree cancer and heart disease are bad, but I&amp;#39;m pretty confident there are more people willing to bomb an abortion clinic than a cigarette factory or chemical plant. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did I miss the memo where everyone decided that 1 baby is worth 10 fat/old people?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I certainly don&amp;#39;t see anyone up in arms over &amp;quot;Dangerous Demographic Shifts!&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Condoms bring make us below replacement rate!&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For women in their child-bearing years, I get it. There&amp;#39;s a lot of impact on their day-to-day lives. Michael J Fox became a lot more interested in Parkinson&amp;#39;s when he was diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every single political issue gets the &amp;quot;Think of the children!&amp;quot; card played on it. I&amp;#39;ve been seeing &amp;quot;Think of the Children&amp;quot; card used for climate change from my literal childhood until I&amp;#39;ve fully grown into an adult, watched EVERY year have record breaking heat waves, and it doesn&amp;#39;t drive the same kind of political energy that abortion generates. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is abortion secretly not a single issue topic for a lot of voters and I got hit with sensationalist media?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is abortion actually way more impactful than aging demographics, climate change, and resource distribution? I&amp;#39;m pretty sure those have more impact on more people&amp;#39;s day to day lives, but don&amp;#39;t drive up nearly the same fervor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Despite disillusioned people, humans are living more privileged and rewarding lives today than they were even 10 years ago.]]></title><description><![CDATA[There are some people that think humanity is only getting worse, all changes
that come forth are bad etc, you know the type. But I don't think that's how it
is. But challenge me. I don't see humanity getting worse, or people getting
worse, but better, even despite the melting pots of people who are…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgic8r/cmv_despite_disillusioned_people_humans_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgic8r/cmv_despite_disillusioned_people_humans_are/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 01:12:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some people that think humanity is only getting worse, all changes that come forth are bad etc, you know the type. But I don&amp;#39;t think that&amp;#39;s how it is. But challenge me. I don&amp;#39;t see humanity getting worse, or people getting worse, but better, even despite the melting pots of people who are disillusioned and/or engaging in bad groups. 
What happened in the last 10 years to make life so good now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food shortages are increasingly being fixed with GMOs and other healthy alternatives to not eating! Science is continually fixing a lot of problems! Plus Vegan food is increasing!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social media allowed us to connect with long lost friends, and almost everyone is internet connected now, all the time, it&amp;#39;s brilliant! Bye Bye huge phone call bills!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are closer and closer to fixing the world poverty problems! The number of people making donations to charitable causes is ever increasing, thanks to the internet!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia got gay marriage approval, about time!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women&amp;#39;s rights are in the best place they&amp;#39;ve been in, yay equality!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men&amp;#39;s problems are at an all time low!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;More BI and Gay couples are being accepted as beautiful people that they always were!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*All in all this wouldn&amp;#39;t be possible without Capitalism, which is definitively the best system ever made without question and spurs the innovations we see today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: it’s not okay to reach out to someone you didn’t match with on other social platforms just because you saw them on Tinder/Bumble]]></title><description><![CDATA[I don’t have my social handles listed on any of my dating profiles but I’ve
still had people be able to find my Instagram as some of them go to the same
college as me and we have mutual followers. I don’t think this is okay as the
fact that we didn’t match should indicate that I may not be…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgegs2/cmv_its_not_okay_to_reach_out_to_someone_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qgegs2/cmv_its_not_okay_to_reach_out_to_someone_you/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 01:12:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t have my social handles listed on any of my dating profiles but I’ve still had people be able to find my Instagram as some of them go to the same college as me and we have mutual followers. I don’t think this is okay as the fact that we didn’t match should indicate that I may not be interested, and it sometimes makes me uncomfortable being randomly reached out to. I also know of women who’ve had someone who found them on tinder (one whom they matched with and one whom they didn’t match with) find them on Facebook and message them, and as we know last names aren’t listed on Tinder and Bumble, so it’s very creepy to me that there are guys who will go out of their way to find someone’s socials just because they saw them on a dating app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve had people say I’m wrong to take issue with guys reaching out to girls they didn’t match with on tinder and bumble as they don’t have bad intentions, but I think the issue for me is respecting boundaries as it does feel invasive. But I’m willing to have my view on this challenged because maybe I am being too hard on these guys, or maybe I’m being a little mean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Taxing unrealized capital gains is an absolutely horrific idea]]></title><description><![CDATA[To illustrate my point, let’s take a simple example:

I buy $100 worth of stock in a company, that stock then appreciates in value to
$500, meaning I owe taxes on $400 worth of “unrealized capital gains”.

If the stock then plummets to $50 in value, all of a sudden I owe the government
for assets I…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qg0l1v/cmv_taxing_unrealized_capital_gains_is_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qg0l1v/cmv_taxing_unrealized_capital_gains_is_an/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 10:32:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate my point, let’s take a simple example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I buy $100 worth of stock in a company, that stock then appreciates in value to $500, meaning I owe taxes on $400 worth of “unrealized capital gains”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the stock then plummets to $50 in value, all of a sudden I owe the government for assets I don’t have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s more, if i have a substantial amount of my overall wealth in the stock market, how am I supposed to pay taxes on unrealized capital gains if I don’t have sufficient liquidity outside of the stock market to do so? I’d be forced to liquidate some of my shares (paying capital gains taxes on them), simply to pay another tax. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seems like a recipe for crashing the stock market as far as I can tell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: College in the U.S. isn't free because doing so would severely lower military recruitment numbers.]]></title><description><![CDATA[One of the largest selling points of joining the military is that you get a
large stipend to spend on your post-secondary education through the GI Bill.
Talking to many recruits and veterans, many of them bring up joining the army to
pay off their college education because they didn't want to deal…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qfwx95/cmv_college_in_the_us_isnt_free_because_doing_so/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qfwx95/cmv_college_in_the_us_isnt_free_because_doing_so/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 05:35:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the largest selling points of joining the military is that you get a large stipend to spend on your post-secondary education through the GI Bill. Talking to many recruits and veterans, many of them bring up joining the army to pay off their college education because they didn&amp;#39;t want to deal with Student Debt or having to ask people for money. If these programs weren&amp;#39;t given, they personally wouldn&amp;#39;t have gone to the military. If nationalized free college was realized in the U.S., many high schoolers would see no reason to join the army, and so recruitment numbers would fall drastically. Only the most patriotic members of society would volunteer into the military leaving the other potential recruits to get a post-secondary education. Of course, this could also just lead to the re-enactment of the draft and forced service, which is seen in other countries around the world (South Korea, Vietnam, ect).   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. There&amp;#39;s an interesting article that goes into this idea more. &lt;a href=&quot;https://warontherocks.com/2016/09/does-free-college-threaten-our-all-volunteer-military/&quot;&gt;https://warontherocks.com/2016/09/does-free-college-threaten-our-all-volunteer-military/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: It’s not an employees responsibility to find a replacement]]></title><description><![CDATA[I remember when I first started working, as long as someone gave a few days
notice before calling off, the manager would handle scheduling. It was nice if
you had already found someone to fill in for you but it wasn’t an expectation.

But it seems at some point that changed where now the employee is…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qfscr7/cmv_its_not_an_employees_responsibility_to_find_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qfscr7/cmv_its_not_an_employees_responsibility_to_find_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 01:44:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I remember when I first started working, as long as someone gave a few days notice before calling off, the manager would handle scheduling. It was nice if you had already found someone to fill in for you but it wasn’t an expectation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it seems at some point that changed where now the employee is expected to coordinate this in order to call off. This makes no sense. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The boss/manager knows everyone’s schedule, when they’re working, when they’re off, when they’re on vacation, what projects they have going on and likely knows who maybe looking for more hours or is also requesting off that may coincidence with the date. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this is just a way to discourage employees from taking days off, but in my mind it’s not their responsibility. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can anyone give me a any good reason why an employee should have to do this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To make my CMV clearer what I’m asking is “what’s is the practical purpose of requiring an employee to find a replacement other than to discourage people taking time off”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Apartments should reserve their ground floors for tenants with mobility handicaps OR something needs to be done about the stairs/fire escapes]]></title><description><![CDATA[Imagine the apartment you live in catches on fire and you live on the third
floor. You get to the elevator but of course there’s a sign that says “in case
of fire use stairs” Seems easy enough, right? But what if you’re in a wheelchair
or scooter. You can’t use the stairs so your only options are…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qfma4w/cmv_apartments_should_reserve_their_ground_floors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qfma4w/cmv_apartments_should_reserve_their_ground_floors/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 19:32:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine the apartment you live in catches on fire and you live on the third floor. You get to the elevator but of course there’s a sign that says “in case of fire use stairs” Seems easy enough, right? But what if you’re in a wheelchair or scooter. You &lt;em&gt;can’t&lt;/em&gt; use the stairs so your only options are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A) Hope a neighbor is able to carry you down or;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B) Hope a firefighter finds you before you inhale too much smoke or the flames get too close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How is that fair or even safe? Buildings are already to meet fire-code regulations so what harm is there in adding a few more even if you never &lt;em&gt;expect&lt;/em&gt; the building to catch fire?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, forcing people who have mobility handicaps to live on the ground floor could be seen as a form of discrimination and therefore illegal, which is why I added the second part in there. Instead of having stairs, apartments could have ramps so &lt;em&gt;in case of&lt;/em&gt; a fire, a tenant confined to a wheelchair who lives on the third floor could wheel themselves down or have another tenant help them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: saying ‘sex work is real work’ is dangerous]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m less inclined to change my view on this topic, more interested to hear
opposing views; I am, however, open to re-evaluating my position and realise my
logic may be wrong.

I am not saying that sex work isn’t HARD work, even in the slightest. I just
feel that the line between ‘lingeries on…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qff4qj/cmv_saying_sex_work_is_real_work_is_dangerous/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qff4qj/cmv_saying_sex_work_is_real_work_is_dangerous/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:32:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m less inclined to change my view on this topic, more interested to hear opposing views; I am, however, open to re-evaluating my position and realise my logic may be wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not saying that sex work isn’t HARD work, even in the slightest. I just feel that the line between ‘lingeries on OnlyFans’ and straight prostitution should be VERY bold, and saying things like ‘sex work is real work’ just blurs that line. I’m 17, and a lot of girls at my school have seriously considered turning to OnlyFans for quick money, and I just find it disturbing - not empowering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: burgers ARE sandwiches.]]></title><description><![CDATA[it boggles my mind how many people I've met who think that burgers aren't
sandwiches. it's crazy. they're so obviously sandwiches. the definition of a
sandwich is 2 pieces of bread, crackers etc, with something between them. a
burger is 2 bread buns with a beef (sometimes chicken) patty in the…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qfc094/cmv_burgers_are_sandwiches/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qfc094/cmv_burgers_are_sandwiches/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 15:35:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;it boggles my mind how many people I&amp;#39;ve met who think that burgers aren&amp;#39;t sandwiches. it&amp;#39;s crazy. they&amp;#39;re so obviously sandwiches. the definition of a sandwich is 2 pieces of bread, crackers etc, with something between them. a burger is 2 bread buns with a beef (sometimes chicken) patty in the middle. how is that not a sandwich? they try arguing with me that it&amp;#39;s a cob or a calzone. but a cob is just a round loaf of bread and a calzone is a type of PIZZA! these people out here tryna tell me that pizza is a burger! CMV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: neo-pronouns are selfish]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m all for trans rights, gender roles should burn in flames and gender
identities should rise from the ashes, but we have 3 pronouns everyone is used
to, he, she, and they. if none of these apply to you, you can’t get offended
when your own personal unique pronoun isn’t used, because you’re forcing…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qfccof/cmv_neopronouns_are_selfish/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qfccof/cmv_neopronouns_are_selfish/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 10:30:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m all for trans rights, gender roles should burn in flames and gender identities should rise from the ashes, but we have 3 pronouns everyone is used to, he, she, and they. if none of these apply to you, you can’t get offended when your own personal unique pronoun isn’t used, because you’re forcing people to break years of speaking habits for a non-reason. They is non-gendered, it should apply to everyone, so i should be able to use it on anyone without offending anyone. also, other-kin are not gender identities and should not have their own pronouns, we still call dogs he or she&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: why are people downvoting my thought-out replies? if my take is bad, change it instead of just saying it’s bad, that’s what the sub is about, isn’t it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Belief systems that rely heavily on shame are abusive.]]></title><description><![CDATA[We seem to agree as a society that shame is harmful to mental health, and is
particularly harmful to children. In my state, intentionally leading a child to
believe that he or she is bad or defective is considered emotional abuse or
neglect. It's grounds to involve social services. Some examples of…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qf2108/cmv_belief_systems_that_rely_heavily_on_shame_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qf2108/cmv_belief_systems_that_rely_heavily_on_shame_are/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 04:44:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We seem to agree as a society that shame is harmful to mental health, and is particularly harmful to children. In my state, intentionally leading a child to believe that he or she is bad or defective is considered emotional abuse or neglect. It&amp;#39;s grounds to involve social services. Some examples of this are calling your child degrading names, convincing them there is something wrong with them, or generally subjecting them to cruel verbal treatment. My state has relatively stringent child-protective laws. However, there seems to be a broader consensus that making a child believe they are bad - not that they did something bad, but that they *are* bad - is harmful to their self esteem and therefore their mental health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are widely held belief systems that employ shame and fear as core tenets. The idea that we are defective is indoctrinated in children from a young age. Beyond simply saying that humans are flawed, personal shortcomings and failures are emphasized. The shame of one&amp;#39;s actions, and the fear of judgment or punishment for these actions, is central to many worldviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we have decided that people, and especially children, are entitled to positive self esteem, then it seems all our institutions should be held to this standard. Again, this assumption varies widely across parts of the US and the world. But in general, we seem to agree that emotional safety is worth striving for, and shame-based belief systems contradict this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, &amp;quot;abuse&amp;quot; is a strong word. But I believe that intentional shaming is emotional and psychological abuse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Tribalism is the biggest obstacle in achieving a true Democracy. And the entire system needs to change to make this happen.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mainly using my points here regarding US politics as the issue is most
pronounced there, but this does apply to other democratic politics aswell.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tribalism

Modern democracy still has a long way to go until it is the idealized system
it's often described as. But I…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qeqaa5/cmv_tribalism_is_the_biggest_obstacle_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qeqaa5/cmv_tribalism_is_the_biggest_obstacle_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 19:30:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mainly using my points here regarding US politics as the issue is most pronounced there, but this does apply to other democratic politics aswell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tribalism&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tribalism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modern democracy still has a long way to go until it is the idealized system it&amp;#39;s often described as. But I think even things like lobbying/corruption aren&amp;#39;t holding it back as much as tribalism does. First of all it&amp;#39;s the reason we even have a two party system in place. Because in theory we don&amp;#39;t. You can vote third party and even submit write-ins for just about everyone. But if it isn&amp;#39;t corrupt-change-absolutely-nothing-party-A or corrupt-change-absolutely-nothing-party-B, your vote doesn&amp;#39;t really matter. Meaning over time most people will become a Party A or Party B supporter, and why wouldn&amp;#39;t they?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tribalism is a completely natural sociological phenomenon, almost every human experiences it in one way or another. Often times it isn&amp;#39;t even destructive. In politics, it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Correct me if I&amp;#39;m wrong, but isn&amp;#39;t the point of democracy to naturally create a economic and ethical system that the plurality of citizens agrees on? That&amp;#39;s not an achievable goal if people partake in destructive behavior just to &amp;quot;stick it to the other side&amp;quot;, or even sadder, actively self-destructive one just so they get validation from their group of people. It&amp;#39;s always us vs them, and that can be a good topic of debate if we&amp;#39;re talking about a singular ethical topic. But more often than not tribalism is the exact thing that prevents people from using their critical thinking skills. They see &amp;quot;us vs them&amp;quot; not as a moral dilemma regarding all our lives, but as two football teams going at it and if your team wins you party no matter how or why they got there. The politicians themselves use this aswell, as they less and less talk about their actual values and more and more about why the other party is dogshit and their candidate did something questionable 30 years ago or something like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not too educated in political theory to propose a better system, but we could start with the fact that we should be voting for the values themselves, not human beings representing a political party. This is already being done on small scale votes to great effect. Oftentimes the only problem being that not enough people participate. On a national scale this could make people a lot less ignorant and when they debate politics, they&amp;#39;d actually debate what politics is about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: In a humane society, painless assisted suicide should be legal for all 25+ people.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The reason for the age restriction is that people's brains are not done
developing until their mid-twenties, and because there are a lot of fluctuations
in emotions and life circumstances in your youth. There should be a time lock
after signing up for the assisted euthanasia where you have to wait…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qeufza/cmv_in_a_humane_society_painless_assisted_suicide/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qeufza/cmv_in_a_humane_society_painless_assisted_suicide/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 17:35:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason for the age restriction is that people&amp;#39;s brains are not done developing until their mid-twenties, and because there are a lot of fluctuations in emotions and life circumstances in your youth. There should be a time lock after signing up for the assisted euthanasia where you have to wait at least a minimum amount of time (1-5 years maybe), and during that period, you have to be seeing a therapist and psychiatrist continually. In fact, it should probably be mandatory that the euthanasia seeker take part in a rigorous therapeutic program for the duration. If, after that period of time, you still want assisted suicide, then you should be able to have it so that you can die with dignity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who are determined enough to commit suicide will do so anyway, but usually in a more painful and undignified way, and in a way that requires loved ones or emergency personnel to find the results. Some people truly do not enjoy life due to physiological factors and no treatment succeeds in &amp;#39;curing&amp;#39; them. They should have the right to end their suffering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inevitable response whenever this topic comes up is that the person might regret it. But people may regret many permanent decisions; this does not mean they don&amp;#39;t have the right to make that choice in order to end unbearable pain with no end in sight. In fact, even if there WAS a definite end that could be predicted, and the person said, &amp;quot;It&amp;#39;s not worth it to me to tough it out until then&amp;quot; ... that would still be valid, and their decision should still be respected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Cancel culture is a manipulative tactic used to silence people.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cancel culture is annoying. No one is perfect so we all make mistakes but what's
annoying about this is how people exploit these mistakes to use you as a
strawman by looking for hipocrisy in your words.

I just can't help but see that as a way to undermine an opponent and not as a
way to promote a…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qesnb3/cmv_cancel_culture_is_a_manipulative_tactic_used/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qesnb3/cmv_cancel_culture_is_a_manipulative_tactic_used/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 16:50:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancel culture is annoying. No one is perfect so we all make mistakes but what&amp;#39;s annoying about this is how people exploit these mistakes to use you as a strawman by looking for hipocrisy in your words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just can&amp;#39;t help but see that as a way to undermine an opponent and not as a way to promote a healthy discussion. Its nowadays used as a way to one-up someone when you say something thet don&amp;#39;t like under a thin veil of a moral high ground. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The people who look deep in someone&amp;#39;s post history are especially guilty of this as you see celebrities cancelled out because of tweets they said years ago, for example. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its actions like these that make it pretty obvious that people are just looking to dig up dirt on you. Honestly, I think people who cancel others out should be ignored altogether because its kind of a bait into humiliating you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since when did anyone who didn&amp;#39;t like me care about my consistency? That&amp;#39;s a red flag in my mind. If you want to shut someone up this way just to gain points over someone else then how are you better than that person? You&amp;#39;re just trying to control the narrative at this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: MLK was entirely against rioting and to say otherwise is to misquote and misrepresent him.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Honestly, I’m not entirely sure how I feel in regards to rioting as a form of
protest, but regardless of that, I feel that when leftists say something along
the lines of “well actually, MLK did riot and supported rioting actually!” I
just can’t help but chuckle to myself and shake my head in…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qecw4q/cmv_mlk_was_entirely_against_rioting_and_to_say/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qecw4q/cmv_mlk_was_entirely_against_rioting_and_to_say/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 12:34:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I’m not entirely sure how I feel in regards to rioting as a form of protest, but regardless of that, I feel that when leftists say something along the lines of “well actually, MLK did riot and supported rioting actually!” I just can’t help but chuckle to myself and shake my head in disprovable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s unfortunate because I’ve been delving into leftist politics and watching debates, and every time a leftist in a debate brings this up, I go to research it. Every time I do, I always wind up finding videos of MLK directly saying that he believes rioting makes people more immoral and that it’s wrong and other such things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand he stated that “rioting is the voice of the unheard” but I still feel as if that wasn’t an approval of rioting, but more so just MLK playing devil’s advocate and explaining to the interviewer why people feel as though they should riot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like my mind to be changed on this and I’m more than willing to have my view swayed, I just can’t seem to find an article or video that can truly convince me to see it that way, and so I figured I’d come here as a last resort since I know that Reddit is overwhelming left leaning from my observations. My hope is that a big brained leftist chad will prove to me exactly why MLK supported riots and actually started some of his own that he never came to regret or something like that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: singing a song or lyric that has the n-word in it does not make you a bad person nor should it count towards being racist]]></title><description><![CDATA[I understand that there is a LOT of baggage and history and context behind the n
word that me as a non-black person couldn’t fully understand. With that said
however, I cannot understand the logic behind not being able to sing a lyric
containing said n word without being labeled a racist, other than…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qel3pm/cmv_singing_a_song_or_lyric_that_has_the_nword_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qel3pm/cmv_singing_a_song_or_lyric_that_has_the_nword_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 09:38:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I understand that there is a LOT of baggage and history and context behind the n word that me as a non-black person couldn’t fully understand. With that said however, I cannot understand the logic behind not being able to sing a lyric containing said n word without being labeled a racist, other than simply “rules for thee and not for me”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve heard some of the common arguments about how the usage is justified as reclaiming the word or taking away it’s power, etc. but if that was truly the goal then there should be no problem with people using it colloquially without bad intentions such as in a song. I think we’re all smart enough to understand the context of someone’s words, yet when it comes to this one there’s no room for forgiveness. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This leads to the most common response lately: “just don’t use it, why do white people want to say it so badly?”etc. To which I’d respond right back “yeah exactly why do we still use it at all?” Which usually leads to the justification above in a loop of messed up logic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another response might talk about the history of slavery in the US, and general racism worldwide, to the effect of “it’s simple: if you’re black you can use it if you want, if you’re not, then don’t”. This is just societal norms at work but logically is a slippery slope of anybody with any history of marginalization or mistreatment being allowed to have exclusive say on some word or phrase. Imagine a multiracial/ethnic/sexual orientation group put out a very catchy hit song widely distributed where the lyrics at one point state every sort of slur to every group imaginable. Who should be allowed to sing these lyrics? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope I’m making sense in that I hear lots of arguments but I simply find them logically unsound and thus I cannot accept the line of reasoning. Not to say I use the word in a casual manner at all, I’m on the unironic side of “nobody should be using it at all, given its history”. I think we’re all mature and socially aware enough to know when someone IS saying it in a harmful manner or simply singing a song. Or perhaps saying it casually which may speak to their sheltered upbringing or environment. Or maybe they actually are racist. All this to say context should matter but for some reason it doesn’t. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;either the word is so hurtful and hate filled that absolutely nobody should be using it INCLUDING BLACK PEOPLE, or it’s a word like so many others that has grown to have multiple meanings and intentions depending on its context and therefore should be treated exactly as such&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: since I have to make this clear: I do not want to say the word, I am not jealous about not being “allowed” to say the word. I think that singing lyrics is not the same as saying it in conversation or in passing. Apparently that’s not the case and to even posit that the logical flaw against this makes someone a horrible person has been very tiring to read. My entire point of this post is not to complain that I’m not allowed to say it, it’s that I’d like to hear arguments changing my view on being able to discern lyrics from casual use without applying two different sets of justifications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Echo chambers and engagement-focused media are causing unprecedented division and damage to society]]></title><description><![CDATA[In recent years it seems that many subjects have become much more divisive. I
don't want to dwell on who's right, because my concern isn't about right or
wrong, but about our ability as a society to live together with these growing
differences.

Politics - In the USA there you can…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qecx2k/cmv_echo_chambers_and_engagementfocused_media_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qecx2k/cmv_echo_chambers_and_engagementfocused_media_are/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 01:44:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent years it seems that many subjects have become much more divisive. I don&amp;#39;t want to dwell on who&amp;#39;s right, because my concern isn&amp;#39;t about right or wrong, but about our ability as a society to live together with these growing differences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Politics&lt;/strong&gt; - In the USA there you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/animation-rise-partisanship-congress-house-representatives-60-years-2016-4?jwsource=cl&quot;&gt;see&lt;/a&gt; how the party-line voting and partisanship increased in the recent 20 years. The situation is also strikingly similar in my country - Voting outside your &amp;quot;block&amp;quot; becomes increasingly irregular. At the same time, the conversation and arguments become increasingly aggressive and hateful. This divide also translated to what the common voter of either party thinks of a voter of a different party. The divide is so great that it even affects family and friends&amp;#39; relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Science vs Anti-Science&lt;/strong&gt; - The anti-science/conspiracy group is no longer a tiny minority. From flat-earth, climate-change-deniers, and vaccine-skeptics. There is a huge influx of people that deny and reject the specialists and the government or science-mandated facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are just 2 examples. But there are plenty of other subjects where I can feel a growing division.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The major blame, in my opinion, lies in the way we consume the media nowadays:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engagement-focused sites -&lt;/strong&gt; Sites like YouTube and Facebook are engagement-focused - They try to present you videos that you&amp;#39;ll be engaged in. That often means that if you saw a left-leaning video you will see much more of these in your feed. Unsurprisingly, the more extreme the content you&amp;#39;re viewing, the more engaged and outraged you might be. This exacerbates the problem - Even if you started with relatively pragmatic views, watching increasingly aggressive media/news will have an effect to make your opinion more extreme as well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Echo chambers&lt;/strong&gt; - Instead of relying on a central and mainstream news source, people create their own thought echo chambers. This relates to news sites addressed to specific demographics (e.g &amp;quot;Fox News&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Mother Jones&amp;quot;) and sites in which you can pick and choose your &amp;quot;subjects of interest&amp;quot; like Reddit. These sites lock people in a reality in which everyone agrees with them, locking them into a positive loop in which every new content reaffirms and solidifies their opinion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel that every day it gets worse and we, as a society, become less pragmatic. Worse, I don&amp;#39;t see any easy solution to this issue that doesn&amp;#39;t involve heavy-handed internet censorship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this indeed how I think it is? Or do I get something wrong and isn&amp;#39;t any worse than it has been in the past?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;#39;d just would like to emphasize that this isn&amp;#39;t USA problem - It is, in my eyes, global country. This extremism and devision seems to be increasing all around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: “African Americans” have more culture in common with white Americans than they do people from Africa.]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you are born and raised in the United States then you are an American,
especially in the working class. We share the same culture, deal with the same
struggles. My message I’m trying to get across here is that if we stop being so
tribal we might can make a difference. Black or white doesn’t…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qegdrg/cmv_african_americans_have_more_culture_in_common/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qegdrg/cmv_african_americans_have_more_culture_in_common/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 01:44:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are born and raised in the United States then you are an American, especially in the working class. We share the same culture, deal with the same struggles. My message I’m trying to get across here is that if we stop being so tribal we might can make a difference. Black or white doesn’t matter we both have shit wages, shit healthcare, and shit education. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes White privilege exists. Yes people of color face more discrimination. The 1% doesn’t want us to be equal and fights hard for us to be as divided as possible, stop letting that happen. We are all hard working Americans and we all deserve better, but we are only gonna be better together as the 99%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: A gun is always loaded, regardless of who you are, what situation you are in, or what others around you have told you.]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was drilled into my mind a thousand times, I am curious if people think
there are legitimate cases where this doesn't apply. I was always told that
regardless of whether or not you just checked the gun, or just finished firing
it, or any other set of circumstances, the only safe way to approach…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qefoon/cmv_a_gun_is_always_loaded_regardless_of_who_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qefoon/cmv_a_gun_is_always_loaded_regardless_of_who_you/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:33:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was drilled into my mind a thousand times, I am curious if people think there are legitimate cases where this doesn&amp;#39;t apply. I was always told that regardless of whether or not you just checked the gun, or just finished firing it, or any other set of circumstances, the only safe way to approach gun handling is to assume the weapon is always loaded and act accordingly. I consider this to be a golden rule of firearms and I am curious if others do too. I feel like many negligent discharges would be avoided if this rule was being strictly followed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: We should’ve never shipped manufacturing to China (or overseas in general).]]></title><description><![CDATA[I feel as though our major manufacturing shift from our countries to overseas
(and especially China) has had many devastating economic, ethical and even
economical issues throughout the past 40 years.

I’m not suggesting we should be “America first” when it comes to a lot of
things, but I do believe…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qeban8/cmv_we_shouldve_never_shipped_manufacturing_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qeban8/cmv_we_shouldve_never_shipped_manufacturing_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:33:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I feel as though our major manufacturing shift from our countries to overseas (and especially China) has had many devastating economic, ethical and even economical issues throughout the past 40 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not suggesting we should be “America first” when it comes to a lot of things, but I do believe we really bit ourselves when we thought “Hey, let’s shift everything to their and screw ourselves in the process!”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a few reasons why I personally believe this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major loss of accessible, middle class jobs: Seriously, why is it that I (and many people of my generation) have to put down thousands in debt just to get a degree for decent jobs that aren’t even guaranteed anymore when my grandparents could’ve gotten a good job right outta high school? Why have we been seeing major economic inequalities in the US alone? The only people who’ve really benefitted from this is the 1% who own these factories and companies. Honestly? The people in places like China barely get paid Jack and don’t even work in decent conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supply chain issues: This has especially been apparent in the last year. When you have whole store shelves empty because half of the stuff has been stuck on boats for weeks on end (and a lot of it being very important stuff), it’s pretty hard not to blame our economic policies in the past 40 years. I’d guarantee we wouldn’t have these issues had we been smarter and actually kept making most, if not all, of our things like we previously did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ecological impact: I’m not suggesting companies in the “good ol’ days” were much better (see: rivers in rust belt cities circa 1965), but at least we actually had controls and regulations of these companies when they were in &lt;em&gt;our&lt;/em&gt; countries. When a good chunk of CO2 emissions and what not come from China, on top of all the transportation involved, it’s gonna cause major problems. It’s just so simple: A T-shirt made with all-American cotton, in an American factory and shipped only on American soil is gonna have a smaller ecological footprint than the vast majority of stuff we import now. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major loss in product quality: To be fair, the connections between quality and country of origin on this one might be sketchy. When Japan became a major exporter in the 70’s-80’s, at least their stuff tended to be of better quality (sometimes better than their Western counterparts). Still, I do believe that our products would improve overall if we didn’t rely so much on imports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bad pricing expectations: This is admittedly hard for me to explain, but I’ll try my best here: Back when a lot of things were American made, many people didn’t bat an eye on the costs. Yes, $100 for a TV in 1953 sounds silly, but this is before inflation. Inflated to today’s cash, that would be a lot more (around $1000 or more). That sounds crazy, but why did they seemingly have no problems with this, unlike now where it’s all about the lowest prices? Well, the thing is, not only were a lot of things back then of better quality, but we also were &lt;em&gt;paid&lt;/em&gt; better overall to afford these costs for products. When everyone’s like “We gotta keep everything at a low low price”, not only do we sacrifice quality (to the point where even major appliances now last a lot less longer than before), but we even see low wages, low working conditions and even more ecological problems (replacing cotton with synthetic fibers because “it’s cheaper” has some significant ecological hazards, as seen with microfibers. Same with low-quality electronics that are dumped in waste fields). Sometimes, low prices are not always a good thing. Low housing or food costs? Ok. Low costs for clothes or electronics that’ll dump out after a while, though? It doesn’t help that a lot of low wage earner who bust their butts to work at places like crappy dollar stores tend to be minorities who’s only job prospects are holes like these. Honestly, probably the best thing about the labor shortage has been in forcing companies to actually &lt;em&gt;pay their employees better&lt;/em&gt;. I hope this point made some form of sense. It’s a whole messy cycle that I rarely hear other people discuss, unfortunately, but I think it does play a role in this CMV. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s probably more I haven’t considered, but these are the big ones that come to mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: A lot of people are saying that I’m suggesting that we should close all importing. I should’ve been more clear on this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not suggesting that imports are necessarily wrong. In some countries (unless something like vertical farming becomes common), it’s almost a necessity. Importing is not inherently wrong. I also do realize that America’s been doing this even in the “good ol’ days” (see the famous Japanese tin toys of the 50’s). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I meant to say is that we should’ve still provided more manufacturing options here and kept ourselves competitive and active.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: The solution to lack of representation in historical media is not to shoehorn it where it doesn't belong, but rather to tell a wider variety of stories.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm not against representation in media. While I don't personally care much
about it, I recognize that it matters to a lot of people and is ultimately
necessary. However, in regards to historical pieces, I think that forcing
representation in cases where it does not make sense is bad. Instead, we…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qed8ym/cmv_the_solution_to_lack_of_representation_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qed8ym/cmv_the_solution_to_lack_of_representation_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 22:34:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not against representation in media. While I don&amp;#39;t personally care much about it, I recognize that it matters to a lot of people and is ultimately necessary. However, in regards to historical pieces, I think that forcing representation in cases where it does not make sense is bad. Instead, we should be focusing on creating historical media which tells a broader array of stories throughout the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stuff like making a quarter of the WW1 German army black in Battlefield 1 is shit representation. It is not only inauthentic and borderline historical revisionism, but it just gives an excuse for the same old stories to be told. Europe is not the only place in the world with a history, there are plenty of fascinating opportunities for historical media to be set everywhere in the world- even if these are just a different perspective on things we have already seen. Example: why is there still next to no mainstream media portraying WWII in China? Or about the Mali Empire? It seems odd that we encourage forcing representation in the same stories instead of encouraging the exploration of new ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Conservatives use identity politics just as much as the left does.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Edit: No, I'm not saying that all Conservatives do this Conservatives use
identity politics in these ways and I agree that calling black conservatives
racial slurs or race based insults is racist and it makes me cringe whenever I
see someone do that

 1. Claiming that it is racist for a white…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qe8nw6/cmv_conservatives_use_identity_politics_just_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qe8nw6/cmv_conservatives_use_identity_politics_just_as/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 19:36:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Edit: No, I&amp;#39;m not saying that all Conservatives do this
Conservatives use identity politics in these ways and I agree that calling black conservatives racial slurs or race based insults is racist and it makes me cringe whenever I see someone do that&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Claiming that it is racist for a white liberal or leftist to make fun of or criticize an individual black conservative without mentioning race. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Claiming that if you can find a small amount of black people or other POC that agree with you that something white liberals think is racist isnt, that means that most black people or POC think that the thing white liberals think is racist isn&amp;#39;t and white liberals are just getting offended on their behalf &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using the existence of gay and black conservatives to prove that they aren&amp;#39;t racist or homophobic and tokenizing them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Claiming that it is impossible for a black or gay person to have any racist or homophobic views&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of these things are usually done in bad faith as an attempt to &amp;quot;own the libs&amp;quot; based on a complete misunderstanding of what liberals and leftists actually believe. I think it&amp;#39;s much more defensible to use identity politics to try to solve issues relating to race then to use it to call someone else a hypocrite based on something that only seems hypocritical if you have a complete misunderstanding of what anti racists actually claim to believe. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I&amp;#39;m pretty sure that Trumps rhetoric about immigrants and Tucker Carlsons rhetoric about white people being replaced by minorities in order to take away their voting power and the accusations of Democrats keeping black voters on a &amp;quot;democratic plantation&amp;quot; and all the stuff about fighting anti white racism counts as identity politics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: "Thou Shall Not Rape" Is An Example Of A Universal Law]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Universal Law, according to Kant's Categorical Imperative, should be able to
be followed by everyone, with absolutely no exceptions.

There is no situation that I can think of in which this maxim should be
violated. This is because rape is never a solution to a problem. A person will
not die due…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qe7eu0/cmv_thou_shall_not_rape_is_an_example_of_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qe7eu0/cmv_thou_shall_not_rape_is_an_example_of_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 18:40:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Universal Law, according to Kant&amp;#39;s Categorical Imperative, should be able to be followed by everyone, with absolutely no exceptions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no situation that I can think of in which this maxim should be violated. This is because rape is never a solution to a problem. A person will not die due to a lack of sex. They may suffer mentally and emotionally but not solely from the lack of sex. Rape also does not allow a person to gain anything other than sex. You do not gain money from sex. And you do not gain any other necessity from sex. Rape also cannot protect a person from a situation, at least not in any situation that murder is a much better solution. For example, if a person broke into your home, it would be better for your safety if you were to kill the person or run away than of you were to rape them. And now that it I established that rape is never a practical solution, it follows that thou shall not rape is a good personal maxim. Everyone should follow it, and there would be no situation in which a person should rape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: The term "gatekeeping" has no place in conversations about mental health diagnoses]]></title><description><![CDATA[What I mean is, if someone says they have autism, but do not have any/enough of
the symptoms of autism to meet criteria for that diagnosis, it is not
"gatekeeping" to say they do not have autism. Diagnoses are definitions of
diifferent types brains and/or different types of human suffering based…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qe3wj0/cmv_the_term_gatekeeping_has_no_place_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qe3wj0/cmv_the_term_gatekeeping_has_no_place_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 15:41:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What I mean is, if someone says they have autism, but do not have any/enough of the symptoms of autism to meet criteria for that diagnosis, it is not &amp;quot;gatekeeping&amp;quot; to say they do not have autism. Diagnoses are definitions of diifferent types brains and/or different types of human suffering based on criteria that either are or are not met. That&amp;#39;s how definitions work; if you don&amp;#39;t meet the criteria, the definition doesn&amp;#39;t apply to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The one place where the gatekeeping argument makes more sense to me is in the context of self-diagnosis of conditions someone does meet criteria for; people rightfully point out that not everyone has equal access to mental healthcare. BUT! The legitimization of self-diagnosis is a very, VERY slippery slope that ends with people:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a) not taking responsibility for behaviors they actually do have control over&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b) over-pathologizing themselves/believing they are &amp;quot;ill&amp;quot; when they may not be&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;c) deciding that this one diagnosis explains their whole identity, thereby missing the opportunity for deeper identity exploration&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;d) ending up in my office (I&amp;#39;m a therapist) insisting they have bipolar disorder when they meet none of the criteria but they have &amp;quot;like crazy mood swings dude&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I get that people want to belong. I get that people are deeply longing for a sense of identity, meaning, and a way of understanding their struggles in a way that&amp;#39;s not a moral/value judgment. But that conversation has no place in mental health; a disorder is a problem - you shouldn&amp;#39;t want one! The gatekeeping argument has gone too far, and it has gone into the wrong territory. You can&amp;#39;t &amp;quot;identify&amp;quot; as someone with diabetes; you either have it or you don&amp;#39;t. Why should you be able to &amp;quot;identify&amp;quot; as someone with schizophrenia?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL; DR: the gatekeeping argument doesn&amp;#39;t make sense in the context of literal healthcare where conditions are either present or they are not. I get that our measurement tools aren&amp;#39;t as precise as they are in the rest of medicine, but we have to use the tools we have, which are the criteria literally designed to diagnose things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Constitutional monarchies have no place in modern society.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The reason I'm only talking about constitutional ones, like what we've got in
Europe, is that even if there's a democracy in place and the monarch is just a
figurehead, the position of head of state is still inherited and taxpayers have
to fund the expenses (which includes security) of an entire…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qdpsrn/cmv_constitutional_monarchies_have_no_place_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qdpsrn/cmv_constitutional_monarchies_have_no_place_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 08:41:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason I&amp;#39;m only talking about constitutional ones, like what we&amp;#39;ve got in Europe, is that even if there&amp;#39;s a democracy in place and the monarch is just a figurehead, the position of head of state is still inherited and taxpayers have to fund the expenses (which includes security) of an entire family whose members have done nothing to deserve their status other than having been born to the right person. While that doesn&amp;#39;t apply exclusively to the royal family, citizens aren&amp;#39;t required to fund millionaires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anything they do, including acting as ambassadors to foreign countries, can be done by elected officials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: The most plausible outcome of death is eternal oblivion.]]></title><description><![CDATA[i believed in god and a afterlife until the last week or so when i started to
question my beliefs, alot of the stuff does not make sense to me, one of these
things is the afterlife,

As far as we know now conciousness (most likely) is connected the brain, And
when we die, the brain does not fully…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qdr0x3/cmv_the_most_plausible_outcome_of_death_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qdr0x3/cmv_the_most_plausible_outcome_of_death_is/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 04:31:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;i believed in god and a afterlife until the last week or so when i started to question my beliefs, alot of the stuff does not make sense to me, one of these things is the afterlife,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as we know now conciousness (most likely) is connected the brain, And when we die, the brain does not fully die yet (explaining NDES And OOBES), therefore we experience nothing. forever, Your body decomposes and thats it, thats all you get, no white lights, no angels, no reuniting with lost family and friends, Sure its depressing but i don&amp;#39;t have faith, I understand we can&amp;#39;t prove that a afterlife does or does not exist but    eternal oblivion makes way more sense than anything where you keep conciousness&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>