<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 12:45:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 签名是一个过时的、无用的系统，用于证明任何文件的身份。]]></title><description><![CDATA[明确地说，我所说的无用是指 "在做他们打算做的事情时没有效果"。在这里
在这种情况下，这意味着要确定有关人员的身份。

基本上，任何时候使用签名，它的目的都是无用的。这里有一些
例子。

 1. 正式电子邮件底部的签名，在他们的名字旁边...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r5548e/cmv_signatures_are_an_antiquated_useless_system/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r5548e/cmv_signatures_are_an_antiquated_useless_system/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:12:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO BE CLEAR, By useless I mean &amp;quot;Ineffective at doing what they intend to do&amp;quot;. In this context, that means identifying the person in question&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically any time a signature is used. it&amp;#39;s purpose is useless. Here are some examples:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A signature at the bottom of a formal email, next to their name and contact information&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A legal document or &amp;quot;official&amp;quot; document, like something signed by a university, with a chairman head&amp;#39;s signature at the bottom&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any document or form YOU sign where you include your signature.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all of these cases, a signature can be faked very easily either digitally or by faking it yourself with some practice - Any remotely talented penman could fake almost any signature with enough practice, so simple put, absolutely nothing about a signature confirms that the person who claimed they wrote something actually wrote it. Moreover, it&amp;#39;s not like signatures are a very good way of identifying people in the first place, seeing as most devolve into something you can&amp;#39;t read, and in a sea of millions of people, there is surely lots of many overlaps by many. I&amp;#39;ve seen signatures that have literally devolved into just a squiggle with no letters! Others look like circles. In theory, it can be anything. It&amp;#39;s such a poorly contrived security system that I think people know actually doesn&amp;#39;t mean anything -- It&amp;#39;s the same reason why I just filled out a form for the dentist and my signature came out terrible and incoherent, but it doesn&amp;#39;t matter and I didn&amp;#39;t care, nor did the dentists&amp;#39; office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that the only practical use of signatures is to scare people into agreement / convince people that under this arbitrary system, a signature means something so if you signed off on it, you&amp;#39;re obligated to be honest and in agreement. Realistically it has never meant anything. Programs like Docusign just let you copy and paste signatures from a given selection of handwriting! And of course, any mobile form of a signature, over mouse or touch screen, is usually quite different than the real thing in writing. Signatures and their existence are one of many reasons things like back cheques are insecure and can be faked -- If we used something else like fingerprints via special ink types and whatnot, we&amp;#39;d probably be much better off - Plus, fingerprints are already stored by the police and whatnot, and are much harder to fake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 1: To anyone saying that &amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s used so technically it isn&amp;#39;t useless&amp;quot;, I&amp;#39;m aware of that and me mentioning it being useless is more of a juxtoposition of it not being useFUL because it&amp;#39;s ineffective. Something useless can be defined as something not used OR something &amp;quot;not fulfilling or not expected to achieve the intended purpose or desired outcome&amp;quot; which is the meaning I intend here.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 2: Someone actually disagreeing with this point brought up some very pertinent information:&lt;br/&gt;
Apparently, &amp;quot;experts can correctly identify 95% of &amp;#39;real&amp;#39; signatures, and correctly reject 71% of forgeries&amp;quot;. This is proof of how ineffective signatures are at identifying who wrote them! 30% failure rate is ABYSMAL! And that&amp;#39;s by experts, wow. One could only wonder what it would be like among people who have no training, or have minimal training - They&amp;#39;d probably have a failure rate of well over 60%, because signatures empart NO information that varifies who wrote them&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：消除性别薪酬差距的最佳方式是促进陪产假]]></title><description><![CDATA[在这之前，我应该先说我完全没有经济学背景。I
我不是通过研究得出的观点，而只是通过
通过思考得出的。我发这个帖子的原因是希望能听到
希望听到那些比我更了解这些东西的人的意见。我是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r55cz4/cmv_the_best_way_to_combat_the_gender_pay_gap_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r55cz4/cmv_the_best_way_to_combat_the_gender_pay_gap_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:12:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I should preface this by saying I have absolutely no background in economics. I haven&amp;#39;t arrived at the view I&amp;#39;m about to outline through research, but simply through thinking about it. The reason I&amp;#39;m making this post is to hopefully hear from people who have a better grasp on this stuff than me. I&amp;#39;m here for a productive and insightful discussion, not a debate. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, my understanding of the gender pay gap is that there&amp;#39;s a fairly significant ( ≈21% in the US) disparity in how much men and women are paid that can mostly be chalked up to differing career choices, levels of education and time taken off work for pregnancy and childcare. I think this is an objective fact pretty much everyone can get on board with. The divisive bit comes in once you account for the factors I mentioned above and are still left with a meaningful disparity (≈5% in the US). Feminists tend to say this remaining disparity is a result of pure misogyny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m of the opinion that the entire pay gap is a problem, but especially the adjusted bit. That&amp;#39;s because even though the majority of the disparity probably isn&amp;#39;t the result of employers explicitly choosing to pay men more than women, it&amp;#39;s still the result of patriarchal cultural factors, such as parents encouraging their sons to go to college but not their daughters. Also, I wonder how much of the &amp;quot;different career choices&amp;quot; can be attributed to women leaving competitive, high-earning fields of work due to harassment in the workplace. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I have a feeling that an awful lot of those patriarchal cultural factors I alluded to stem from the fact that women generally need to take time off work as a result of childrearing and men don&amp;#39;t. That&amp;#39;s why I think the best thing we can do to meaningfully lower the gender pay gap is to promote paternity leave, both through cultural and legislative means. Ideally, I think every single person on earth should be entitled to at least 12 paid weeks off work upon childbirth or adoption. I realise many first world countries don&amp;#39;t even guarantee paid maternity leave yet though, so I&amp;#39;m willing to set the net a little lower for a start. I&amp;#39;m not going to specify exactly what changes I want to be made because that would vary wildly from country to country, so I&amp;#39;ll let you just go after my logic here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this would greatly improve the pay gap situation (both the unadjusted and adjusted portions) as well as lead to societal improvements in other areas. For instance, I think it could lead to a decrease in men abandoning their children. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the record, I don&amp;#39;t mind maternity leave still being slightly longer than paternity leave, at least in cases that don&amp;#39;t involve adoption or surrogacy, considering pregnancy and breastfeeding are a thing. But I do think the aforementioned minimum 12 paid weeks for either parent would be a good thing to aim for in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: I haven&amp;#39;t abandoned the thread. I&amp;#39;ll be back in about an hour and continue replying to comments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 如果你发现自己不是孩子的父亲，支付孩子的抚养费是不公平的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[前段时间，我的一个朋友通过DNA测试发现，他的儿子和女儿都不是他的父亲。
他的儿子和女儿。这两个孩子都比较年轻。

他申请了离婚，并获得了离婚，但从那时起，他必须支付儿童抚养费
这是他一半以上的工资。此外，他还有租金和账单...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r4xge3/cmv_paying_child_support_if_you_find_out_that_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r4xge3/cmv_paying_child_support_if_you_find_out_that_you/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 16:50:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some  time ago, a friend of mine found out through DNA test is not the father  of either his son and daugther. Both of them are relatively young.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He  filed for divorce and obtained it, but since then he has to pay child  support which comes out as more than half his paycheck. Plus he has rent  and bills to pay. He challenged it in a court of law but ended up  losing the legal battle due to a number of circumstances. Long story  short, it was determined that he is the best candidate to provide the  kids a confortable upbringing and that he was not allowed to conduct a  DNA test on his child without the consent of the mother as well (and was  fined for that).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has made it clear that he does not want ties to his previous family and has changed city and job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I  find it unfair towards him and other people in his same situation. In  this case, the real father should step up and take responsibilities for  what he has done instead of being able to walk out free. Furthermore,  the mother should also be liable of some sort of fraud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of  course, the wellness of the children matters. But this is way we pay  taxes. is it not? So that the state could support the less fortunate of  us and give them a fighting chance? Why should anyone be paying more to  contribute to the upbringing of children that are not his? What do they  have that is so special in respect to some other random orphan kid who  will do years in an temporary accomodation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let  us allocate more of our budget towards creating a safety net for this  unlucky kids instead of torturing a poor guy to a life of 1€ meals,  shared accomodation and no savings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT the reduction of his check is not just because of child support but also because he needed to pay all the expenses in his court case and also he has to pay his now ex wife monthly until she marries again. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：宇宙中的其他地方是否存在智能生命，这绝不是显而易见的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在这篇文章中，我将把智能生命定义为一个有机体
具有与我们自身相当或更高的精神能力。

我觉得这是一个相当普遍的信念，尤其是在相对年轻的人中间。
我觉得这是一个相当普遍的信念，特别是在相对年轻的人中间，不仅可能有一些智能生命存在，而且...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r4ouc3/cmv_it_is_by_no_means_obvious_that_intelligent/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r4ouc3/cmv_it_is_by_no_means_obvious_that_intelligent/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 13:32:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the purpose of this post I will be defining intelligent life as an organism with comparable or superior mental capabilities to our own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel like it&amp;#39;s a fairly commonly held belief especially among relatively young people that not only is there probably some intelligent life out there, but that there is certainly tons of it. While I think it is certainly possible and even likely given the vastness of the universe, the idea that it is clear that numerous super advanced extraterrestrial civilizations exist is unconvincing to me. My view primarly hinges on dissecting the Drake Equation, which I feel is one of the main arguments coming from people with this belief:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those that don&amp;#39;t know, the Drake equation is a model designed to predict the number of civilizations with which humans could communicate (i.e the number of alien worlds with technology similar or more advanced than ours in our galaxy alone). The equation asserts that this number is the product of mean rate of star formation, fraction of stars w/ planets, mean # of planets that could support life per star w/ planets, fraction of habitable planets that have life, fraction of planets w/ life that develop intelligent life, fraction of planets w/ intelligent life that develop communication, and mean length of time that civilizations can communicate. I actually am mostly ok with the model itself. I think that if the correct values were used, this model might be able to predict the proper number of advanced civilizations within a couple orders of magnitude. However, the values traditionally used for these parameters render a completely psuedo-scientific result. The following values are those which were orginally estimated by Drake himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mean rate of star formation&lt;/strong&gt;- Set by Drake as 1 per year, I&amp;#39;m no astronomer but this is something we apparently have sufficient evidence for and is regarded as a conservative estimate. This value is totally fine by me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fraction of stars with planets&lt;/strong&gt;- Estimated to be between 0.2 and 0.5. Also something we have evidence for, fine by me. I actually thought this number was considered to be even higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Planets that could support life per star with planets&lt;/strong&gt;- Estimated to be between 1 and 5. This is completely baseless. Given that we have never been able to successfully recreate abiogenesis, and we only really have evidence that it has ever taken place once on Earth, I do not see a compelling reason to believe that the true value is greater than something like 10^-9. There is really nothing to suggest that life is nearly as common as this estimate asserts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fraction of these planets that will develop life&lt;/strong&gt;- Estimated as 100%. I guess the idea is that over billions of years, anything that could happen will almost certainly happen. However, this doesn&amp;#39;t take into account the fact that the ability to support life and the ability to start life are entirely different. For example, a major hypothesis about abiogenesis is that it arose from lightning. It is entirely possible if not likely that a given planet with the elemental building blocks of life and proper temperature range would not have the required forces to precipitate abiogenesis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fraction of planets with life that will develop intelligent life&lt;/strong&gt;- This is the one I have the biggest problem with, as it is also set as 100%. This presupposes that there is something inevitable about intelligent life, something intrinsic to the process of natural selection that moves species towards intelligence over many generations. However there is really no evidence for this and it even goes against modern ideas of how evolution works. One of the last lines of Darwin&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;On the Origin of Species&amp;quot; asserts that &amp;quot;all corporeal and mental endowments will tend to progress towards perfection&amp;quot;. But we know now that this is not the case. Organisms adapt to the conditions of their surroundings, and more often than not intelligence is not an adaptive trait as it is costly in terms of energy and does not benefit a species that cannot utilize it. Primates, given the structure of their body, were in a unique position to benefit from intelligence as they were capable of physically manipulating their environment. It even appears to be the case that multicellular life arising from single cell life is quite rare, as we only have observed it successfully occuring once on our planet. So many specific selective pressures had to be enforced to give the Homo genus their paramount intelligence that this number is likely far closer to 0% than it is to 100%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fraction of planets with intelligent life that will develop sufficient communication systems&lt;/strong&gt;- At 10 to 20%, this estimate is less egregious than the others but I would still argue it is too high. Again, there is nothing inherent or inevitable about the factors that lead to advanced technology. There is no reason to believe that intelligent beings necessarily organize themselves in such a way that such technological advancement is possible or desirable. Hunter-gatherer cultures for example do not tend towards industrialization or even the type of labor specialization required to create advanced technology. Additionally, even if a planet has intelligent life, why does this mean it must also have the requisite resources for communication systems. Such technology requires enormous amounts of energy. The industrialization that took place on our own planet was only possible due to the Carboniferous as well as the presence of large quantities of heavy metals such as iron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Years that such civilizations will be able to communicate&lt;/strong&gt;- Estimated to be between 1000 and 100,000,000 years. The lower bound is plausible enough though the upper bound feels ludicrously high. There is no evidence of how long such a civilization will last. However, I don&amp;#39;t have a well backed argument for a much lower value so I will accept &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given these numbers, we find that Drake predicted between 20 and 50,000,000 civilizations in the Milky Way with which humans could communicate. People use this result as evidence or advanced extraterrestrial life but as I believe I have demonstrated, the values used render this estimate far too high. If we use my values rather than Drake&amp;#39;s, we would estimate less than once advanced civilization in the Milky Way, thus indicating that it is by no means obvious that intelligent life is widely or even somewhat present outside of Earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want my view changed as there appear to be plenty of intelligent, well credentialed people who believe that many, many advanced civilizations exist. I have never really encountered someone who agrees with me on this so I feel that I must be missing something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：过渡性幼儿园和幼儿园（4-5岁）的孩子太小了，不能把家庭作业发回家并进行评分。]]></title><description><![CDATA[T-K（过渡性幼儿园）的学生，我想说的是幼儿园也是如此。
以及我想说的是，幼儿园，可能包括大部分小学低年级的学生，都不应该接受家庭作业，尤其是有等级的家庭作业。
幼儿园的学生，以及我认为幼儿园的学生，可能还有大部分小学低年级的学生，都不应该接受家庭作业，特别是有分数的家庭作业。

到昨天为止，我的儿子已经5岁了，但他一直在一个过渡性幼儿园就读。
幼儿园项目，在...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r4t3e8/cmv_transitional_kindergarten_and_kindergarten_45/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r4t3e8/cmv_transitional_kindergarten_and_kindergarten_45/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 12:37:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;T-K (transitional Kindergarten) students, and I would argue kindergarten as well, probably through most of early elementary, should not receive homework at all, especially graded homework. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My son is 5 years old, as of yesterday, but he’s been enrolled in a transitional kindergarten program at the local elementary school as he was too young at the beginning of the school year to enroll in kindergarten. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the age of 4, and now 5, as presumably it won’t change, he gets daily homework, and weekend homework, and he got a rather large homework packet for the thanksgiving break as well. This all comes back graded. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, none of this homework is hard, but this is all relative as well, and he doesn’t understand the concept of grading either, but all the parents do. The homework consists of about 90 minutes worth of work for a 4-5 year old (assuming they can concentrate straight through, this is highly unlikely in my experience).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until a few weeks ago his school didn’t have a TK teacher and he was just put into a kindergarten class along with all the other TK students. They’re still short a TK teacher, and this thanksgiving homework packet was labeled “kindergarten” and had activities that frankly we had to just, well, do for him because they were way beyond him. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit: I just got done dropping off my son at school (8:15AM EST) and his teacher said that the thanksgiving packet that was sent home was a mistake made by a substitute teacher and none of the children should have been expected to complete it. It was far too advanced for TK level, he actually did most of it fairly well.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So perhaps this is just laziness and not the norm. After all I don’t have a plethora of kids in different schools. The packet took about 2 hours per day over 1 week. It would have taken longer if I hadn’t given up trying to teach him things that were way over his head that he hasn’t even begun learning in class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I think this is ridiculous for this age group. CMV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美国政府应预填所有税表]]></title><description><![CDATA[我曾是一名志愿报税员，亲眼目睹了官僚主义的细枝末节是如何压倒一些人的。
琐事会让一些人（尤其是低收入的人）不知所措，并导致他们在填写错误的税单时产生滞纳金和其他罚款。
当他们错误地填写了他们的税单时，会导致滞纳金和其他罚款。我不
我不确定有什么好的理由让每个人都自己做......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r4f7ps/cmv_the_us_government_should_prefill_all_tax_forms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r4f7ps/cmv_the_us_government_should_prefill_all_tax_forms/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 04:49:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been a volunteer tax preparer and seen firsthand how the bureaucratic minutia can overwhelm some people (especially low-income folks) and lead to late fees and other penalties when they fill out their taxes incorrectly. I&amp;#39;m not sure what good reason there is to make everyone do it themselves (or pay someone else to help) from scratch, especially for those living on social security or disability payments. I believe the current practice puts an undue burden on all citizens, most of all those who can least afford to spend time or money sorting through their own financial situation in order to accurately file taxes every year. Can anyone offer a compelling reason we should keep doing things the way we are now?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我们应该停止使用 "拉美人 "一词]]></title><description><![CDATA[我承认要改变我的观点是非常困难的，因为我在这方面的感觉非常强烈。
但我愿意重新考虑我的观点。

 1. 这个词在西班牙语中完全不能按人们的意图发音。
    1.这个词在西班牙语中完全不能以人们想要的方式发音。如果这个词所针对的人不能
    甚至...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r454ng/cmv_we_should_stop_using_the_term_latinx/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r454ng/cmv_we_should_stop_using_the_term_latinx/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 15:39:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I admit it will be very difficult to change my view as I feel very strongly on this but I am open to reconsidering my view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term is completely unpronounceable in Spanish the way that people intend for it to be pronounced. If the people for whom the word is intended cannot even pronounce it, then it is not an effective solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Latino” is gender neutral in Spanish already but if that is unacceptable because of its masculine inclination for some people then there are other alternatives that are easier to pronounce such as “Latine” and “Latin.” In Spanish, it is understood that “Latino” is gender neutral and it does not have the sexist connotation that English-speakers assume it does. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term is largely pushed by progressive white Americans against the will of the Latino community in the US. Only 3% of Latinos in the US identify with the term according to the Pew Research Center, the vast majority have not even heard of it, and amongst those who have their view of it is overwhelmingly negative. They see it as a white Western attempt to disrespect the rules of the Spanish language for politicized means, which is linguistic imperialism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the number of people who actually use the term being so small, it should not be used as the default for all Latinos unlike what corporations and politicians in the US are doing. If you know someone identifies as a woman or a man just call them Latino or Latina. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We often say people are the authors of their own experience and this is a central tenet of progressivism especially for the marginalized. So why are people NOT listening to the majority of Latinos who do not want to be called Latinx? It screams “we know what is better for you than you know for yourself so sit back and shut up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：面具任务是必要的，因为人们有点愚蠢，而且没有很好的理由反对它们。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为了了解情况，我住在苏格兰，那里确实有来自政府的面具授权。
最近我去了英国，那里没有（我想他们可能从昨天开始就有了，因为霸天虎的变种或其他什么，但他们没有。
我想他们可能从昨天开始，因为霸天虎的变种或什么，但他们没有
但在我一个多月前旅行的时候，他们没有）。在苏格兰，95%的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r40wos/cmv_mask_mandates_are_necessary_as_people_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r40wos/cmv_mask_mandates_are_necessary_as_people_are/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 13:30:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For context, I live in Scotland, which does have mask mandates from the government, and recently traveled to England, which does not (I think they might have starting yesterday because of the decepticon varient or whatever, but they didn&amp;#39;t when I travelled a month or so ago). In Scotland, 95% of people on public transport and in shops wear masks. In England, about 2% seem to. The point of bringing this up, is to make the point that if we want people to wear masks, we do basically need to tell them they have to, as most people are too stupid to do it without the government telling them to. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the mask mandates themselves, I have never heard a good argument against them. I often hear people say things like &amp;quot;oh so should we have mask mandates for the flu then&amp;quot;, I don&amp;#39;t see how this is a counter. I would be happy to wear a mask for a few months in winter when the flu is most prominent, and if there is a particularly bad flu strain, then telling people to wear masks seems justifiable even if only to reduce money spent in healthcare, not to mention that hospitals often get overwhelmed in winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other arguments I hear are &amp;quot;muh government telling us to do things bad&amp;quot;, to which the obvious response is seatbelts and not being allows to drunk drive, both of which are things that have small chances to negatively affect other people or you, which you can&amp;#39;t do. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are medical exceptions, which I do think should be allowed, although maybe with a slightly higher burden of proof than we have now. And I&amp;#39;ve heard good argument for why kids shouldn&amp;#39;t wear them, although those argument are stuff like &amp;quot;they need to be able to see each others faces to develop emotional intelligence&amp;quot;, not &amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s child abuse&amp;quot; or some stupid shit like that. I think teenagers should have to wear them too though, this would only apply to young kids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：想和某人浪漫地在一起，而不想成为他们的朋友，这是完全正常的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到的这些帖子很有趣，比如。"我告诉一个人我不会和他约会，现在他不和我说话了？
就不跟我说话了吗？"

这是一个如此奇怪的观点。我有朋友是因为我们有特定的
兴趣爱好，或者从小就认识。浪漫的关系是
是另一回事。我有女人说她们...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r3myrg/cmv_its_totally_normal_to_want_to_be_with_someone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r3myrg/cmv_its_totally_normal_to_want_to_be_with_someone/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 10:42:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s funny these posts I see like. &amp;quot;I told a guy I wouldn&amp;#39;t date him and now he won&amp;#39;t talk to me??&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s such a strange perspective. I have friends because we share specific hobbies or have known each other since we were kids. Romantic relationships are a different thing. I&amp;#39;ve had women say they just want to be friends and I just politely said &amp;quot;that&amp;#39;s ok I&amp;#39;m just looking for a romantic partner right now.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;#39;s weird that people feel that friendship is the foundation and you build romance on top of that. Of course I&amp;#39;m friends with my wife, but if we weren&amp;#39;t together then I probably wouldn&amp;#39;t be. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider this: if you have a young child, would you spend time with them if they weren&amp;#39;t your child? I&amp;#39;m not saying you wouldn&amp;#39;t enjoy spending time with kids if they aren&amp;#39;t yours, but would you specifically set up time to hang out them? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have friends the same age as your parents? Or do you only have that relationship with them &lt;em&gt;because&lt;/em&gt; they are your parents? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s not an insult to not be friends with someone. I&amp;#39;m not friends with a lot of people I would probably enjoy spending time with. The reality is I just have a few spaces in my life for important people. I wouldn&amp;#39;t go around treating kids like my own child just like I wouldn&amp;#39;t go around talking about my feelings with women who aren&amp;#39;t my wife. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not saying men and women can&amp;#39;t be friends. That&amp;#39;s not the claim. I&amp;#39;m saying friends and other catagories aren&amp;#39;t the same. I don&amp;#39;t look for the same thing from friends that I do from a parent or a spouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now obviously, there&amp;#39;s nothing wrong with seeing someone as just a friend. But you can&amp;#39;t decide they have to see you the same way and not leave when they find out you don&amp;#39;t like them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I&amp;#39;m interested in someone sexually and they aren&amp;#39;t into me. I don&amp;#39;t want to see them anymore. I&amp;#39;m not angry about it, but if someone specifically tells me I&amp;#39;m not what they want, why would I want to spend time with them? If we were already friends for a while sure, but if it&amp;#39;s always been a romantic potential for me then no romance = I&amp;#39;m out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We only have so much time for each person in our lives. As well as work and self care, meditation, hobbies, etc. If you don&amp;#39;t want to be in the one catagory I&amp;#39;m hiring for, then there&amp;#39;s no open positions at this time. And honestly it should go vice versa. Why you would want to be friends with someone who wants to date you is beyond me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV："特权 "一词是有毒的，不利于减少歧视]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，我必须先声明，虽然我确实面临着基于我的性取向和一般外貌的欺凌/骚扰。
我的性取向、体型和一般的外貌，但我从来没有面临过
种族歧视。所以我只对我要谈的事情有部分经验
谈论的事情。

我还想说，我完全承认...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r3sjsb/cmv_the_term_privilege_is_toxic_and_not_conducive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r3sjsb/cmv_the_term_privilege_is_toxic_and_not_conducive/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 07:30:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Firstly I have to preface that although i did face bullying/harassment based on my sexual orientation, size and general physical appearance, I&amp;#39;ve never faced racial discrimination. So i only have a partial experience of the things I&amp;#39;ll be talking about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also wanna say that i entirely acknowledge the fact that some people have a harder life than others due to societal factors; It&amp;#39;s obvious to me that being white, cisgender, straight and born in a developped country makes one a lot less susceptible to being discriminated against than being black, gay and transgender in a developing country. I certainly don&amp;#39;t intend to invalidate the experience of anyone who has been discriminated against- I also readily accept that compared to a lot of people I&amp;#39;ve lived a very privileged life myself. And i also readily accept that there is a lot more nuance to the subject than (for exemple) being trans or cis, and that discrimination affects people differently based on a variety of factors (for instance the ability to &amp;quot;pass&amp;quot; or the like). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However I simply don&amp;#39;t understand why so much of the debate in LGBT+ communities or racial minorities consists of &amp;quot;is X a privilege or not?&amp;quot;. Or rather, it&amp;#39;s mostly &amp;quot;X is a privilege! We need to acknowledge it as such&amp;quot;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason I think that the term &amp;quot;privilege&amp;quot; is problematic is two-fold: first of all, being treated normally shouldn&amp;#39;t be considered a privilege. It makes it sound like basic human decency is something special that some people receive unfairly, when it&amp;#39;s really the opposite (meaning it&amp;#39;s the fact that some people are discriminated against that should be considered abnormal and unfair). Secondly, instead of making people concentrate on the issue at hand (typically racism or homophobia), it makes them concentrate on &amp;quot;exposing&amp;quot; the people that have it better. Which will typically provoke one of 2 reactions from the side characterized as &amp;quot;privileged&amp;quot;: either they will feel guilty for being white/straight, or they will think that the characterization is injust because they also struggle in life and deny being privileged. In either cases this doesn&amp;#39;t help at all the people being discriminated against! The only thing it does is alienating potential allies that feel like they are being guilt-tripped for no reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you will say &amp;quot;yes but the fact that some people have an advantage should be acknowledged by society&amp;quot; well yes, of course. But anyone who is smart enough to be worth disussing with already realizes that being white/straight/cis/male is advantageous. And if they don&amp;#39;t, saying &amp;quot;check your privileges&amp;quot; certainly won&amp;#39;t change that, quite the opposite. Maybe this just comes down to my personal experience, but in my case almost every single person that has ever physically harassed or bullied/insulted me in my adult life belonged to a very specific group (male, religious, low education). These are people that are also discriminated against for other reasons, and having a meaningful discussion with them isn&amp;#39;t even in the realm of possibility. What needs to be done is have better education, i really don&amp;#39;t see how accusing people of being &amp;quot;privileged&amp;quot; achieves anything as far as actual racism/homophobia is concerned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To put it bluntly it seems to me that the reason this is a thing is that instead of working towards making an actual change, a lot of people nowadays are reveling in their status of &amp;quot;discriminated against&amp;quot; and base their identity around it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：当目的是为了获得清洁时，淋浴比洗澡好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我完全理解有合理的理由去洗一个漂亮的温水澡。如果你是
例如，如果你想放松，或舒缓你的肌肉，那么我明白整个洗澡
的事情。我很确定洗澡对去除皮肤角质也很有好处。
然而，当我们在谈论清洁问题时，我认为...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r3mh61/cmv_showers_are_better_than_baths_when_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r3mh61/cmv_showers_are_better_than_baths_when_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 02:40:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I totally understand there are valid reasons to take a nice warm bath. If you&amp;#39;re looking to relax, or soothe your  muscles for instance, then I get the whole bath thing. I&amp;#39;m pretty sure baths are really good for exfoliating skin as well. However when we are talking about cleanliness I would argue there&amp;#39;s no comparison. Showers evenly distribute water over your body while efficiently mixing with soap to break apart oils, dirt, and sweat that are stuck to your skin. Plus in a bath you&amp;#39;re kind of left to sit in the water that&amp;#39;s now mixed with all the grime that comes off your body, as opposed to the dirty water being sucked down the drain when you&amp;#39;re in the shower. Again, I&amp;#39;m not bashing baths here, just saying when the priority is to get yourself clean, I don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s even close.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：允许在推特上对 "白人 "进行种族主义，只会把木头扔到已经失控的火上。]]></title><description><![CDATA[简单而简短。推特允许各种种族主义，以及针对 "白人 "的种族诱饵，好像完全没有问题。
"白人"，就像它是完全正常的。这一切都造成了一个更深的
分裂

你看到多少条今天仍然存在的关于圣诞游行的推文？
受害者应该得到它。或它是因果报应。

有多少人...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r3g7pc/cmv_allowing_racism_on_twitter_against_whites/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r3g7pc/cmv_allowing_racism_on_twitter_against_whites/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 19:36:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simple and short. Twitter allows all sorts of racism, and race baiting against &amp;quot;whites&amp;quot; like it&amp;#39;s perfectly fine. All this does is creates an even deeper division&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many tweets, that still exist today, did you see about the Christmas parade victims deserving it. Or it being karma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many tweets like this: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TalbertSwan/status/1464016757295915010&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/TalbertSwan/status/1464016757295915010&lt;/a&gt; who are calling out an ENTIRE group of people BY SKIN COLOR and blaming them for tragedies against other ethnic groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you call somebody white, you&amp;#39;re basing it COMPLETELY on their skin color, or appearance. Not on ethnic background, nationality, or ANYTHING else. You are ASSUMING just because the color of their skin, they must be connected to colonization, slavery, and hell maybe even the holocaust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as this kind of behavior is socially, and TOS permitted, we will continue to drift further and further into the void.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change my view...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Here is the rule I am talking about)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/hateful-conduct-policy&quot;&gt;https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/hateful-conduct-policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;We prohibit inciting behavior that targets individuals or groups of people belonging to protected categories&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在流行的话语中，强迫人们用他们的种族而不是他们的族裔来识别，会增加基于种族的集体主义，增加种族主义的程度远远超过提高对特权的认识。]]></title><description><![CDATA[种族主义本质上是一种集体主义的意识形态：来自一个群体的人被教育
认为自己在本质上优于另一群体，基于他们的集体身份和与之相关的积极属性。
群体身份和他们与之相关的积极属性，以牺牲他们认为低劣的另一群体为代价，将自己视为天生的优越者。
牺牲另一个群体的利益，他们认为另一个群体是低等的。白人至上主义...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r3d82x/cmv_forcing_people_to_identify_by_their_race/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r3d82x/cmv_forcing_people_to_identify_by_their_race/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 14:30:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Racism is inherently a collectivist ideology: people from one group are taught to view themselves as inherently superior to another group based on their collective identity and the positive attributes they associate it with at the expense of another group whom they view as inferior. White supremacy is an example of this. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is currently progressive/Leftist tendency to say that we must think of ourselves not as Irish, Polish, Greek, Nigerian, Jamaican, Dominican Americans but as “white” and “Black” first, and essentially view ourselves as homogenous groups whose differences aren’t relevant because those differences have no bearing on the experience of privilege or oppression within the group. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THIS IS VERY TOXIC especially for white people because the second that collectivism around whiteness becomes commonplace, it is a breeding ground for white supremacy. Forcing unity of identity between groups of people with little in common other than complexion creates collective white identity which has never historically led to anything positive for race relations. It is far better for instance that white people do not view themselves as a cohesive group but as Irish, Polish, Greek, Italian etc who share little more other than skin color. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similarly, grouping all Black people together is also nonsensical because the cultural differences that exist between an Ethiopian, Nigerian, Dominican, African American and Jamaican are very present as are their experiences. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way to end racism and discrimination between groups is to dissolve the sense of group identity along racial lines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: 电子游戏通过转移注意力和/或支持玩家脱离现实生活中的绝境，拯救了数百万人的生命。]]></title><description><![CDATA[电子游戏通过分散玩家的注意力和防止他们吸毒，肯定已经防止了世界上数百万人的死亡和伤害。
通过分散玩家的注意力，防止他们吸毒/自杀/抑郁。
复发/自杀/抑郁，可能是攻击、酗酒、酒后驾车，以及
可能还有数以百计的容易造成死亡或伤害的情况。I...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2yy3g/cmv_video_games_have_saved_millions_of_lives_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2yy3g/cmv_video_games_have_saved_millions_of_lives_by/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 02:40:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Video games have surely prevented death and injury to millions of people in the world by distracting their players and preventing them from drug relapses/suicide/depression, possibly assault, alcoholism, drunk driving, and possibly hundreds more generally-death or injury prone circumstances. 
I believe this argument would be useful in dampening a common baby boomer philosophy against video games, and would ultimately change public opinion of video game culture. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have seen few lives altered negatively from video games, but there are possibly millions that have been saved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：修女的习惯不等同于头巾，比较它们是一个错误的比喻。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如今，进入修会的妇女必须年满18岁，在任何时候离开
任何时候离开都是允许的，即使你已经宣过誓。调解是一个非常现实的问题。
即使如此，完全加入也需要几年时间（我认识一个人，她刚拿到最后的誓言，她是在2007年开始的）。
我认识一个人，她刚拿到最后的誓言，她是在2007年开始的）。有几十种...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2rlkn/cmv_nuns_habits_are_not_equivalent_to_the_hijab/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2rlkn/cmv_nuns_habits_are_not_equivalent_to_the_hijab/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 22:37:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nowadays, women who enter religious orders must be eighteen and leaving at any time is permissible, even if you&amp;#39;ve sworn your vows. Dispensation is a very real thing and even then, fully joining takes years (I know someone who just got her final vows and she started in 2007). There are dozens of women&amp;#39;s orders and many of them don&amp;#39;t even wear the habit or wimple anymore. There is no deep symbolism to the outfit itself - it&amp;#39;s just what women wore back in the Middle Ages; some orders changed the uniform, others did not. I know nuns who wear the full ensemble and I know nuns who wear normal clothes - neither sees the other as being any lesser for their different apparel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hijab is directly mandated by the hadiths (if you are a Quranist, it&amp;#39;s more open to interpretation), which make it clear that women who do not observe it are sinning. The whole modesty thing is a modern excuse - it came along because Umar (2nd Rashidun caliph) was complaining about Sawdah (Muhammad&amp;#39;s wife between Khadija and Aisha) arousing him, and this was the compromise instead of women being under house arrest. The most conservative views say the hijab is much more than a headscarf - even a woman&amp;#39;s voice or something as simple as a handshake are considered part of her nakedness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve never seen any Catholics threatening random women on social media with hellfire for not wearing a mantilla, but i&amp;#39;ve seen lots of victim blaming with Muslim women who aren&amp;#39;t dong it &amp;quot;properly.&amp;quot; I&amp;#39;m sure there are Muslim women who wear it of their own volition, but at the same time, I am sure there are plenty who don&amp;#39;t and aren&amp;#39;t saying anything because of social/religious pressure. Lastly, you cannot tell me that small children who wear the hijab are giving their consent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: A nun&amp;#39;s habit isn&amp;#39;t so much a religious garb as it is a uniform for a career choice. The hijab is very much connected with a subconscious desire to censor women and sexualize them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：盲目拥抱的趋势（和其他）并不健康，也不是为了心理健康。]]></title><description><![CDATA[想象一下，你走在街上，看到有人举着一个牌子，上面写着 "如果你今天心情不好，你可以拥抱我"。
如果你今天心情不好，你可以抱抱我"。你拥抱了这个人，也许和他们谈了谈
谈论你的烦恼，然后继续你的一天。

但是他们阻止你说："嘿，这其实是一个社会实验。可以
我可以利用你...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2tdvu/cmv_the_blind_hug_trend_and_others_arent/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2tdvu/cmv_the_blind_hug_trend_and_others_arent/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 22:37:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine you’re walking down the street and see someone with a sign that says “If you’re having a bad day, you can hug me”. You hug the person, maybe talk to them about your troubles and go on about your day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Except then they stop you and say “hey this is actually a social experiment. Can I use you in my YouTube video”? Or even worse days or months later someone shows you a viral video you’re in where you’re hugging someone and venting frustrations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example: &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/Gf2ao3_kyTk&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/Gf2ao3_kyTk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The comments are always this is so wholesome, we need more people like you, etc. But when we bring it to reality and consider this was all set up it becomes a lot less wholesome and a lot more deceptive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These people are coming up to a stranger putting themselves in a vulnerable position. For some of these people I’ve seen in videos it’s a major release. There’s an inherent sense of trust in that situation. That trust is then broken when you figure out there’s a creep in the trees shooting everything. Do we really believe this guy would be out there doing this if it weren’t for a camera?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Videos like this do more damage than good because it makes caring about mental health a trend. In order to make it worth your while you have to take a picture or make a video so you can get your internet points. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not so wholesome or helpful if you ask me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：一般来说，加密货币是一个美化的赌博系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[现在听我说完。我真的非常缺乏关于这个问题的适当教育
但我从许多人那里听到了他们对这个概念的反对意见，同时也
同时听到朋友们说这是 "快速致富 "的计划，我觉得这听起来不像是真的。
这听起来好得不象是真的。现在我真的想成为一个有知识的人。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2kckj/cmv_crypto_in_general_is_a_glorified_gambling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2kckj/cmv_crypto_in_general_is_a_glorified_gambling/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:34:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now hear me out before.
I really REALLY lack and proper education on the subject but I’ve heard from many their disapproval to the concept and at the same time heard friends speaking of it as ”get rich quick” schemes, which imo sounds to good to be true.
Now I really want to become knowledgeable on the subject so I’d figure this subreddit is a good place to do so.
To clear up, I don’t believe it involves any proper tactics and it’s system is way too risk-based. I dont believe it can be regarded as a get rich quick scheme as MANY teenagers of equal age to me seem to believe, my dad is where I developed this opinion from and its root is based on that it’s too good to be true, at least according to getting rich quick concept. You always see stories on people succeeding but never on ones losing, because in theory, more people need to lose for someone to become relatively rich.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：医生完全有理由根据病人情况要求进行检查]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我读了这位来自南非的黑人妇女的证词后，我开始思考这个问题。
南非的黑人妇女的证词后，我开始思考这个问题。她搬到另一个国家，去看医生。虽然这个女人没有表现出任何相关的症状
她没有表现出任何相关的症状，但医生要求她做一个HIV测试。
"因为她是来自非洲"。病人认为这是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2l172/cmvdoctors_are_totally_justified_to_request_exams/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2l172/cmvdoctors_are_totally_justified_to_request_exams/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 16:38:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It got me thinking about it after I read the testimony of this black woman from South Africa. She moved to another country and went to the doctor. Although the woman didn&amp;#39;t show any related symptoms, the doctor requested her do an HIV test &amp;quot;because she is from Africa&amp;quot;. The patient sees this as racism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did some research and found that in South Africa 20% of the adult population has HIV. And a large share of them does not even know they are HIV positive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Medical authorities from all over the world recommend practitioners to HIV test patients that have some non-negligible risk of having HIV, however small that risk is. That includes victims of rape, people who have unprotected casual sex, sex workers, gay men, among other groups considered at risk. Even among these groups, rates of undetected HIV are below what is seen in South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just to be clear, I believe it is the doctor&amp;#39;s duty to explain in a clear and respectful way why they are requesting an HIV exam, to make it as safe and confortable an experience as possible to the patient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I got banned from a subreddit for pointing out that requesting an HIV test from a patient from south africa is not necessarily racist. It is good practice, with few exceptions. I believe what made this woman feel uncomfortable about the HIV test is her own prejudice against HIV patients and ignorance of the statistics. HIV testing is quick, simple, and nothing to be offended by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my point is: the doctor must be respectful and offer information, but patients should be submitted to simple exams if they are part of certain demographics according to statistical data, and they are wrong to claim that is racism/discrimination/etc&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：打砸抢是很危险的，不应该以 "一个价值几十亿的公司损失了几千块 "来搪塞。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这种态度在微博上尤其普遍。"诺德斯特姆是一家价值数十亿美元的公司
价值数十亿美元的公司，谁会在乎他们失去价值几千美元的库存呢？
谁会在乎他们损失了价值几千美元的库存，他们可以直接更换。" 按照人们的说法，那些
反对打砸抢的人是有问题的，因为他们并没有说...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r26rmb/cmv_smash_and_grabs_are_dangerous_and_should_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r26rmb/cmv_smash_and_grabs_are_dangerous_and_should_not/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 04:42:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This attitude is especially prevalent on twitter: &amp;quot;Nordstrom is a multi-billion dollar company, who cares if they lose a few thousand dollars worth of inventory, they can just replace it.&amp;quot; The way people frame it, the people who are against smash and grabs are the problem because they aren&amp;#39;t talking about wage theft-a separate issue-and because they care too much about property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I would argue that there&amp;#39;s a difference between petty shoplifting (snatching toothpaste from CVS) and mobs armed with sledgehammers destroying property. For employees, it&amp;#39;s distressing to see armed mobs destroying their workplace, especially because they don&amp;#39;t know that the armed mob won&amp;#39;t hurt them. And people have gotten hurt before during these smash and grabs. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the executives and CEOs of these major companies are far away from the crimes being committed, so if this is supposed to be retaliation against them for mistreating employees (or if people think what is happening is OK because of past wrongdoing, it&amp;#39;s very misguided seeing as employees are the ones getting hurt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t understand why so many people are jumping to the defense of the criminals vandalizing stores, so maybe I can find out how somebody who is defending them views the situation and, possibly, change my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: "真正的共产主义从未被尝试过 "是一个与事实不符的、令人难以置信的虚伪的论点]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 1. 1.真正的共产主义可能从未实现过，但它肯定被尝试过。
    的尝试，而忽视这一点则是忽视了真正的人对社会主义的理论和实践所作出的真实而具体的贡献。
    真正的人对社会主义的理论和实践做出了真实而具体的贡献。毛泽东、列宁、卡斯特罗和
    斯大林都广泛地阅读和撰写了马克思主义。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2bcqc/cmv_real_communism_has_never_been_tried_is_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r2bcqc/cmv_real_communism_has_never_been_tried_is_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 03:37:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real communism may have not ever been achieved, but it has certainly been &lt;em&gt;attempted&lt;/em&gt;, and to ignore that ignores the real and tangible contributions of real people to the theory and practice of socialism. Mao, Lenin, Castro and Stalin all read and wrote extensively about Marxist theory and made many justifications on how their policies would bring their respective countries closer to the ideal of Marx. If you would want to establish real communism, you have to see how past people did it and what they got right and wrong. And it&amp;#39;s not as if they were all charlatans either who only cared about money or big mansions - that kind of thinking leads to small men who get overthrown easily. A lot of these people genuinely bought into their own bullshit and believed that communism would be achieved within their lifetimes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&amp;#39;s a self-fulfilling redundancy where you essentially define your ideology as being perfect, and any attempt to do it where it goes wrong can be easily disavowed because if it were truly attempted, it would obviously succeed. Communism may be an ideal, but it is also inherently flawed because of the means available to us to achieve that ideal in the first place, no?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：只要存在处决无辜者的风险，死刑就不应该存在于社会中。]]></title><description><![CDATA[一段时间以来，我一直支持死刑，但我现在意识到
处决无辜者的论点是高于一切的。

只要存在处决无辜者的风险，死刑就不应该存在。
就不应该存在于社会中。

据估计，至少有4%的死囚是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r27gug/cmv_as_long_as_there_is_a_risk_of_executing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r27gug/cmv_as_long_as_there_is_a_risk_of_executing/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:58:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a while I have supported the death penalty, but I now realise that the argument of executing innocent people is above all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as there is a risk of executing innocent people, the death penalty should not exist in society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is estimated that at least 4% of people on death row are innocent. There is no way to justify killing innocent people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rate of innocent people will never be non zero, and, coupled with other reasons such as the fact it is more expensive than life in prison, to have the DP in society is inappropriate; no one should be at the risk of death due to a flawed system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在过去24小时内，许多主要媒体没有对沃克沙杀人事件进行实质性的报道，这说明了这些媒体的偏见到底有多大]]></title><description><![CDATA[当我用谷歌搜索 "Darrell Brooks "并查看过去24小时的新闻时，只有
只有福克斯新闻和《纽约邮报》等主要媒体有关于此事的报道。CNN。
MSNBC，NBC，ABC，华盛顿邮报，纽约时报都没有。也有
一些当地的小媒体也在报道此事。

这应该...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r20cye/cmv_the_lack_of_substantial_reporting_from_many/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r20cye/cmv_the_lack_of_substantial_reporting_from_many/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:58:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I google &amp;quot;Darrell Brooks&amp;quot; and look at news in the past 24 hours, the only major outlets having any stories about this are Fox News and New York Post.  CNN, MSNBC, NBC, ABC, Washington Post, New York Times are all missing.  There are also some local smaller outlets reporting on this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This should really wake people up about what these media outlets are all about.  When the Kyle Rittenhouse shootings happened, all of the media outlets I named were reporting on those shootings non-stop for weeks.  There were many stories published as well as many opinion pieces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it&amp;#39;s eerily quiet about an event that even objectively, just based on the number of victims is much bigger (6 killed and dozens wounded vs 2 killed and 1  wounded).  Not to mention that in this case the dead and injured include kids and women.  Also not even mentioning that this did not happen during a riot/protest, but was done at a peaceful parade.  Also done by a man with a violent criminal record who was out on bail at the time of the incident compared to Kyle with no criminal record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I look at the MSNBC Daily today, 2 out of the first eleven stories they have are about Rittenhouse (they are still talking about Rittenhouse), there is stuff about white supremacy, trans deaths.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main story seems to be about Arbery and there is something about Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is nothing that even mentions Darrell Brooks or Waukesha.  CNN is similar, there is nothing on their main news pages about this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is clearly evidence of media bias because this IS a big story, one that is objectively bigger that the Rittenhouse story at the time it happened (based on number and age of victims alone) and yet there is a lack of coverage of this case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 那些喜欢看到罪犯通过受伤、被打倒或被杀死而 "得到他们应得的 "的人，只是在寻找借口享受人们的痛苦。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我从不喜欢看到有人受伤或被杀，无论他们是多么 "坏 "的人。
即使他们是真正的希特勒。

在reddit上，我经常看到关于私刑暴力的帖子，或者说，例如
例如，自行车在无人看管的情况下被困住，导致小偷受伤，而人们在
在...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r1uupq/cmv_people_that_enjoy_seeing_criminals_getting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r1uupq/cmv_people_that_enjoy_seeing_criminals_getting/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 13:37:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll never enjoy seeing someone getting hurt or killed no matter how &amp;quot;bad&amp;quot; of a person they are. even if they were literally Hitler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It happens often on reddit that I see posts about vigilante violence, or for example bikes being left unsupervised and trapped to hurt the thief, and people in the comment section are all getting very excited about seeing a &amp;quot;bad person&amp;quot; getting hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is my opinion that they actually just enjoy seeing people suffering, and they need an excuse for it. It happening to a &amp;quot;bad person&amp;quot; enable it being &amp;quot;fine&amp;quot; instead of completely horrible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 我一直讨厌工作，并将永远讨厌工作。我只是需要储蓄和退休。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我（41岁）从15岁起就开始工作，讨厌其中的每一分钟。工作只是占用了
工作只是占用了我想做的事情，说实话，它让我感到沮丧和愤怒。
说实话，它让我感到沮丧和愤怒，以至于即使在休息时间，我也经常不做我想做的事情。
因为我很生气，因为我不得不工作，而且害怕......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r1ofg3/cmv_ive_always_hated_work_and_will_always_hate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r1ofg3/cmv_ive_always_hated_work_and_will_always_hate/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 08:30:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I (41F) have worked since I was 15 and hated every minute of it. Work just takes away from stuff I would rather be doing and honestly it depresses me and angers me so much that even during my off time I often don&amp;#39;t end up doing what I want to do because I&amp;#39;m so pissed that I had to work and dread going back to work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s not the conditions of my particular job. It&amp;#39;s not my coworkers. I like them and they like me, but I wouldn&amp;#39;t hang out with them outside work (though in fairness I&amp;#39;d rarely hang out with anyone, I generally don&amp;#39;t like people). It&amp;#39;s not the pay. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s just that I don&amp;#39;t want to do it because I hate how work takes priority over everything else in my life. The best and only solution I&amp;#39;ve found is to save as much as I can without being a complete miser so that I can retire earlier than normal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And starting my own business or doing a hobby as work? No thanks to that either. That&amp;#39;s still work too and extrinsic vs intrinsic motivation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Reddit（除了幽默和信息子站之外）是一个不可救药的粪坑，充满了白痴式的打圈圈、扯皮、政治垃圾和权力操纵的mods。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这恰好包括这个子，虽然根据规则D，我不是在谈论
我仍然认为完全有可能改变我的想法。
我的想法--见下文）。

总之，在任何不致力于幽默或中性话题的子栏目中都是这样的
(即没有任何政治、社会或......）。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r1g6ww/cmv_reddit_outside_of_humor_and_informational/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r1g6ww/cmv_reddit_outside_of_humor_and_informational/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 02:40:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This &lt;em&gt;happens&lt;/em&gt; to include this sub, although as per Rule D I am &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; talking about this sub in particular (and I DO still think it is entirely possible to change my mind--see below.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, this is how it goes on any sub not devoted to humor or neutral topics (i.e. without any political, social or psychological relevance whatsoever)... you have two choices:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A) Choose to post something short and blunt, get a torrent of people spamming the same exact objection, which you do have a response to but you have to repeat it over and over until your fingers bleed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B) Choose to post something of medium to long length, everyone reads 10% of it and skims the rest, and then spews out &lt;strong&gt;the same exact frickin&amp;#39; objections anyway&lt;/strong&gt;, and this is allowed because being lazy or an illiterate moron is not just &lt;em&gt;allowed&lt;/em&gt;, but is actively &lt;em&gt;encouraged&lt;/em&gt; by mods on those types of subs... because this level of idiocy is very time-efficient, drives sub activity, and drives the drama that ultimately gives them that sweet, sweet release of dopamine that they so crave when they get to remove a post (generally for the crime of being too coherent and/or too non-troll-y.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no option C.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one is ever warned, banned or otherwise sanctioned for posting non-sequiturs, straw men, or generally incoherent second grade level drivel. Ever. On any sub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And on top of this, the overwhelming majority of mods also lazy and/or capricious (see above comment re: dopamine) and/or pursuing their own agenda, so it doesn&amp;#39;t really matter what the rules are anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s also the matter of CONSTANTLY having to &amp;quot;prove&amp;quot; that you&amp;#39;re not a conservative (and I most certainly am not!) in order to make any comment that in any way that &lt;em&gt;happens&lt;/em&gt; contradicts the moronically fortune cookie-level party line that the popular left happens to be championing today.  E.g. Fauci is a self-serving asshat who obviously made the pandemic much worse, but no one can mention this without prefacing it with a 10,000 word essay about how horrible Trump and Rand Paul are.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yet actually taking the time to post those sorts of disclaimers is enough to make your post too long for 95% of people to bother reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, any time you comprehensively and decisively debunk someone&amp;#39;s ignorant nonsense with a bevy of citations and earnest rhetoric, there will be no reply (unless it&amp;#39;s someone who simply ignores what you wrote and starts strawmanning), but instead there will be a single and amusingly defiant vote down. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is because:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a) there&amp;#39;s no penalty for doing this (because everyone copied Slashdot&amp;#39;s amazing idea of comment moderation, but no one bothered copying or expanding on the equally important concept of meta-moderation to keep it honest) and &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b) your intelligent rebuttal is far, far too long for anyone other than the poster you&amp;#39;re replying to to bother reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And due to a combination of the above reasons, Hot / Top are inevitably dominated by the same asinine line-toeing topics, so you have to wade through the garbage heap of New in order to find something that isn&amp;#39;t the same cliched circlejerk you&amp;#39;ve seen 1000 times before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is section is NOT meant to be a part of my CMV (otherwise, a particularly intrepid mod might claim it runs afoul of rule D!) I am including this here ONLY for the sake of mods who may be considering removing the post, and for those considering reporting it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule A: I clearly pass this rule, though I&amp;#39;m sure an especially ambitious mod could simply claim that I posted less than 500 words (in base 200!), in which case I&amp;#39;ll simply have to tip my hat to their creativity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule B &amp;quot;willingness&amp;quot;: It would be very, very, very easy to change my view. &lt;strong&gt;Link to a sub where the clowns and trolls are not running the show.&lt;/strong&gt;  That would change my mind. It&amp;#39;s exceedingly simple.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course it doesn&amp;#39;t actually matter if I do end up posting 7 times that my view has &amp;#39;substantially changed&amp;#39;, because someone only has to link 3 posts where I disagreed with examples provided (by trolls and/or the illiterate) and that will surely be enough to have the post removed.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule B &amp;quot;soapbox&amp;quot;: Lol, hell no I don&amp;#39;t expect to any of this change anyone&amp;#39;s mind. I&amp;#39;ve spent a few hours going through this sub and it&amp;#39;s obviously beyond redemption. The vast majority of people here (as elsewhere on Reddit! No rule D, no rule D! This isn&amp;#39;t meta! I mention it &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; to explain why I certainly wouldn&amp;#39;t bother trying to soapbox here) are lazy douchebags, and the ones that aren&amp;#39;t certainly don&amp;#39;t need me to explain the patently obvious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(BUT! Some noble person from this remaining tiny percentage might be able to give me a counterexample, thus Changing My View and giving me a more worthwhile sub to focus on.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Of course, because I almost always make the effort to articulate myself clearly and completely, this will likely be deemed &amp;quot;soapboxing&amp;quot; by mods who are used to people posting the textual equivalent of a stream of emojis.&lt;/strong&gt;  The working definition of &amp;quot;non-soapboxing&amp;quot; is obviously just flinging your feces at a wall for a couple minutes and calling it a post.  Whereas anyone who actually thinks about things and has ideas complex enough to rise above a gradeschool level, and is willing to take the time to articulate those ideas, &lt;em&gt;obviously&lt;/em&gt; has an agenda of some sort. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(But not the legions of trolls; those guys are cool.) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule C: I think my title more or less covers it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule D &amp;quot;meta&amp;quot;: Again, I&amp;#39;m more than happy to not mention this subreddit at all (and indeed this entire section is meant ONLY for the mods.) HOWEVER, what may end up happening is this: some troll is going to go through my post history and comment on something specific. I will inevitably respond, because I have no self-restraint whatsoever in these matters. This will be used as justification to remove the post, while the troll (who brought up the subbreddit first) will suffer no consequences. C&amp;#39;est la vie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And again this isn&amp;#39;t specific to this sub. The mods on nonhumorous/noninformational subs know well enough not to remove the trolls.  Trolls are their lifeblood.  Without the trolls and the circlejerkers, who would drive their traffic up to desirable levels (as well as luring in unsuspecting victims to be sacrificed for that sublime hit of dopamine)?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule D &amp;quot;personal harm&amp;quot;: I mean, it &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; true that 97% of Reddit (and the human race in general) would serve society infinitely better by being fed into a wood chipper and used as fertilizer for crops. This is just an objective fact. You can&amp;#39;t argue with facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But no, I&amp;#39;m not campaigning for this nor do I bear especially ill will toward any one &lt;em&gt;particular&lt;/em&gt; person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule D &amp;quot;self-promotion&amp;quot;:  Uh. no. I mean Christ, if anyone has a good idea for actually monetizing my entirely well-founded and righteous contempt, PLEASE DM me.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule E: Oh, believe you me I will respond. And it will not be low effort.  I can count on one hand the number of Reddit users I&amp;#39;ve ever seen who&amp;#39;ve put more effort into their responses than I (on any sub. I&amp;#39;m NOT talking about this sub! No Rule D violation!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: CMV: 任何要求员工完成无偿实习的公司也应该要求在实习期间为他们提供食宿。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这不会很长。如果一个公司要求员工在成为无偿的
如果公司要求员工在成为带薪雇员之前成为无薪实习生，他们应该被要求为他们提供住所和食物。
并为他们提供食物。就这么简单。否则基本上就是契约奴役了。

所有每周40小时或3个全天的志愿工作或...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r1atb1/cmv_cmv_any_company_that_requires_employees_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r1atb1/cmv_cmv_any_company_that_requires_employees_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 02:04:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;#39;t going to be long. If a company requires an employee to be an unpaid intern before becoming a paid employee, they should be required to house them and feed them. Simple as that. It&amp;#39;s basically indentured servitude otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All volunteer work that is 40 hours a week or 3 full days or more (24 hours a week but 3 days a week) should require room and board because it prevents the volunteer from being able to work full time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unpaid internships are the biggest scam in America. A classist system meant a way for the upper class to get free labor from the lower class by veiling it as &amp;quot;experience&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit- I am mostly talking about internships that impede the ability for the interns to work another job while in training for prolonged periods of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：所有理性的成年人都有死亡的权利]]></title><description><![CDATA[我相信所有理性的人都有身体自主的权利，并且可以
允许他们以任何他们认为合适的方式改变或使用自己的身体，只要
只要不侵犯他人的权利。这在一定程度上排除了
幼儿、婴儿和动物，这就是为什么我们要做某些...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0pepa/cmv_all_rational_adults_have_a_right_to_die/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0pepa/cmv_all_rational_adults_have_a_right_to_die/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 19:34:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I believe that all rational agents have a right to bodily autonomy, and are allowed to alter or engage their own body in whatever way they see fit so long as it doesn&amp;#39;t infringe on the rights of others. This would somewhat exclude young children, infants, and animals which is why we do certain things without their consent, and I&amp;#39;m not going to defend that parties with limited rationality have a right to die.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To elaborate, the right to bodily autonomy would include a right to end one&amp;#39;s life on their own terms because that is just a person exercising control over their body, and it doesn&amp;#39;t violate the rights of anyone else. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To clarify, a lot of suicides can be irrational. But I don&amp;#39;t think suicide is ever immoral, unless perhaps if someone&amp;#39;s dependant on you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Potential objections:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanting to die is a sign of mental illness, and thus irrationality. So no one has the right to die&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why is it irrational to want to die though? It is true that humans on average will value their own lives, but I don&amp;#39;t think it follows from this that they therefore ought to value their own lives. Why is it always in one&amp;#39;s self-interest to live?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don&amp;#39;t have a right to someone&amp;#39;s labor, so you don&amp;#39;t have a right to something like euthanasia or assisted suicide&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t disagree with this, however, I still think people should at least have the option to go see a doctor for the chance of receiving assisted suicide. People still have a right to at least associate themselves in consensual relationships where they get a say, so why can&amp;#39;t a doctor and a patient engage in such a consensual relation? I don&amp;#39;t think doctors should be fired for refusing to deliver a certain type of care, but this is still compatible with saying that the state should lift certain restrictions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who genuinely want to die will find ways to die without assisted suicide&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know if completely remember the objection correctly, but I&amp;#39;ll respond to this statement anyways. Yes, people may end up finding other ways to die if they&amp;#39;re desparate, but I don&amp;#39;t see how it follows that we need to maintain a restriction on something like assisted suicide. People still have a right to engage in certain consensual relations. They should have certain positive freedoms. Why would we need to limit their options? Now if the point of this objection is trying to say that it&amp;#39;s useless to lift the restriction because people will just use other methods of killing themselves instead, then this arguably seems false. People will no longer have to use certain methods which are less successful or have a higher risk for leaving them disabled, and they also have an incentive to not commit suicide in public areas which will traumitize more people. Granted, in an assisted suicide scenario, you&amp;#39;re probably still affecting the doctor mentally, but you&amp;#39;re still traumitizing less people in that setting. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, the uselessness of lifting a regulation which infringes on bodily autonomy doesn&amp;#39;t thereby follow that we shouldn&amp;#39;t life that regulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recognizing the right to die will lead to more irrational suicides and will lead to abuse&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think certain policies could be enacted to prevent irrational suicides. For healthy adults who want to kill themselves, there can be a waiting period put in place to give them time to think about whether they actually want to kill themselves. For adults who are chronically or mentally ill, I would rather they don&amp;#39;t have a waiting period if they are in lots of suffering and want to get rid of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：无政府状态会使社会变得更糟。]]></title><description><![CDATA[想象一下，如果明天，政府说他们将取消所有的
控制 "的指标。不再有分隔车道的线，不再有停车位
标志、速度限制、红灯、绿灯、行人过街标志等等。
什么都没有! 你有完全的自由来驾驶你想驾驶的东西......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r17skt/cmv_anarchy_would_make_society_worse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r17skt/cmv_anarchy_would_make_society_worse/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 18:30:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine if tomorrow, the government said that they would be removing all indicators of &amp;quot;control&amp;quot; on roads!  No more lines separating lanes, no more stop signs, speed limits, red lights, green lights, pedestrian crossing signs etc... nothing!  You have total freedom to drive how YOU want to drive without the state in any way telling you how you should drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would this work?  yeah, maybe... would it make driving and/or being a pedestrian an infinitely more dangerous task with vehicularly related fatalities sky-rocketing?  of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one aspect of society among many that could be pointed to where it is much better for society in general that we have regulation!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now sure, if you want to make the argument that, on principle, people should be free to do what they want even if it makes society considerably worse for everyone... fair enough!  I personally find that immoral; but insofar as we are concerned with bettering society and everyone&amp;#39;s lives... anarchism is antithetical to that goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：即使他在技术上没有违反法律，凯尔-瑞特豪斯的行为也是不道德的，应该被劝阻。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我首先要说的是，我知道Reddit上的大多数人都同意我的观点，但右翼人士的普遍看法似乎是凯尔-瑞特豪斯在做的事情。
右翼人士的共同信念似乎是，凯尔-瑞特豪斯在进行
他的无罪释放是美国自卫权的一次胜利。
他的无罪释放是美国自卫权的胜利，所以我想给这些...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r1af45/cmv_even_if_he_technically_didnt_break_the_law/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r1af45/cmv_even_if_he_technically_didnt_break_the_law/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 18:30:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll  start by saying that I know most of Reddit agrees with me, but the  common belief among right-wing folks seems to be that Kyle Rittenhouse  was doing the right thing during the Kenosha unrest, and that his  acquittal is a victory for the right to self defense in the US, so I  want to give those folks the chance to change my mind if I truly am  being brainwashed by the media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s what I saw: A right-leaning 17-year-old boy sees that  left-leaning protests are happening about 20 miles away from him, and  that some of the protestors are being violent and destroying property.  He drives to the scene of the unrest with a semi-automatic rifle, and  begins pointing it at many different people. Many, though not all, of  the people his weapon is pointed at are non-violent and unarmed. People  with weapons point them back at him, they shoot at him, he shoots back,  he kills three people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opinions on this are divided along political lines, with many  praising his actions as successfully defending someone else&amp;#39;s property.   I personally feel that if this type of behavior is encouraged, it opens  the door for vigilante justice and extrajudicial murder:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If someone owns a business that is at risk during civil unrest, a  third party doesn&amp;#39;t just get to take a deadly weapon, stand in front of  it, and kill anyone they think might pose a risk to that business,  especially when the business owner never asked them to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This can be used as a justification for nearly any murder, as long  as there&amp;#39;s some sort of identifiable risk nearby. Consider: &amp;quot;A hurricane  passed near our town. There&amp;#39;s a store there that might have been  destroyed (not my store, someone else&amp;#39;s who never asked me to help in  any way). I stood in front of the store to protect it. I brought my  rifle because that&amp;#39;s my right. Someone approached store who I thought  was likely a looter, so I killed them to protect the store.&amp;quot; Basically,  any time there&amp;#39;s unrest, &amp;quot;protecting property&amp;quot; can be used to justify  killing anyone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rittenhouse was pointing his gun all over the place, which means  that many people could have been justified in feeling that their life  was in danger. If someone shot him in self defense, then his shooting  them back could not be considered self defense either. Even if we don&amp;#39;t  include a legal perspective here, bringing a rifle anywhere and pointing  it at an unarmed person in a vigilante/extrajudicial manner is immoral,  and if people with weapons are pointing them at each other, self  defense no longer becomes a valid moral defense for either of them on  the whole. Once someone starts shooting at Rittenhouse, his only viable  choice might have been to shoot back, but that doesn&amp;#39;t discount every  choice he made up until that point.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m sure I have an incomplete version of the facts, and I&amp;#39;d certainly  love to be corrected (ideally with proper sourcing), but learning more  about that night is only going to change my view if it helps establish  that Rittenhouse was morally justified that night. I really want to see  what I&amp;#39;m missing here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果美国不对其选举和政治制度采取任何措施，它将不再是 "民主"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我相信你已经听说了美国现在发生的一切，而我
我不禁问自己，几年后这个国家会是什么样子。

正如你可能知道的那样，选区划分允许一个政党（民主党和共和党都这样做）在本质上决定了一个国家的命运。
共和党人都这样做），基本上可以提前决定选举结果......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r17vby/cmv_if_the_us_doesnt_do_anything_to_its_electoral/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r17vby/cmv_if_the_us_doesnt_do_anything_to_its_electoral/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 17:00:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m sure you’ve heard of everything that’s going on in the US right now, and I can’t help but ask myself what the country will look like in a few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you probably know, gerrymandering allows a party (both Democrats and Republicans do this) to essentially determine election results ahead of time. There is no way this is healthy for a democracy like the US. Democracy is supposed to be free and fair, and deciding results ahead of time or altering maps to benefit yourself is definitely not fair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we have the issue of an increasing willingness from the Republicans to reject all defeats as fraudulent (I personally find this hypocritical given their record of passing voter restriction laws). You might know that this is one of the things that put the US on the receding democracies list earlier this year. This wouldn’t concern me too much if it was just talk, but an increasing amount of “election fraud” lawyers are being appointed to election boards, which will probably allow them to overturn any defeats by refusing to certify the election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So these are my two top concerns with US democracy, especially the second one. I guess this is why the US is a “flawed democracy” and not a full democracy like many other countries and why it is classified as a receding democracy this year. I know that I’m wrong about a couple of things, so feel free to point out my mistakes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：病态肥胖的人不应该参与身体积极性的活动，也不应该在媒体上被美化。]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为一个胖子，我已经厌倦了看到病态肥胖的人拥抱身体积极性和美化身体。
我厌倦了看到病态肥胖的人拥抱身体，美化他们可怕的健康选择。

我明白很多事情都会影响到体重的增加。我不是在说
我说的不是200磅的人，而是300多磅的人相信他们是健康的，而且
那是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0pfxc/cmv_morbidly_obese_people_shouldnt_get_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0pfxc/cmv_morbidly_obese_people_shouldnt_get_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 17:00:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a fat person, I’m tired of seeing morbidly obese people embrace body positivity and glorify their horrible health choices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand a lot of things come into play with gaining weight. I’m not talking about 200 lb people, but people who are 300+ lbs believing they are healthy and that there’s nothing wrong with them, the media encouraging them too. Those people will probably need oxygen, are taking a plethora of medications, probably can’t walk for more than 5 minutes, and can barely move. Not to mention the psychological toll it has to be taking on them. Shows like my 600 and 1000lb life disgust me. They show women who clearly need serious help and somehow glorify their life. Sure, they have docs on the show but you see how they don’t take them seriously. Those people are disgusting. No, people who mention their health are not being fatphobic, those are genuine concerns. If you don’t want to change your life, so be it. But don’t showcase your death wish for others to see. Stop glorifying it. It’s not cute, it’s not trendy, no one should want to look like that. No one should struggle taking a shower or walking their dog. Body posi is not for you, it’s for big (300lb and under), poc, and disabled men and women. Stop ruining the movement for us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cmv: 从商业角度来看，公司采取政治立场，尤其是在今天的政治舞台上采取强烈的政治立场是愚蠢的，甚至是愚蠢的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国人的政治立场几乎各占一半，采取强烈的政治立场
采取强烈的政治立场是完全愚蠢的，为什么你可能会消除你的一半
客户群？商业和政治没有理由联系在一起。
今天，采取强烈的进步立场的公司正在被拉黑......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0s6xc/cmv_its_silly_even_stupid_from_a_business/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0s6xc/cmv_its_silly_even_stupid_from_a_business/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 03:42:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a near 50/50 split in politics amongst Americans, taking a strong political stance is flat out foolish, why would you potentially eliminate half your customer base? Business and politics has no reason to be in association. Companies today taking strong progressive stances are being blackballed by many conservatives. Not so much the other way around but the point still stands either way. Produce your product and service and keep your views to yourself. When you openly put your views out there as a company you 9/10 times are gonna lose more customers than gain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：任何对Covid疫苗的反对意见几乎完全是政治性的，根本不是基于科学和医学的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我之所以持这种观点，是因为我所看到的所有对Covid疫苗的安全性或有效性表示怀疑的信息来源都是右派政治。
我之所以持这种观点，是因为我所看到的所有对科维德疫苗的安全性或有效性表示怀疑的资料都可以追溯到右翼政治。它们是
他们是政治来源，发表在政治网站上，他们是博主，也发表右翼政治观点。
他们也发表右翼政治观点。

任何非政治性的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0iojg/cmv_any_opposition_to_the_covid_vaccine_is_almost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0iojg/cmv_any_opposition_to_the_covid_vaccine_is_almost/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 18:47:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hold this view because EVERY source I&amp;#39;ve seen that casts doubt on the safety or efficacy of the Covid vaccine goes right back to right-wing politics. They&amp;#39;re political sources, they&amp;#39;re published on political websites, they&amp;#39;re bloggers who also post right-wing political view. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any non-political source I&amp;#39;ve found is clearly in support of vaccines. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want my view changed because I do try to look at both sides of an issue. I do want all the information about a topic, especially in regards to mine and my family&amp;#39;s health and safety. And if nothing else, I want to be able to respect the views of friends and family who feel otherwise. I would love for it to simply be a difference of opinion that&amp;#39;s intelligently based in reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit- i would add that any irrational, non-credible reason would be included with political, even though I only specified political. Whether it&amp;#39;s fear, conspiracy, or anything along those lines&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：没有人有权获得任何人的吸引力，批评不与跨性别女性约会的男性的跨性别者与批评不与矮个子男性约会的女性的跨性别者一样糟糕（又称乱伦者）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我的标题可能有点混乱。但在reddit上有很多反incel的帖子
reddit上有很多反incel的帖子。煽动者整天抱怨女人不和矮个子男人约会，女人认为矮个子男人 "不是真正的男人 "等等。
矮个子男人是 "不是真正的男人 "等等。人们理所当然地把他们叫出来，告诉他们停止抱怨。
他们停止发牢骚。

然而，我看到人们在谈论如何...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0fzsx/cmv_no_one_is_entitled_to_anyones_attraction_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0fzsx/cmv_no_one_is_entitled_to_anyones_attraction_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 17:31:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So my title may be a bit confusing. But there&amp;#39;s a lot of anti-incel posts on reddit. Incels whine all day about how women don&amp;#39;t date short men how women see short men as &amp;quot;not real men&amp;quot; etc etc. People, rightfully call them out and tell them to stop whining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I&amp;#39;ve seen people talk about how &amp;quot;men that don&amp;#39;t date trans women don&amp;#39;t see trans women as real women and therefore bigots.&amp;quot; and the same group of people agree with that sentiment disagree with the sentiment that &amp;quot;women who don&amp;#39;t date short men are bigots&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, my view is, trans women who complain about men who don&amp;#39;t date trans women are just as bad as the cis men who complain about women not dating them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one is entitled to be attracted to you. I&amp;#39;m allowed to not be attracted to trans women the same way women are allowed to not like short men. And this is coming from a guy who is legally a drawf (5&amp;#39;6&amp;quot;),and kinda hate women for not dating me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：没有什么超自然现象或超自然现象。]]></title><description><![CDATA[鬼魂、恶魔、神灵、神话中的生物，所有这些都声称存在。
这些都是由传闻证据支持的。视频监控无处不在。
每个人的口袋里都有一个录像机，但却没有任何证据表明有什么异常。
不正常。灵媒和通灵者总是被揭发，因为他们都很沮丧....。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0bn13/cmv_the_is_nothing_paranormal_or_supernatural/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r0bn13/cmv_the_is_nothing_paranormal_or_supernatural/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 16:39:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghosts, demons, deities, mythical creatures all of these claim to exist all of which are only propped up by anecdotal evidence. Video surveillance everywhere, everyone with a video recorder in their pockets, yet no evidence of anything abnormal. Mediums and psychics always being exposed as fruads. Voodoo practitioners exposed as frauds. Self proclaimed witches that do nothing. If ghosts were real with all that time our greatest minds that have passed on would have found a way to communicate with the living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking all of that into consideration I can only conclude there is nothing para or supernatural.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：不管你的政治观点如何，一般来说，人们需要对他们花钱的地方承担更多责任。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我相信，行动比语言更有说服力。如果你意识到并抱怨
抱怨一家公司的做法--甚至只是一家小企业，我想
- 但你继续在那里花钱，那么你真正说的是
这些商品和服务的价值超过了......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r079eh/cmv_regardless_of_your_political_views_people_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r079eh/cmv_regardless_of_your_political_views_people_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 13:31:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I believe that actions speak louder than words. If you are aware of and complain about the practices of a corporation - or even just a small business, I suppose - but you continue to spend your money there, then what you’re really saying is that the value of those goods and services outweigh the cons (such as underpaid employees, environmental issues, sexual harassment, etc). You’re sending the message to company and the market that what they are doing is ultimately okay in your eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is based on the assumption that you have the ability to spend your money somewhere else, which I think is true much more often than not. After all, most things aren’t strictly necessary to buy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: As I’ve already awarded deltas for these points, I need to clarify that I’m talking about picking the least objectionable options you’re aware of when you shop.. not turning yourself into a saint. If our culture was more intentional with the way it spends its money, the world would be a better place.. would it not?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：告诉一个不伦恋者去做爱只会弊大于利。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我注意到，在社交媒体上，那些与乱伦者争论的人告诉他们要
我注意到，在社交媒体上，那些与乱伦者争论的人告诉他们，让他们躺下，因为他们不喜欢让乱伦者发疯。我同意，让不结盟者发疯
是相当有趣的。然而，让他们上床并不能阻止他们憎恨女性。
妇女。

不合群者的产生远比 "不合群 "更深入。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzs6nb/cmv_telling_an_incel_to_get_laid_only_does_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzs6nb/cmv_telling_an_incel_to_get_laid_only_does_more/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 06:30:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have noticed that on social media, those who argue with incels tell them to get laid out of spite of making the incel mad. I will agree, making incels mad is quite funny. However, telling them to get laid will not stop them from hating women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The creation of incels goes far deeper than the inability to have sex. It usually stems from popular culture (specifically from the 1980s-2010s), portraying those who don&amp;#39;t have a lot of sex or those who look like the average person, as losers. This doesn&amp;#39;t mean incels are free from blame, it should be their responsibility to distinguish reality from fantasy. However, that fantasy can leave an impression on the youth, specifically those in high school. Mind you, incels don&amp;#39;t just wake up and start hating women one day, its a slow process, taking months or even years to fully mature the hatred. It&amp;#39;s a process that usually starts in high school, where everyone is trying to make a name for themselves in those 4 short years. If anyone here has been to high school, you should know how the social hierarchy works in that hell hole. Though its not as common anymore (thank fuck), virgins still get made fun of and are considered losers who are ultimately at the bottom of this hierarchy. Now think about it, you have an insecure person who grew up with this sort of culture all their lives, then they go to high school (specifically between the late 1990s and early to mid 2010s), which then reinforces this way of thinking with the established hierarchy, you now have the perfect breeding ground for incels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me just add one more thing. Porn. As we all know, most porn is fake as fuck and as teenagers, its safe to say that 80% of us has watched porn at least once in our lives. When we watch porn, we see this fake image of what sex is supposed to be. Y&amp;#39;know loud, easy, good looking models, large dicks, large breasts, etc. Essentially people that some people consider &amp;quot;flawless&amp;quot;. But behind the scenes, its just fake as fuck. However, incels more or less don&amp;#39;t know this, and consider those &amp;quot;flawless&amp;quot; individuals as &amp;quot;Chads/Tyrones&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Stacies&amp;quot;. To them, those &amp;quot;Chads&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Stacies&amp;quot; are the ones who are valued more in society, because of the supposed ease they have getting sex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To wrap this up, telling incels to get laid is a horrible thing to do. It only reinforces the idea of &amp;quot;The amount of sex a person has is equal to an individual&amp;#39;s value in society and if I don&amp;#39;t have sex, I am worthless.&amp;quot; Sex is not the equivalent of therapy. So stop it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: Telling an incel to get laid is bad. It only reinforces the idea of &amp;quot;sex = individual value.&amp;quot; Inceldom stems from years of unchecked insecurities and horrible pop culture. They need therapy not sex.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在新闻报道中描述某些嫌疑人而不描述其他嫌疑人是偏执的做法]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道这种情况在美国有多普遍，但你通常可以通过缺乏描述来判断一个
你通常可以通过缺乏描述来判断犯罪是由少数人犯下的。我的当地新闻
对白人的描述是没有问题的，即使它并不重要。
也不一定重要。但是当它是一个少数民族群体时，它就显得格外...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r02c3e/cmv_its_bigoted_to_describe_certain_suspects_but/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/r02c3e/cmv_its_bigoted_to_describe_certain_suspects_but/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 05:35:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure how common it is around the US but you can usually tell when a crime is committed by a minority by the lack of description given. My local news will give a description of white people no problem even when it doesn’t necessarily matter. But when it’s a minority group it’s extra vague. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, there was a story about a woman who was harassing some kids to get off the sidewalk riding bikes and spit on them. She was arrested and taken to jail, they had her name and age but for some reason had to make it known she was white. It wasn’t really relevant &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, there was a story about a group of 3 “massage therapist” who were meeting people at hotels and robbing them. the clients who came forward gave a description but the news only reported “3 women about 5’10”-6ft tall posing as masseuses”. This spree went on for another week until they were finally caught and it turned out to be 3 black transwomen. The people who came forward said they gave this information &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another kinda goofy one was where the guy was caught on camera robbing a store and they described everything about him, down to a bandage on his leg, excluding his race. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how it’s pretty easy to tell when some crime was committed by a nonwhite person because there’s no mention of race at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this In itself is bigoted and dangerous. I don’t know how effective descriptions actually are, but I’d bet they’re far less effective leaving out major descriptions like this as well. Just put relevant descriptions in all articles or none&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: forgot to add the “masseuses” were actually robbing people&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：应该为消费者简化条款和条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[大多数产品/服务涉及无休止的法律术语和术语的段落。
术语，根本无法让普通消费者理解。
因此，正如许多关于这个问题的调查所表明的那样，大多数消费者只是简单地阅读了一下
或在任何程度上都不承认上述条款和条件，尽管他们接受了......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzw2xq/cmv_terms_and_conditions_should_be_simplified_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzw2xq/cmv_terms_and_conditions_should_be_simplified_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 01:12:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most products/services involve endless paragraphs of legal jargon and terminology which simply cannot be described as accessible for the average consumer hence, as many surveys on the matter suggest, most consumers skim read or do not acknowledge, to any extent, said T&amp;amp;C&amp;#39;s despite their acceptance of them. Allowing T&amp;amp;C&amp;#39;s to be simplified would allow consumers to make better informed choices before engaging in any contractual relationship. Consumers should be able to ascertain the fundamental principles that establish a contract with ease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I&amp;#39;m not suggesting the removal of the current T&amp;amp;C&amp;#39;s (they should be maintained for valid reasons that comments below explain) but rather a supplementary version alongside for ordinary consumers (in that the event or pursuit of any legal challenge is unlikely) that covers the essentials of a contractual relationship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：共和党建制派并不真正支持小政府的理想]]></title><description><![CDATA[IMO，一个 "小政府 "将减少外国军事存在。
争取降低监禁率和累犯率，（包括取消耗费资源并耗费各州大量资金的私营监狱系统）。
包括取消耗费资源和花费各州大量资金的私有化监狱系统。
美元）减少警察的存在，结束对毒品的战争，取消法律......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzgy25/cmv_the_republican_establishment_isnt_really_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzgy25/cmv_the_republican_establishment_isnt_really_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 21:32:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IMO, a “smaller government” would have a reduced foreign military presence, strive for decreased incarceration and recidivism rates, (including the removal of privatized prison systems which drain resources and cost the states a lot of $$$) less police presence, end the war on drugs, remove laws that legislate on a women’s right to an abortion. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this just the compromise between libertarian ideals and the evangelicals? Tbh idk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess, the way I see it, small government is only being upheld by Republicans is in a financial context: no handouts, and less government regulation of the economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I have been convinced that abortion isn’t a valid piece of evidence&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：对瑞特豪斯判决的回应是对刑事司法改革的打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为刑事司法改革倡议的长期支持者和捐助人，我对所谓的 "专家 "对判决的反应感到非常不安。
我对所谓的 "自由主义者 "对这一判决的反应感到非常不安，他们在去年的大部分时间里都在赞扬BLM的抗议活动，有时还做了一些事情。
他们去年大部分时间都在赞扬BLM的抗议活动，而且有时还在刑事司法方面做了一些实际的工作。
在刑事司法方面做了一些实际的好工作（运动...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzpvy1/cmv_the_response_to_the_rittenhouse_verdict_is_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzpvy1/cmv_the_response_to_the_rittenhouse_verdict_is_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 18:32:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a longtime proponent and donor to Criminal Justice Reform initiatives, I am extremely distraught by the reaction to the verdict by so called &amp;quot;liberals&amp;quot; who spent much of last year praising BLM protests and have, at times, done some actual good work in terms of criminal justice (&lt;a href=&quot;https://campaignzero.org/#research&quot;&gt;Campaign Zero&lt;/a&gt;, for example).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many extremely prominent individuals and organizations have made it clear that much like their (usually right-wing) opponents, they do not care about accused individuals who do not line up with their politics or aren the wrong race. Similar to free speech, the concept of criminal justice needs to be politically agnostic. There should be no political prosecutions in this country. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2021/11/19/statement-by-president-biden/&quot;&gt;President&lt;/a&gt;, to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-kamala-harris-denounces-rittenhouse-verdict-says-clearly-theres-a-lot-more-work-to-do/&quot;&gt;VP&lt;/a&gt;,  to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ACLU/status/1461762952567136259&quot;&gt;ACLU&lt;/a&gt; of all places, prominent people who say they are proponents of Criminal Justice Reform have not only spouted misinformation about the facts of the case, but have objected to a decision made by a jury of fellow citizens, an extremely dangerous president to set. They&amp;#39;ve made it clear that they would have preferred Rittenhouse be found guilty of murder without any real explanation of their stance outside of objecting with how it made them feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is in no way condoning the valorization of Rittenhouse by the right, but the left has been entirely unprincipled in this extremely important area of governance and their hypocrisy has hurt the overall cause. &lt;strong&gt;If you&amp;#39;re unwilling to support people you do no like, you don&amp;#39;t actually care about a principle.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMV!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果你公开携带步枪在美国城市走动，你就是个混蛋。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在正常情况下，这样做的唯一原因是为了证明一个
观点（即，这是美国，我们有权利使用我们的枪）或恐吓
人。如果有积极的骚乱，你想坐在你自己的屋顶上
你想拿着步枪坐在自己的商店或类似的地方（就像许多韩国人一样... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzn2tm/cmv_if_you_walk_around_a_us_city_open_carrying_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzn2tm/cmv_if_you_walk_around_a_us_city_open_carrying_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 17:03:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under normal circumstances, the only reason to do this is to either prove a point (i.e., it&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;merica and we got our right to our gun) or to intimidate people.  If there is active unrest and you want to sit on the roof of your own store or something like that with a rifle (like many of the Korean shop owners did during L.A. riots) to protect your own property, I can at least understand that.  I don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s a good idea, but you&amp;#39;re not an asshole for doing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But just walking around the streets open carrying a rifle?  Yeah, there&amp;#39;s no reason for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This excludes military and police.  Not that it&amp;#39;s okay for them to just walk around with a rifle whenever; but there are situations where they can probably do it and not be an asshole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：至少，美国应该为所有18岁以下的公民提供政府资助的医疗保健。]]></title><description><![CDATA[归根结底，我认为这还不够；我认为我们应该有
我认为我们应该为每个人提供社会化的医疗保健。但我确实理解反对的论点
它。然而，我不认为这些论点在我们谈论儿童时能站住脚。
谈论儿童的时候，这些论点都站不住脚。由于孩子们无法找到工作，所以无论多么努力...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzjnnk/cmv_at_the_very_least_the_united_states_should/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzjnnk/cmv_at_the_very_least_the_united_states_should/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 15:40:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, I think this doesn&amp;#39;t go far enough; I think we ought to have socialized healthcare for everyone. But I do understand the arguments against it. However, I don&amp;#39;t think that any of these arguments hold up when we&amp;#39;re talking about children. Since children can&amp;#39;t hold jobs, no amount of hard work or personal responsibility is going to help them pay for medical care. Since their parents make the vast majority of nurturing decisions for them (like what to eat and what to drink) their medical issues are very unlikely to be their fault. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Children aren&amp;#39;t their parents&amp;#39; property. A system in which a child receives inadequate medical care because his parents&amp;#39; are janitors with bad health insurance is an immoral system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：媒体为了利益，故意在瑞特豪斯案上误导公众，并有可能在案件结束后挑起更多的民间骚乱，不管结果如何，他们知道由于他们故意的错误信息，大家都很分裂。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，我没有在新闻中关注瑞特豪斯案。我不看新闻直播，不看流媒体。
我不看流媒体，一般来说，我倾向于避开这种东西。

我对瑞特豪斯案的唯一真正了解是
我在这里读到的几条线索和我看到/听到的几个片段......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzlq44/cmv_the_media_was_intentionally_misleading_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzlq44/cmv_the_media_was_intentionally_misleading_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 15:40:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I did not follow the Rittenhouse case on the news. I don’t watch live news, I don’t watch streams, I tend to, in general, steer clear of this kind of stuff. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My only real understanding of what was going on with the Rittenhouse case was the few threads I read on here and a couple clips I saw/heard from other peoples devices when I was present, other than the basics of what happened from back when it all actually happened. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But as much as I tried to stay neutral, I formulated an opinion, though not a particularly firm one, admittedly. My initial opinion was that he was an absolute idiot for going to Kenosha to begin with armed with a gun, and was probably looking for trouble, and had no reason to go there as he didn’t even live in Wisconsin. And while he may have actually feared for his life in that moment, he probably should be found guilty because of his stupid decisions that lead him to be in that position in the first place. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But curiosity and a desire for the truth got the best of me, and I went and watched archives of the full trial. And boy did angry people angry at the acquittal and the media misrepresent realty in a &lt;strong&gt;major&lt;/strong&gt; way. But the most concerning issue here is that I actually think that many of the angry people on social media that want Rittenhouse in prison &lt;em&gt;aren’t even aware of how incredibly misinformed they are.&lt;/em&gt; Because all they’ve seen is what CNN or their favorite social media reporter/influencer wants them to see, which paints a picture very different from reality. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They never mention that Rittenhouse had family and friends that live in Kenosha.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They never mention that he was employed in Kenosha.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To both of these points, they make it seem like he’s over there blindly and had no reason to be there other than to be in the fray and incite fear and hostility in rioters. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They never show pictures of him the previous day scrubbing graffiti off the walls of the high school down the road from where the shooting took place.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They never show footage of him walking around with his medical bag asking people if they need medical assistance, yelling “friendly friendly friendly” to assure everyone that he’s not hostile.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And most importantly, they never show any of the footage that clearly shows from multiple angles all three of the people he shot, and the fact that he was running away from 2 of them, lunged at by one before cornered between vehicles and a mob of people while his weapon was being grabbed, and the other two he was hit in the head and knocked down while being advanced on by a mob of people. He was sitting down flat on his ass while a man charged him and pointed a gun point blank at his head, and Kyle gave him a chance to retreat. And did not shoot numerous other people, who did retreat.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is clear, implicit bias by left wing media by intentionally omitting information they most certainly had access to. I can only assume this was done with the intent of riling up the American public for profit, and quite potentially in hopes of stirring more civil unrest and riots in the wake of whatever outcome was to come of this highly charged and politicized trial. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is absolutely disgusting, and an egregious misuse of the public ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：期望移民学习他们所移民的国家的主流语言，至少在他们打算留下来的情况下，这不是不合理的，也不是种族中心主义。]]></title><description><![CDATA[直到两年前，我一直住在德国的一个社区，那里有很多土耳其和俄罗斯移民。
土耳其和俄罗斯移民。

他们中的大多数人都是非常好的人。不管他们的语言能力如何。

但我不明白为什么有人会在外国生活10多年
(甚至是第二代)而不...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzkc84/cmv_its_not_unreasonable_or_ethnocentric_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzkc84/cmv_its_not_unreasonable_or_ethnocentric_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 14:30:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until two years Ago I used to live in a neighborhood in Germany with a lot of Turkish and Russian immigrants. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of them are very nice people. Regardless of their language skills. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I don&amp;#39;t get why someone would live in a foreign country for 10 plus years (or even in second generation) and not be able to communicate with more than a handful of broken words. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was told that this view would be ethnocentric or that I am a literal nazi because of it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not suggesting anyone changing their culture or religion or that speaking foreign languages should not be allowed. I just think communication is key to successfully building a community and just for obvious practical reasons the people who moved into a country should be those who have to learn the new language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：强迫教师在签名中加入代名词并不能帮助变性人]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是变性人，我把一个人是否在签名中使用他们的代名词作为他们是否安全出柜的标志。
签名，作为判断他们是否可以安全出柜的标志。那些没有
签名中没有代名词的人并不能保证他们有变性恐惧症，但是
如果没有额外的背景和信息，是无法判断的......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzane6/cmv_forcing_teachers_to_put_pronouns_in_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzane6/cmv_forcing_teachers_to_put_pronouns_in_their/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 11:39:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m trans and I use whether or not someone have their pronouns in their signature as a sign of if they&amp;#39;re safe to come out to or not. People that don&amp;#39;t have their pronouns in their signature aren&amp;#39;t guaranteed to be transphobic, but it&amp;#39;s impossible to tell without additional context and information about that person whether or not they&amp;#39;re safe to come out to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This system only works when people choose to have their pronouns in their signature. In cases where it&amp;#39;s mandated there&amp;#39;s no telling who is a safe person to come out to and that may just lead to us misgendered and deadnamed in all our courses because it&amp;#39;d be too risky to come out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s no benefit in mandating it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：核电是世界上最好的能源，它的坏名声来自于人为错误]]></title><description><![CDATA[核能得到了一些坏消息，但大多数是没有根据的。核能
不幸的是，核能在过去遭遇了一些相当大的公关灾难
(切尔诺贝利、福岛等），这可以理解为动摇了公众对其安全的信任。
其安全性的信任。尽管它的声誉不好，但核能一直是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzf123/cmv_nuclear_power_is_the_best_source_of_energy_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qzf123/cmv_nuclear_power_is_the_best_source_of_energy_in/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 09:41:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nuclear energy gets some bad press, but most of this is unfounded. Nuclear energy has unfortunately suffered some pretty large PR disasters in the past (Chernobyl, Fukushima etc) and this has understandably shaken public trust in its safety. Despite its bad rep, nuclear energy has consistently been shown to be orders of magnitude safer than most other methods of electricity generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chernobyl had too much red tape. Fukushima was built on a fault line. The third was almost a disaster. Need I say more?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ourworldindata.org/grapher/death-rates-from-energy-production-per-twh&quot;&gt;Studies &lt;/a&gt; have shown that nuclear energy causes just 0.07 deaths for every tera-watt hour of electricity generated. This is in comparison with 2.82 for gas, 18.43 for oil and 32.72 for coal. Nuclear power plants do not release any carbon dioxide during the course of energy generation and even accounting for CO2 emissions during construction, the emissions associated with nuclear energy are still 50 times lower than those associated with coal power and 30 times lower than those associated with coal mining and natural gas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One often overlooked aspect of the pollution released by coal power is that ash released from burning coal often contains highly concentrated levels of thorium and urainium. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/coal-ash-is-more-radioactive-than-nuclear-waste/&quot;&gt;Studies &lt;/a&gt; have shown that exposure to the elevated levels of radioactive material present in coal ash has the result that people living in the vicinity of coal power stations experience radiation doses up to 200% greater than those living close by to nuclear power plants. Bizarrely enough, the radioactive waste produced by burning coal is actually more radioactive than the waste from nuclear power and yet there are no restrictions on coal ash simply being released into the atmosphere. Nuclear energy is a low carbon, low risk method of energy generation and has an essential part to play in the battle against climate change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hydro and Wind can&amp;#39;t run entire countries without a really large supply of either. At best, they simply lower costs overall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV："如果瑞特豪斯是黑人，就不会发生这样的事情"，这不是反对他的论点，而是系统改革的论点。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到这么多评论把他的种族归结为他被释放的原因，但如果你
但如果你真的看清楚了一切，那就是因为数据的问题：他没有违反任何
法律。

因此，虽然我同意这是一个糟糕的情况，而且事情的发展是一个悲剧。
是一个悲剧，但他仍然被追究责任的程度......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qz72s0/cmv_if_rittenhouse_was_black_this_wouldnt_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qz72s0/cmv_if_rittenhouse_was_black_this_wouldnt_of/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:06:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see so many comments bring his race into the reason he got off, but if you really look at everything it’s because down to the data: he didn’t break any laws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So while I agree it was a bad situation to be in, and that how things played out is a tragedy, he still was held accountable to the extent the law demanded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means that if the case would have ended differently for a black teen, then the issue isn’t with Rittenhouse’s actions, but racial bias AGAINST black people, not FOR white people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suggest there’s a major difference of “lawful compliance” being a reason someone didn’t get charged, and racism the reason someone else did get charged. And blurring those lines only confuses the goal of equality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：每个人都有权要求别人使用某些代名词来指代自己，但其他人也有权拒绝这一要求。]]></title><description><![CDATA[编辑：为了澄清，我指的是法律上的权利。

只要请求或拒绝都不会导致或要求对以下人员造成身体伤害
严格来说，这两者都是社会契约的问题，并不属于 "法律 "范畴。
法律的范畴之外。

个人解释：一个合理的人应该尽力...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qywcv2/cmv_everyone_has_the_right_to_request_that_others/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qywcv2/cmv_everyone_has_the_right_to_request_that_others/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 16:54:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Edit: to clarify, I&amp;#39;m referring to the &lt;em&gt;LEGAL&lt;/em&gt; right. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as neither request nor refusal results in or calls for physical harm to either party, both are strictly matters of social contract, and fall outside the purview of law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal interpretation: a reasonable person should try their best to accommodate such a request (and broadcasting such a request via LinkedIn profile or email signature is useful guidance to avoid hurting each other&amp;#39;s feelings), but if they forget or slip up, that can&amp;#39;t be illegal. At the same time, if someone refuses such a request, that is their right, but they should accept the consequences of being perceived as bigoted and/or derogatory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gray area: explicit refusal to use requested pronouns in such a way as to intentionally cause psychological harm. To me this is hate speech, which although constitutionally legal, should carry heavy social stigma (similar to using a racial slur).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我相信Tik Tok上的医生，就像相信菲尔医生、奥兹医生或任何电视明星医生一样；要有一粒盐。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的女朋友已经开始在Tik Tok上关注那些自称是医生的人。
她开始告诉我一些事情，比如 "你知道妇女在产后不提供任何止痛药吗？
你知道妇女在分娩后没有任何止痛药吗？"。这听起来很荒唐，所以我
所以我问她从哪里知道的。我告诉她，任何医生...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qyum3l/cmv_i_trust_a_doctor_on_tik_tok_as_much_as_doctor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/qyum3l/cmv_i_trust_a_doctor_on_tik_tok_as_much_as_doctor/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 16:54:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My girlfriend has started following people who claim to be doctors on Tik Tok. She’s started telling me things like “did you know women aren’t provided any kind of pain medication after giving birth?”. That just sounds ridiculous, so I asked her where she learned it from. I told her any doctor that is making Tik Tok videos should always be questioned. I related it to celebrity doctors like Dr. Oz. Who in my eyes aren’t trusty worthy. Also a quick google search found that U of M study, conducted by Dr. Alex Friedman Peahle, M.D., focused on women with private health insurance across America and found that among those who had a C-section, 76% would be prescribed an opioid. For vaginal l births, the figure was 27%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>