<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 04:33:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：壓制COVID反疫苗者等並不是打擊錯誤信息的正確方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[在看到許多子版塊被私有化，試圖迫使Reddit的手，以便
他們禁止諸如NoNewNormal和其他這類社區的分站，這讓我開始
這讓我開始思考我們如何對待有這些爭議性觀點的人和社區。
觀點，Reddit對回聲室一直都很糟糕，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pfbcp1/cmv_silencing_covid_antivaxxers_etc_isnt_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pfbcp1/cmv_silencing_covid_antivaxxers_etc_isnt_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After seeing many subreddits go private in an attempt to force Reddit&amp;#39;s hand so they ban subs such as NoNewNormal and other such communities, it&amp;#39;s made me start to think about how we treat people and communities with these controversial view points, Reddit has always been bad for echo-chambers, however despite that, I think one of the main appeals of the platform for me personally has been the opportunity to see opposing viewpoints and have proper critical discussions that you can&amp;#39;t really get elsewhere, right now everyone&amp;#39;s very much in a Us vs. Them mindset, and if we start silencing communities that spout out misinformation, I&amp;#39;m not entirely sure we&amp;#39;re going to help the problem but rather make it much much worse as people start to internalize their belief that they&amp;#39;re being silenced and further believe in what they believe in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, I guess what I&amp;#39;m trying to say is that to combat misinformation, just shutting it down at this stage does more harm than good, Reddit has always been a free platform, albeit recently it has changed dramatically and it seems the admins pick and choose who gets silenced, but at the end of the day the people on these subreddits are just going to find another outlet, and push them further into the echo chamber, instead, surely we should just let everyone be, and discuss the issues fairly and critically whenever we can, I would love and welcome a good debate on this, and what exactly shutting these communities down will do in the long run?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I should also mention that important subreddits dedicated to discussing Covid are privating themselves for this exact reason, notably &lt;a href=&quot;/r/CoronavirusUK&quot;&gt;/r/CoronavirusUK&lt;/a&gt; have done this, and I&amp;#39;ve always used that sub to get all the important information I need about the state of the pandemic in my country, surely this is counter-intuitive and does more harm than good when it comes to misinformation??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 如果它能使你的生活變得更好，並且不會導致你傷害他人，那麼信教就是理性的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我認爲有太多關於上帝是否存在的文字了，而關於相信上帝是否合理的文字卻不夠多。
而關於相信上帝是否合理的文字卻不夠多。我打算
我打算在假設上帝不存在的情況下寫這篇文章，因爲我認爲這將
與普通的Reddit用戶產生更好的共鳴，儘管我並不...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pfamvb/cmv_if_it_makes_your_life_better_and_doesnt_cause/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pfamvb/cmv_if_it_makes_your_life_better_and_doesnt_cause/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:47:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think there are far too many words written about whether God exists and not enough written about whether it is rational to believe in God. I&amp;#39;m going to write this under the assumption that God doesn&amp;#39;t exist because I think that will resonate with the average Reddit user better though I don&amp;#39;t necessarily think that myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We engage in all sorts of useful fictions just because they make life easier. Like that &amp;quot;everything will turn out fine in the end&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;your vote counts.&amp;quot; These are things we all deep down know aren&amp;#39;t necessarily true but they are necessary lies to keep our society functional. We all know that our individual vote will basically have zero impact but we believe that it will have some because if everyone thought realistically, democracy wouldn&amp;#39;t work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think there are many situations in which the same logic can be applied to religion. Even if rationally you know you can&amp;#39;t prove a religion to be true, I think in a lot of cases it could still be useful to believe that it is true. While there are many religious groups that spread more hate than love, there are plenty to choose from that do just the opposite. I am not talking about those religions that are hateful in their message, because I don&amp;#39;t believe those are useful beliefs to have. On the Christian front there are organizations like the United Church of Canada who treat homosexual people as equals. Most North American Mahayana Buddhist groups have done away with any sort of discrimination against women or homosexual people as well. Sikh groups also have a tendency towards acceptance. Those are the types of groups I&amp;#39;m saying can be of use to be a part of and believe in. I think people on Reddit tend to forget that there are more religions than evangelical Protestantism, traditional Catholicism, and fundamentalist Islam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Religious people are statistically happier and are given a community and something to be a part of. Provided the right one is chosen, religion can encourage people to be more empathetic and loving. Some religious groups even mandate charity. Remember, I am only advocating for participation in religious groups that advocate empathy towards all, what I classify as useful beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that if believing in religion causes you to be happier and a better person, then that belief is rational. If you&amp;#39;re a materialist atheist you believe that we only have one chance at this life, is it not rational to spend it in the way that makes you happiest and causes you to increase the happiness of others? I don&amp;#39;t believe in some supreme value of truth above all else, I think sometimes belief in the irrational can be a great benefit. That isn&amp;#39;t to say that truth isn&amp;#39;t very important in many cases, just that sometimes fiction is more useful than truth. I think it&amp;#39;s time to stop asking whether belief in religion is rational, and time to start asking whether it is rational to believe. If we had proof of God, then faith would not be necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：史蒂夫-歐文經常對動物進行愚蠢的冒險，動物殺死他只是時間問題。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我首先要說的是，史蒂夫-歐文似乎是一個真正的好人
有一顆大心臟。他顯然熱愛動物，併爲保護動物奉獻了自己的一生。
它們。

這可以理解爲使他成爲大多數Redditors眼中的英雄。我並不是
試圖攻擊他這個人。他不應該被...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pey51f/cmv_steve_irwin_regularly_took_stupid_risks_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pey51f/cmv_steve_irwin_regularly_took_stupid_risks_with/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:47:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll start by saying that Steve Irwin seems like he was a genuinely nice guy with a big heart. He clearly loved animals and dedicated his life to protecting them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This has understandably made him a hero in the eyes of most Redditors. I&amp;#39;m not trying to attack him as a person. He didn&amp;#39;t deserve to get hurt, let alone killed. But I think his death serves as a cautionary tale about messing with wild animals, much like &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Timothy_Treadwell&quot;&gt;Timothy Treadwell&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I knew a lot of people working in conservation while Irwin was alive. They were all waiting with dread for the day one of his stunts would kill him. No one expected it to be a stingray - it&amp;#39;s extremely uncommon to be killed by one. But if someone was going to die by stingray, it was going to be the guy who regularly took insane risks with animals - that was the consensus when it happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently made a comment about this on &lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/Damnthatsinteresting/comments/pdaaez/of_course_steve_irwin_shreds_in_khaki_should_have/&quot;&gt;a video showing him draping an extremely venomous wild sea snake over his head, with the snake&amp;#39;s head resting on his eyelid&lt;/a&gt;. As I expected, I received a good dose of downvotes. I was told that deaths from stingrays are extremely rare. My counter to that was - if a person takes enough risks (big and small) with wild animals, eventually something will go wrong. Play with fire long enough and you&amp;#39;ll get burnt. I was told that stingray deaths are rare again. That conversation wasn&amp;#39;t going anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; surprising that it was a stingray that got him. It was more likely that he&amp;#39;d be killed by one of the more dangerous animals he regularly harassed. But anyone who knows wild animals knows that every animal that can defend itself is inherently dangerous - stingrays included. Irwin knew that too. Keep in mind, he wasn&amp;#39;t handling wild animals in a safe way, he was deliberately antagonizing them and taking unnecessary risks to create engaging content (like in the video linked above). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And let&amp;#39;s dig into the stingray thing for a moment. It was a short-tail stingray, which are generally docile. So what made this one attack Irwin? I&amp;#39;ve helped free short-tail stingrays from fishing nets before, and when they feel threatened they&amp;#39;re anything but docile. Another good way to make an animal feel threatened is to sneak up above and behind it. Or to corner it between people. Irwin would have known that too. But, according to Irwin&amp;#39;s cameraman, he did both of those things. And, while threatening the stingray, he positioned himself  in a way that put his exposed chest and abdomen within striking distance. No one should ever be doing that. It would be surprising if it wasn&amp;#39;t consistent with his modus operandi: putting himself in harm&amp;#39;s way to make exciting TV. The cameraman was told to keep filming if he was attacked, no matter how viciously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But let&amp;#39;s say, hypothetically, that he did &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt; right in that situation, my original point stands: dealing wild animals is like Russian Roulette. There are a lot of chambers, and you start with only one bullet. When you antagonize an animal, you add more bullets. Even more if they&amp;#39;re usually dangerous, and more again if you get in their space. But you only need one bullet to lose Russian Roulette. And he loaded a lot of bullets that really didn&amp;#39;t need to be there. Over and over and over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Irwin liked to downplay the danger of wild animals and I think he genuinely believed it to a degree. It&amp;#39;s a dangerous attitude and it&amp;#39;s stupid. Irwin should have known better. But he kept pulling the trigger, and eventually he lost the game. CMV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My sources are the Wikipedia articles on &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Steve_Irwin&quot;&gt;Steve Irwin&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stingray_injury&quot;&gt;stingray injuries&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Short-tail_stingray&quot;&gt;short-tail stingrays&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20140310154552/http://www.independent.co.uk/news/people/news/steve-irwins-final-words-cameraman-present-at-death-opens-up-about-deadly-stingray-attack-for-the-first-time-9181077.html&quot;&gt;this interview with the cameraman&lt;/a&gt; cited in some of those articles, and many hours of watching &lt;em&gt;The Crocodile Hunter&lt;/em&gt; when I was young.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought about posting this in &lt;a href=&quot;/r/unpopularopinion&quot;&gt;r/unpopularopinion&lt;/a&gt; but I really want to understand why most people on Reddit seem to disagree with me. It can&amp;#39;t just be that people don&amp;#39;t want to acknowledge the faults of their hero, can it? I love it when something makes me change my mind. Please tell me what I&amp;#39;m missing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Edit&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I&amp;#39;m not asking you to convince me stingray deaths are absurdly rare. I already know.&lt;/strong&gt; I knew how rare they were before I posted this. I knew before he died. I&amp;#39;ve acknowledged it in my post several times, and explained why that argument doesn&amp;#39;t hold much weight. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/comments/pey51f/cmv_steve_irwin_regularly_took_stupid_risks_with/hb0skg2?context=3&quot;&gt;I&amp;#39;ve said a bit more about it in this comment&lt;/a&gt;. I have experience with this species that I&amp;#39;m betting few here have ever had. The fact that he was killed by such an unlikely animal only further emphasizes my point about how the risks he took.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your point is just some version of &amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s extremely rare&amp;quot; without at least addressing some of the counterpoints I&amp;#39;ve made, you can&amp;#39;t expect to CMV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Edit 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve posted what I think it&amp;#39;s a well-written argument that&amp;#39;s generated a significant amount of comments. I feel like I&amp;#39;m being amicable, articulate, and open minded. My views might be wrong, that&amp;#39;s why I&amp;#39;m here. But it seems people are downvoting this post because they disagree with me. That really doesn&amp;#39;t help CMV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 3. I fixed a typo. The downvotes seem to have slowed right down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: r/AITA是一個讓人們的決定得到驗證的地方，不管他們是否是真正的混蛋。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到的90%的AITA帖子都是人們在發表道德上有問題的決定/行動。
的決定/行動，然後因爲這些行動而被奉承。

我看到很少有帖子真正指出發帖人的行爲，甚至更少的帖子試圖看到衝突的雙方。
試圖看到衝突的雙方的帖子就更少了。

更有甚者，一些人的行爲的後果......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pf7x1g/cmv_raita_is_a_place_for_people_to_get_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pf7x1g/cmv_raita_is_a_place_for_people_to_get_their/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:47:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;90% of the AITA posts I see are people posting morally questionable decisions/actions, then getting fawned over for those actions.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see few posts that actually call out the poster for their actions, and even fewer that try to see both sides of a conflict.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even more, the consequences of some of these actions are out of balance to the offense, the response is out of proportion, and often times refuses to realistically fix an issue.  The entire point is to assign blame and make OP feel better about themselves.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since it&amp;#39;s not trying to see past &amp;quot;OP good, everyone else bad,&amp;quot; it is actively harmful.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：法律/法規的宗教豁免不應成爲一種事物]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我看來，宗教豁免可以歸結爲："如果你有一個堅定的信念，那就是
如果你有堅定的信念，認爲你不應該遵守這個規則，那麼你就不必
遵循該規則"。但是，只有當你屬於一個預先批准的羣體，而這些人
他們也強烈認爲他們不應該遵守該規則。

I...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pemlsq/cmv_religious_exemptions_to_lawsregulations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pemlsq/cmv_religious_exemptions_to_lawsregulations/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 22:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I see it, religious exemptions boil down to, &amp;quot;If you have a firmly held belief that you should not have to follow this rule, then you don&amp;#39;t have to follow the rule.&amp;quot; But only if you belong to a pre-approved group of people who also feel strongly that they shouldn&amp;#39;t have to follow that rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see no practical difference between, &amp;quot;I really really don&amp;#39;t want to do that&amp;quot; and, &amp;quot;God says I don&amp;#39;t have to do that&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we as a society deem a rule important enough to make it a law, it should apply to everyone equally, regardless of whether or not they want to follow that law. And if we as a society feel like a proposed rule is not so important that absolutely everyone needs to follow it regardless of how they feel about it, then we should not make that rule into a law at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally, this is most commonly about vaccine hesitancy nowadays, but I think that religious exemptions across the board should be abolished. For example, I used to lifeguard at a pool where there were many patrons that practice Islam. Muslim women would come to the pool wearing ankle length flowing dresses, expecting to be able to swim. I lost track of the number of times that I had to tell them that swimming in a large piece of fabric that can wrap them up and limit their mobility in the water is too unsafe to be allowed, only for them to come back with, &amp;quot;But my religion says I have to wear this.&amp;quot; Well, then your religion also implies that you cannot swim in our pool.  (We did sell modesty swim suits, made of swim suit material, that were ankle length and wrist length, with a head covering. They were specifically designed to be safe to swim in while also covering all skin except hands, feet, and face. Some of the women did not feel like the closer (safer) fit of these modesty suits was modest enough to fit with their religious restrictions.) The rule about not wearing loose, flowy clothing while swimming is a safety rule important enough that everyone needs to follow it without exceptions. If it were determined that it&amp;#39;s not so important that there should be no exceptions, then the rule shouldn&amp;#39;t exist in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果你反疫苗是因爲你相信 "我的身體我做主"，那麼你也一定是支持選擇的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這一切都源於我一直從反疫苗陣營中聽到的這種反應，"我的身體
我的身體，我的選擇"，這聽起來非常像我們長期以來從支持選擇權運動中聽到的東西。
這聽起來非常像我們從支持選擇權運動中聽到的東西，已經有很長一段時間了。我認爲，如果你相信這句話
作爲反對接種疫苗的論據，你就有...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/percty/cmv_if_youre_antivax_because_you_believe_in_my/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/percty/cmv_if_youre_antivax_because_you_believe_in_my/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 22:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It all stems from this response I keep hearing from the anti-vax camp &amp;quot;my body my choice&amp;quot;, which sounds an awful lot like something we&amp;#39;ve been hearing from the pro-choice movement for a long time. I think that if you believe in that statement as an argument for being anti-vaccination that you have to also be pro-choice. There seems to be a large overlap of people who are anti-vax and evangelical (anti-abortion), which got me thinking...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only argument I&amp;#39;ve been able to come up with being against this line of thinking is that abortion effects a 3rd party (the fetus) where as a vaccination only effects the host. My argument would be that when you choose to not get vaccinated you&amp;#39;re choice doesn&amp;#39;t just effect you. Your choice has the potential to effect countless other people around you including death. If you infect someone with something you&amp;#39;re carrying and they die because of it I&amp;#39;d argue that you caused the death of that person. Sure you could argue it&amp;#39;s not a one-to-one thing and there&amp;#39;s a chance that you might not infect anyone, but ultimately it&amp;#39;s a choice you&amp;#39;re making that has the potential to effect a lot of people who didn&amp;#39;t have a choice in the matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, yeah, I don&amp;#39;t really see how you can be anti-vax and not also pro-choice. Change my view!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美國的教育/勞動系統已經崩潰。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我把教育和勞動結合在一起，因爲它們是相輔相成的。
教育的目的不僅是爲了教育下一代，使人們變得有知識
知識，而且也是爲了讓人們能夠獲得職業，過上有意義的生活。
因此，我將把這個問題分成三部分。

第1部分。K...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pem04k/cmv_the_educationlabor_system_in_the_united/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pem04k/cmv_the_educationlabor_system_in_the_united/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 20:39:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am combining Education and Labor as the same because they go hand in hand, the purpose of education is not only to teach the under generations so people become knowledgeable but also so that people can get careers and live productive lives. So I am going to split this into 3 parts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part 1. K-12&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The issue with the current system is that we teach based on age not based on ability. School should have 3 levels for each subject in each grade. Behind, normal and advanced. Each level should have tests that place a child and allow them to move up at ANY TIME. They should be able to request a test at any time, and all courses should have an online option for those who move faster then the class. If a child is able to test out of their grade they should imminently move up to the next level. Once they are done with all 12 (13) grades they are done with school and can go on to other things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part 2. Higher education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Higher education aka college/university is a terrible system, there are about 3 careers that I would say need University and that is Lawyers, Doctors, and Educators. Because those require a lot of text book learning that can&amp;#39;t be left to individual companies to teach. Other then that, everything else should be taught by the companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies and industries not only should teach their prospective employees though academies or training but they have an incentive to. If people have to go to no cost training/academies for employment you are much more likely to keep the employees you hire for their whole career since switching will be more time then its worth and they will start at a younger age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part 3. At Will Employment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At will employment is one of the biggest frauds committed against the American people ever. In 49 out of 50 states Employment at Will is the law. That means that a company can hire you and fire you for any reason (that is not protected) and you can quit for any reason at any time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hire at will, fire at will, quit at will sounds nice right? Nope that means...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;On call 24/7 oh it says you only have to work for specific hours and yes you do get over time, however if you refuse then they can fire you and you can&amp;#39;t do anything because fire at will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stagnant wages there is no incentive to give you a raise or hell even keep your pay the same because since you aren&amp;#39;t contract they can just fire you and no even give a reason and then hire a different person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;No reason fires you effectively don&amp;#39;t have any rights because they simply just have to make up a reason or say nothing at all and you are gone, try going to HR because of inappropriate or intentional bad behavior meant to try to get you to quit or just take advantage they can say bye.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arbitration the bullshit that removes the courts, that any private sector employee likely signed because of course they can force you to give it up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the law required contracts for employment that would mean that you could only get fired for either directly breaking code of conduct or failure to do your job correctly, and that you would have due process before being fired. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If they fire you for a dumb reason then you get damages, if the employee quits before term is they pay penalties. Basically the way the public sector works. Better pay/benefits (might be slightly lower pay but you get real benefits and pensions) Most have 20-25 year retirement with 60+% of your monthly way pension then you get Social Security check later in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ending at will employment is what must happen for labor standards to go up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit- Retirement savings plan is not a pension, a pension is no cost to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：小費文化是有毒的，需要被廢除]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們生活在一個社會中，如果你不給你的服務員或送貨司機小費。
你就會立即被打上有權、自私或無禮的烙印。有的服務員
威脅要在食物中吐痰或做手腳，故意提供糟糕的服務。
或者因爲不給小費而拒絕交付訂單......然而，我們作爲...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pelbp2/cmv_tipping_culture_is_toxic_and_needs_to_be_done/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pelbp2/cmv_tipping_culture_is_toxic_and_needs_to_be_done/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 17:37:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We live in a society where if you do not tip your server or delivery driver, you’re immediately branded as entitled, selfish, or rude. There are servers who threaten to spit in or tamper with food, intentionally provide terrible service, or refuse to deliver an order due to non-tipping…yet we as a society have decided that we are okay with this and fall into the pressure of tipping culture to avoid these issues. This is the only industry where workers essentially strong-arm the consumer to pay them extra money and threaten or ridicule them otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How is this okay? The truth of the matter is, if you can afford the cost of the meal and any delivery fees associated with it, you literally CAN afford to eat out per almost every restaurant in America’s policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美國總統應該有年齡限制。75歲。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我感到噁心的是，在過去的幾次選舉中，我們所有的選擇都是超級老的。
而且不能代表我們的縣。我認爲我們需要一些年輕的血液，大多數
人在65-70歲退休。爲什麼要讓他們來管理這個國家，因爲我們已經百分之百的
之前的總統已經開始了他們的認知能力下降......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pe6x4m/cmv_there_should_be_an_age_limit_for_us_president/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pe6x4m/cmv_there_should_be_an_age_limit_for_us_president/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 15:37:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m sick that all our choices the last few elections have all been super old, and not representative of our county.  I think we need some young blood, most people retire at 65-70.  Why should they be running the country, when we’ve 100% had presidents before that had started their cognitive decline while still holding the nuclear football?  I would almost rather at 28 year old in charge then someone that’s 80.  I also don’t think that Supreme Court judges should be appointed for life till either, but that’s another argument.  I’m not being ageist, and I think there’s a million other jobs older people can do, just not this.  I also would still think it would be good if their cabinet didn’t have a age range.  It’s good to hear from people with experience.  For the record, I’m 39, for disclosure.  Credit to &lt;a href=&quot;/u/Tony_Pizza_Guy&quot;&gt;u/Tony_Pizza_Guy&lt;/a&gt; for the idea.  Change my mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 以 "購買 "來推銷非永久性購買應該是非法的，而應該使用 "租賃 "等術語。]]></title><description><![CDATA[編輯：由於我可能沒有說清楚我的意思，所以我不是針對這些詞
詞，而是它們所表達的意思。我試着用一個
具體的例子。

一個常用的說法是 "在PLATFORM上獲得GAME"。

"在GOG Galaxy上獲得《運輸狂熱2》"意味着我可以得到這個遊戲和。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/peh7oq/cmv_it_should_be_illegal_to_market_nonpermanent/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/peh7oq/cmv_it_should_be_illegal_to_market_nonpermanent/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 14:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt; Since I probably wasn&amp;#39;t clear what I mean, I don&amp;#39;t target the words specifically, but the meaning they convey. I&amp;#39;ll try to explain by using a concrete example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A commonly used way of saying stuff is &amp;quot;Get GAME on PLATFORM&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Get Transport Fever 2 on GOG Galaxy&amp;quot; means I can get the game and play it forever, because GOG doesn&amp;#39;t apply DRM, so after the game is on your computer they have no control on what you do with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Get Transport Fever 2 on Steam&amp;quot; means I can get a license to play the game and play it as long as my Steam account is valid, I&amp;#39;m not VAC banned, etc etc etc.
Getting the game on GOG Galaxy means getting it forever, getting the game on Steam has the possibility that at one point I won&amp;#39;t be able to play it anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because of that, Steam saying &amp;quot;Get Transport Fever 2 on Steam&amp;quot; should be illegal (perhaps false advertising), because it could imply permanence (like in the case of GOG), even though the EULA doesn&amp;#39;t give that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is going more and more towards renting stuff rather than owning it, and it is doing so in a misleading way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such, I think that laws should be put in place such that &amp;quot;buying&amp;quot; something can only be used if, after the purchase, that &amp;quot;something&amp;quot;, with all the advertised features, can be used indefinitely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s take the example of the PlayStation 4. After buying the PS4, you can use the hardware forever. You can also play games you have on CD forever. However, you cannot play multiplayer games forever (if PSN goes away so goes multiplayer), and if your PlayStation account is banned (for example if you make a chargeback), you also lose all digital games you bought from the PlayStation Store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such, if Sony wants to advertise the PS4 as something you can buy, it should be illegal to make any reference to the ability to play games multiplayer, play digital games, or download stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similarly, it should be illegal for Sony to say that games obtained through the PlayStation Store can be &amp;quot;bought&amp;quot; or that they &amp;quot;sell&amp;quot; those games. Instead, Sony should only be allowed to say that you can rent those games through the PS Store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems unfair for Sony to be able to permanently erase all your games you bought online if you chargeback a fraudulent payment. Since the chance of preventing that is low, and since that&amp;#39;s not the only issue (once Sony shuts down the PlayStation Store for an old console, all online games are gone too), the distinction between something you buy and keep and something you rent and &lt;strong&gt;will&lt;/strong&gt; disappear at one point should be clearly advertised to consumers so they are at least informed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not just a Sony/PlayStation rant, but the easiest example and first that came to mind. Internet of Things (smart home) stuff is famously becoming paperweight if the company decides to no longer support the product, for example. As such, it seems unfair to advertise features that may be gone anytime as features of the product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I understand that products don&amp;#39;t last forever. For example, the PlayStation 4 or a smart lightbulb might break. However, in these situations, the lifetime of a product is longer than the guaranteed lifetime of stuff that should be labeled as &amp;quot;rented&amp;quot;. If my PS4 breaks, &lt;em&gt;c&amp;#39;est la vie&lt;/em&gt;, I can&amp;#39;t play games anymore, that&amp;#39;s to be expected. But if I &lt;strong&gt;buy&lt;/strong&gt; a game from PlayStation Store, I expect to be able to play it until my PS4 breaks, not until tomorrow (which is when Sony might arbitrarily decide to ban my PSN account and invalidate all my purchases).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And no, I don&amp;#39;t agree that pointing it out in the EULA is even remotely enough. &lt;em&gt;(In an unrelated note, I don&amp;#39;t think EULAs should be enforceable or legally binding if a company can&amp;#39;t prove the user properly read &lt;strong&gt;and understood&lt;/strong&gt; it. This particular opinion is mostly unrelated to the rest of this post, however, and even if you don&amp;#39;t agree with this last opinion, my point in the rest of this post still stands.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：散佈疫苗虛假信息的政客應承擔法律責任。]]></title><description><![CDATA[政治家被選來領導我們，特別是在重大事件中，如目前的大流行病。
目前的大流行病。無視專家的科學數據，告訴公民不要
要相信疫苗，這簡直是在殺人。這些人有影響力
在社會上和他們支持的立法中。我不是在說...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pe3f3c/cmv_politicians_spreading_vaccine_disinformation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pe3f3c/cmv_politicians_spreading_vaccine_disinformation/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:37:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Politicians are elected to lead us especially during major events like the current pandemic. Ignoring scientific data from experts and telling citizens not to trust vaccines is literally killing people. These people have influence socially and in the legislation they support. I’m not talking about your crazy uncle on Facebook. He’s not elected or in a position of leadership. I think politicians that give false medical advice that is refutable by science should face legal consequences. Knowingly giving someone an STD is illegal. Spreading false information from a place of leadership and enacting policies that aren’t supported by science needs to have consequences or they will keep doing it. Next time we might be dealing with a virus with much higher deaths rates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在採訪塔利班成員時，派一個女記者去採訪是沒有意義的。大家都已經知道塔利班不尊重婦女（這很可怕），但在一次重要的採訪中用一個婦女來對抗他們，只是爲了譁衆取寵而自我破壞。]]></title><description><![CDATA[隨着所有重要的新聞從阿富汗傳出，很多人都在急切地想知道在阿富汗的疏散狀況等信息。
很多人急切地想知道在喀布爾進行的疏散等活動的情況。
喀布爾的情況。

英國廣播公司（BBC）、美國廣播公司（ABC）、半島電視臺（Al-Jazeera）和其他電視臺都有女主播在當地採訪。
他們正試圖採訪塔利班領導人，以獲取關鍵信息。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdz4ll/cmv_when_interviewing_members_of_the_taliban_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdz4ll/cmv_when_interviewing_members_of_the_taliban_it/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 19:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;With all the important news coming out of Afghanistan, lots of people are desperate for information on the status of the evacuation, etc, going on in Kabul. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BBC, ABC, Al-Jazeera, and others, all have female lead reporters on the ground who are trying to interview Taliban leaders for critical information, and oftentimes the interview (with the goal of &lt;em&gt;getting critical information&lt;/em&gt;) ends up accomplishing nothing at all because the Taliban don&amp;#39;t respect them. Here is an example I saw this morning on Al Jazeera:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/RiYAmfb.png&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;I asked for information about the situation at the airport, and they refused to talk to me because I was a women and not dressed appropriately&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course they didn&amp;#39;t want to talk to you on camera. What did you expect? &lt;strong&gt;The Taliban don&amp;#39;t respect women.&lt;/strong&gt; We all know that. We all know that is wrong and bigoted. We have known that for decades, so why self sabotage an important information gathering activity by purposefully antagonizing the people you are trying to interview?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would be like sending a blind reporter to give an eye witness report for a newspaper. Or sending a deaf person to review a new music album. Or sending an Amish person who doesn&amp;#39;t use electricity to an press conference about new computer chip designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It just isn&amp;#39;t the right person to send for this one particular activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美國人真的需要坐上坐便器的火車了]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年，當衛生紙出現短缺時，我訂購了坐便器，而不是爲了爭奪紙張。
爭奪紙張。結果，我用的衛生紙少了，我的屁眼也乾淨多了。
我的屁眼也更乾淨了，而且我觸摸屁眼的次數比使用衛生紙時少得多。
紙。

淨身盆是一種優越的、可負擔得起的和更好的選擇...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdyqxj/cmv_americans_really_need_to_get_on_the_bidet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdyqxj/cmv_americans_really_need_to_get_on_the_bidet/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 18:46:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year when there was a run on toilet paper I ordered bidets instead of fighting over paper. As a result, I use less toilet paper, my butthole is much cleaner and I have to touch my butthole far less than when I was using toilet paper. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bidets are superior, affordable and the far better option for a country that can afford them. It&amp;#39;s fairly barbaric that we were cleaning our buttholes with our hands and a thin piece of paper. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Might also make teenage boys smell less like they were fisting their own assholes as well. Probably won&amp;#39;t solve the semen smell though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Just figured I&amp;#39;d add this edit. You&amp;#39;ll probably have an easier time convincing me of logistical issues or environment issues than whether or not it&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;cleaner&amp;#39;. Although you&amp;#39;re welcome to try to convince me it&amp;#39;s not clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：認爲宗教人士有妄想症是沒有錯的]]></title><description><![CDATA[我個人不相信任何宗教，我是由非常嚴重的
的基督教徒。我聽到的一些論點是："你無法證明上帝
是不真實的。" 好吧，我也不能證明牙仙不是真的，但這並不意味着我
如果你相信它是真實的，我就不能認爲你有妄想症。這就像宗教...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdx5hb/cmv_it_is_not_wrong_to_think_religious_people_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdx5hb/cmv_it_is_not_wrong_to_think_religious_people_are/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 17:32:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Personally I do not believe in any religion I was raised by very heavy christians however. Some of the arguments I heard was &amp;quot; you can&amp;#39;t prove god isn&amp;#39;t real.&amp;quot; Well I can&amp;#39;t prove the tooth fairy isn&amp;#39;t real either doesn&amp;#39;t mean I can&amp;#39;t think you&amp;#39;re delusional if you believe it is. It&amp;#39;s like religious people have to completely shut down their brains to continue believing at this point which is nearly identical to a cult. Religion meets the definition of a cult by every definition I can find. Just because the majority people are in some cult doesn&amp;#39;t mean it&amp;#39;s not a cult. &amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s funny how the right religion is always the one you grew up with. &amp;quot; That is such a true statement I really don&amp;#39;t see how anyone can believe knowing all that without being mentally delusional. Truthfully religion seems like a very primitive practice that makes very little sense in modern society and should be classified as a delusion or a mental disorder in the DSM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 如果一個男人發現他不是父親，就不應該指望他留下來。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在看到這麼多不同的Reddit帖子，其中有以下的故事和迴應的評論。
的故事和迴應的評論，我不確定我是否是那個被這種問題困擾的人。
關於這種問題的屁股。

男子養育孩子

發現女人出軌，謊稱自己是父親

男子問該怎麼做

Reddit Hivemind說...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdv8vz/cmv_if_a_man_discovers_he_is_not_the_father_he/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdv8vz/cmv_if_a_man_discovers_he_is_not_the_father_he/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 15:34:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After seeing so many different Reddit Post about stories with the below as the story and the comments in response, I am not sure if I am the one who is being the butt about this kind of issue.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Man raises child&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Discovers woman cheated, lied about paternity&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Man asks what to do&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Reddit Hivemind says he should remain in the child&amp;#39;s life.&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every time, no concerns about what the men must now feel about the child, often the fruit of the infidelity he only recently discovered, but that if he stops caring for said child, he is no longer a &amp;quot;Real Man. It is never said in those words, but that&amp;#39;s the feeling from it, some even saying things like a man should castrate himself if he can&amp;#39;t be a father to a child that isn&amp;#39;t his or if he leaves partway through.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shouldn&amp;#39;t a guy be able to leave? He did nothing wrong, the child isn&amp;#39;t his concern, or at least shouldn&amp;#39;t be if he no longer wishes to do so. That child has a chance to be raises by their real bio-dad or by someone else. But it has to be him, the betrayed, who MUST stay, or at least continue to be in the child&amp;#39;s life.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure, the child themselves didn&amp;#39;t do anything wrong, but that child is still a picture of the hurt, the pain, the cheating, the lies. But, he should swallow all of that because the child might grow up without him there.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In any other kind of relationship, this isn&amp;#39;t expected. If you are married to someone for ten years, then get ill and you find out that they cheated, maybe even that this illness is the reason of them cheating, you can and should still be able to leave that marriage, because why should you be tied to an agreement they didn&amp;#39;t keep? If you worked in a business that was supposed to be yours, but you find out that it wasn&amp;#39;t that it legally belongs to someone else, why on Earth should you be forced to stay, otherwise, you really didn&amp;#39;t care for the business?   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why should the time that passed matter? Why shouldn&amp;#39;t your next move be fore you and you alone? Why is it ok to tell a man that if he doesn&amp;#39;t care for the child that isn&amp;#39;t his, that he never really loved the child or that there is something wrong with him?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am I seeing this issue wrong somehow? Change my Views on this!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：自動禁止參與有爭議的子版塊的人，弊大於利]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛被一個我已經幾年沒有參與的子版塊禁言了
(/r/pokemongo)，因爲我在另一個我不積極參與的子紅上發表了一條評論。
積極參與的另一個子版塊（/r/conspiracy）發表了一條評論。我偶然路過/r/conspiracy，嘲笑了
的陰謀論。瞬間就被禁止了，因爲 "參與...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdr4hy/cmv_automated_banning_of_people_who_participate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdr4hy/cmv_automated_banning_of_people_who_participate/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 12:33:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just got banned from a subreddit I hadn&amp;#39;t participated in for several years (&lt;a href=&quot;/r/pokemongo&quot;&gt;/r/pokemongo&lt;/a&gt;) because I made a single comment in another subreddit I don&amp;#39;t actively participate in (&lt;a href=&quot;/r/conspiracy&quot;&gt;/r/conspiracy&lt;/a&gt;). I happened by &lt;a href=&quot;/r/conspiracy&quot;&gt;/r/conspiracy&lt;/a&gt; and mocked a covid conspiracy theory. Instantly banned for &amp;quot;participating in subreddits that spread covid misinformation&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel like if I was the kind of person they actually wanted to ban... this would only cause me to double down on my beliefs of censorship and fascism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What good is accomplished? Don&amp;#39;t these sort of actions only increase their confidence and passion, causing them to spend more time trying to spread their beliefs? Do they just care about their own subreddit and nothing else?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Thanks for the replies, folks. Deltas awarded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;#39;t realize &amp;quot;Do they just care about their own subreddit and nothing else?&amp;quot; was such a stupid question. But I agree now... it is... modding their own sub is all a mod typically cares about when modding their own sub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still think this is a bad practice that will only create more of the people it tries to remove, but they don&amp;#39;t really care if that happens as long as those people are outside their sub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: "自己做研究 "與社會成功的核心原因是對立的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們擁有今天的社會的主要原因可以歸結爲
歸功於人類可以將工作分門別類的事實。

在某種程度上（古希臘？ 我不知道），我們意識到不是每個人都需要知道所有的事情。
都需要知道每一件事。我們可以將工作專門化，在一個
某個領域的工作...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdjhk3/cmv_do_your_own_research_is_antithetical_to_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdjhk3/cmv_do_your_own_research_is_antithetical_to_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 06:39:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main reason that we have the society we have today can mainly be attributed to the fact that humans can compartmentalize work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At some point (Ancient Greece? Idk), we realized that not every single person needs to know every single thing. We can &lt;em&gt;specialize&lt;/em&gt; and have jobs in a particular space of knowledge, if we don&amp;#39;t &amp;#39;do our own research&amp;#39; and trust that the society will mitigate our other risks. This specialization of skills/knowledge gives rise to economy, social class, professional subcultures, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a short, limited example, the farmer doesn&amp;#39;t need to know how to or actually build or repair their own house. The builder doesn&amp;#39;t need to know how to or actually farm crops. They will exchange their services to each other to mitigate each other&amp;#39;s risk, allowing each of them to become better at their specialization. When you scale this example, you see how you now need an economy to be able to efficiently exchange work between mediums. It gives rise to social class as the ones with the most utility (doctor&amp;#39;s, politicians, judges, etc.) can curry the most favour in exchange for their work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note: We see this property being leveraged across multiple facets of nature (biological sex, multicellular organisms). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, society progressed much faster when we were able to centralize meaningfully differentiated skills and knowledge. Of course this does not mean that this system is immune to the typical challenges of centralization (lack of transparency, trust, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when I hear &amp;#39;do your own research&amp;#39;, my brain translates it to &amp;#39;There is a significant enough risk that this centralized knowledge/skill base is compromised, that I need to mitigate the primary risk myself&amp;#39;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is a fair thing to say, and act on for a lot of contexts (ie. Journalism/media on political events), but the implication above for such key systems such as healthcare or engineering, is the equivalent of basically trying to mitigate the risk of a total societal collapse/revolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is antithetical to, imo, one of the core reasons for society&amp;#39;s success and state today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果吸菸者可以拒絕酗酒者的肺部移植，並被拒絕肝臟移植，那麼拒絕接種疫苗的人（沒有正當的醫療理由）應該是最後一個獲得醫療牀的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[醫院是如此之滿，以至於人們進來後因其他原因而被拒絕治療。
醫療的東西。一名退伍軍人因闌尾炎而死亡，因爲病牀上擠滿了未接種Covid的病人。
未接種疫苗的科維德病人太多。夠了！夠了 我失去了對
我對那些冒着變異科維德的風險而接種疫苗的人失去了同情。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdon9h/cmv_if_smokers_can_be_refuse_lung_transplants_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdon9h/cmv_if_smokers_can_be_refuse_lung_transplants_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 05:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hospitals are so full that people are coming in and being denied care for other medical stuff. A veteran died because of an appendicitis because the beds were so full of unvaccinated Covid patients. Enough is enough! I lost sympathy for people who are risking a mutant covid that makes vaccinated people at risk of losing immunity. Shame on adults not getting vaccinated and getting sick children who can’t get vaccinated yet! Their choices hurt the rest of us, if they want freedom, they need to take responsibility! Last in line for a bed for unvaccinated people!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：網上辯論更好，因爲你不能打斷別人的書面文章]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個人擺出一張桌子和一個牌子，上面寫着 "支持生命，改變我的觀點"。隨着
隨着越來越多的人加入對話，人羣中的成員大喊 "性別歧視的豬"，"我的身體我的權利"，並且一般來說，他們的謾罵更加激烈。
身體是我的權利"，一般來說，他們的謾罵會更加激進。這場對話
辯論的目的是爲了真正改變一個人的想法，但它已經...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pddibd/cmv_debates_are_better_online_because_you_cant/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pddibd/cmv_debates_are_better_online_because_you_cant/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 02:00:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A person puts up a table and a sign that says “Pro Life, change my view”. As more people join the conversation, members of the crowd yell “sexist pig”, “my body my rights”, and generally get more aggressive with their heckling. The point of the debate was to truly change a persons mind, but it has now devolved into near physical altercation because two sides can’t agree to let the other side finish their sentences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This scene of debates goes back as old as ancient Greece all the way to modern democratic parliaments. Humans are simply too emotional to put them aside for the sake of truth seeking. Angers rise when words can no longer be found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Edit]: Thanks guys. What I like about this thread is that it both proved and disproved my argument. I learned a lot via online opinions but I also learned that online makes debates very disjointed and lose interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：大學招生的平權行動應該基於社會經濟地位，而不是種族。]]></title><description><![CDATA[標題。我以自己爲例來開始。我是倫比族印第安人
(Card-carrying)，因此，許多機構對我來說，大學是免費的。

問題是，我並不住在北卡羅來納州的羅伯遜縣，而我的大部分家人都住在那裏。
卡羅來納州的羅伯遜縣，我的大部分家人都住在那裏，而那裏的倫比人往往比白人更窮
倫比人往往比白人更窮......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pddz0n/cmv_affirmative_action_for_college_admissions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pddz0n/cmv_affirmative_action_for_college_admissions/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 18:45:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title. I&amp;#39;ll use myself as an example to start. I&amp;#39;m Lumbee Indian (card-carrying), and thus college is free for me from many instutions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The issue arises from the fact that I don&amp;#39;t live in Robeson County, North Carolina, where much of my family does, and where the Lumbee tend to be poorer than white people, on average. I live in Minnesota, am moderately well-off, and have never faced racial discrimination, (mostly because my dad is white and I got his genes.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I still get free college, despite my grades being average at best. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why I believe that college admissions shouldn&amp;#39;t look at you&amp;#39;re race, but at the wealth of your family. Race doesn&amp;#39;t generally cause people to get poor grades and test scores, but the wealth of their parents can. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A white kid with a single mother who works as a janitor, but has a 3.8 GOA and a 30 on the ACT would be more qualified for university than Malia Obama, if she had the same numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Race can be a factor, but it isn&amp;#39;t always a factor, and colleges should recognize that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果明確表示他們從來不想要孩子，就不應該強迫男人撫養他們的孩子]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個女人可以決定不做母親，並在受孕後承擔所有的責任。
在受孕後的所有責任。她們可以選擇（在我居住的地方）進行
墮胎或將他們的孩子送去收養。她們可以決定自己是否
想在受孕後成爲父母。男人則沒有選擇，在...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdcacs/cmv_men_should_not_be_forced_to_support_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdcacs/cmv_men_should_not_be_forced_to_support_their/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 17:30:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman can decide not to be a mother and have all the responsibilities that come with it after conception. They can choose (where i live) to have an abortion or put their kid up for adoption. They can decide whether or not they want to be a parent after conception. A man has no choice, after conception whether or not he wants to he could be made a father. My view is that if the man makes it clear to the woman that he does not want this baby (with ample time for the woman to consider her options) then he should not be forced to support the child. I think morally this should be a very black and white issue, if women can choose to be or not to be a parent after conception so should men. In the sense that they should not be compelled to support or acknowledge the babies existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果蚊子🦟滅絕，世界將變得更好--它們沒有任何有益的用途]]></title><description><![CDATA[夏天快結束了，幸好是蚊子季節的結束。每年
年過去了，我不得不在自己身上塗抹除蟲劑，以避免大量的叮咬，並且
天知道是什麼疾病。

蚊子存在於地球上，只是爲了成爲寄生蟲和傳播...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pd8kuo/cmv_the_world_would_be_better_off_if_mosquitoes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pd8kuo/cmv_the_world_would_be_better_off_if_mosquitoes/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 16:39:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s towards the end of summer and thankfully the end of mosquito season. Every year goes by and I have to slather myself in deet, to avoid tons of bites, and god knows what disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mosquitoes exist on planet earth, simply to be parasites and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/topics/outdoor/mosquito-borne/default.html&quot;&gt;spread disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And we’re talking things like West Nile Virus, Zika Virus, Malaria. Diseases that have life altering consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried reading the arguments of why they should exist: they feed bats and birds, they keep humans out of sensitive natural environments like the rainforests. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But humans are going into the rainforests anyway and chopping them down, so not much of a deterrent if you ask me. And surely there’s enough OTHER kinds of bugs that could feed bats and birds. I’d like for them to eat more spiders please.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway I’m convinced the world would be better off if mosquitos would just go extinct. Change my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV："朋友圈 "是一些地獄般的噩夢的概念絕對是荒謬的，坦率地說，爲它感到不安是不成熟的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我認爲被拒絕和其他人一樣糟糕，但這是你決定向你的朋友，特別是向你的朋友求愛時所承擔的風險。
當你決定對你的朋友，特別是你最好的朋友進行預付時，你要承擔風險。
最好的朋友。你知道當你這樣做時，有什麼在等着你。你應該知道
你是否能處理好與一個人做朋友的問題......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pd58lk/cmv_the_concept_of_the_friendzone_being_some/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pd58lk/cmv_the_concept_of_the_friendzone_being_some/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 09:41:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think getting rejected sucks just as much as the next person, but it’s the risk you take when you decide to make an advance on your friend, especially your best friend. You know what lies in wait for you when you do it. You should know whether or not you can handle being friends with someone who rejected you, or whether or not you can handle separating from them entirely if need be. If you’re unsure, err on the side of caution. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t have issue with people who understand the risks and decide to move forward anyway, I have issue with the people who do it, get rejected, and ostentatiously whine about it afterward because they’ve been put in the accursed “friendzone.” If it bothers you so much, why not be straightforward and tell them you need to break away from their friendship for some time (maybe even forever) instead of hiding behind an awkward mask while continuing to stick by their side with feelings you haven’t dealt with? Or better yet, do some self-reflection, grow up, and understand that your love for them is a testament to your enjoyment of their company, therefore you should be content with having at least their friendship. Don’t ruin a good platonic relationship by thinking it’s the end of the world to be put in the friendzone. The friendzone is a beautiful place, and if you give it a chance you’ll come to understand that it’s worth the temporary pain you get from rejection. Being friends is more important than (the idea of) being lovers, at least if you truly care about that person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：藍莓是最好的漿果。]]></title><description><![CDATA[多樣性

餡餅、果醬、冰沙、鬆餅等等，我想不出有哪種漿果的用途比不起眼的藍莓更多。
我想不出有哪種漿果的用途比卑微的藍莓更多。草莓的優勢在於
但你上次看到草莓鬆餅是什麼時候？I
我想沒有。我想小紅莓汁是相當不錯的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcz5to/cmv_blueberries_are_the_best_berry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcz5to/cmv_blueberries_are_the_best_berry/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 04:31:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Versatility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pies, jams, smoothies, muffins and more, I can&amp;#39;t think of a single berry with more uses than the humble blueberry. Strawberries do have the advantage of making a sick ice cream but when&amp;#39;s the last time you saw a strawberry muffin? I thought not. I suppose cranberry juice is pretty nice but I think blueberry smoothies offset that too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ease of use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some berries like strawberries require removing a green thing before they&amp;#39;re eaten and pretty much need to be cut up. Blueberries just need a quick rinse before they can be chomped down upon. Wanna eat just one blueberry? Have a quick, tiny snack! Wanna ingest a giant spoonful of blue and round goodness? Enjoy that as well! Blueberries work great with both a fork and a spoon too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best bush&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raspberry bushes are covered in spikes and are very scary in general. 0/5, not family friendly at all, my kids were very scared. Blueberry bushes, on the other hand, are inviting, gentle creatures. They are a bit more of a pain to take care of (I accidentally mowed a part of a baby one, oops), but I think the benefits make it well worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not gonna sit here and pretend that blueberries are the cheapest berry, they aren&amp;#39;t. But is that really what we should be looking at when it comes to price? A GT 1030 is cheap, but does that make it the best graphics card? Of course not. What really matters is price to performance, and on that front I don&amp;#39;t think you can fault the blueberry even slightly. Sure, it might cost a bit more per calorie but given all the aforementioned uses for the blueberry I think it&amp;#39;s well worth the price of admission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I think has been thoroughly demonstrated, the blueberry is the berry to reign superior over all other berries. I look forward to seeing what others have to say on the matter...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：企業應該使用滾動期來計算獎金/目標/配額，而不是任意的時期，因爲這造成了員工對數字的不正當刺激。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，例如，如果你是一個汽車經銷商的員工，你可能有一個目標
一個月賣出30輛車，如果你賣得更多，你會得到獎金，比如說每賣出30輛車就有500美元的獎金。
每輛車超過30輛，你會得到500美元的獎金。我相信這種事情鼓勵員工和
損害業務的方式行事，並且......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcqisj/cmv_businesses_should_use_rolling_periods_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcqisj/cmv_businesses_should_use_rolling_periods_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:44:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So for example, if you are an employee of a car dealership, you may have a goal to sell, say, 30 cars a month and if you sell more, you get a bonus of, say $500 per car above 30. I believe this kind of things encourages employees and customers to act in ways that are damaging to the business and that these  negative behaviors could be reduced if bonuses/quotas were instead calculated on a trailing rolling basis. So for example, in the above example you would get a daily bonus calculated by the formula: (Average cars sold per day for past 30 days - target cars sold per day)*$500. Yes, this is slightly more complicated, but in the days of automated tracking the added complexity is negligible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By going to this system, it would stop the employee from doing things like offering price discounts, etc. in order to game the numbers in an arbitrary accounting period provided the commission they lost from being negotiable on price was less than their volume bonus. It might also cause an employee to try to shift sales in to a later month if they were below the bonus quota (so they would have a better chance of making bonus next month) and risk losing the deal as a result of the delay. Furthermore, if customers knew they no longer could get pricing power by coming in on the last day of the month/year, they would stop trying and stop expecting a discount from doing so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have personally seen time and again, companies and individuals making horrible business decisions because they want to close deals or achieve certain goals within an arbitrary accounting period. Employees sloppily finishing a project by an arbitrary deadline, or cutting scope out of a job so they can book/complete it by a certain date. I once literally saw a team in my company find a BS reason to cut $30M of scope out of a job so they could get the contract signed by the end of the bonus period. Every time I see this, I think to myself that this most of this could be fixed by just having incentive structures that was based on trailing averages and not based arbitrary hard deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I acknowledge that the reason for using arbitrary accounting periods is also because reporting periods for public companies are also based on arbitrary periods, I feel that this is circular reasoning. If companies moved away from arbitrary accounting periods to using better thought out incentive periods, so might their investors take a longer view at financial results. I would also say that only a tiny fraction of companies are publicly traded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 用 "decimate "這個詞作爲 "destroy "的同義詞是可以的]]></title><description><![CDATA[當我們把12月稱爲第12個月時，沒有人不高興，儘管12月的字面意思是 "第十個月"。
字面意思是 "第十個月"。那麼，爲什麼其他人會對
"decimate "被用來描述已經被消滅到很厲害的東西
程度？

語言隨着時間而變化。例如，"鹿 "這個詞曾經...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcvcn5/cmv_its_ok_to_use_the_word_decimate_as_a_synonym/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcvcn5/cmv_its_ok_to_use_the_word_decimate_as_a_synonym/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:44:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one gets upset when we call December the 12th month even tho December literally means &amp;quot;tenth month&amp;quot;. So why do others get so pissed off over &amp;quot;decimate&amp;quot; being used to describe something that has been vanquished to a great degree?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Language changes over time. The word &amp;quot;deer&amp;quot; for instance once referred to any kind of animal. Then it narrowed to just one.  The word &amp;quot;silly&amp;quot; once had the definition of &amp;quot;innocent&amp;quot;. The word &amp;quot;loft&amp;quot; once referred to the sky (and &amp;quot;heavens&amp;quot; in the plural also could be substituted for such).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stop being smug bastards and accept that &amp;quot;decimate&amp;quot; is perfectly fine when someone says &amp;quot;Did you see the game last night? The Raiders got decimated!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：年輕人最好能發生輕微的（但足夠痛苦的）傷害，這樣他們就能更好地掌握死亡率。]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近看到很多年輕司機像瘋子一樣在交通中開車的視頻。
瘋了一樣在交通中行駛，其中很多都以火爆的、有時是致命的車禍而告終。作爲一個
15歲時由於自己的愚蠢而被卡車撞倒，這讓我更加意識到
事實上，只要發生一次事故就能徹底...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcl3rj/cmv_its_desirable_for_youth_to_incur_minor_but/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcl3rj/cmv_its_desirable_for_youth_to_incur_minor_but/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:44:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Been seeing a lot of videos lately of younger drivers driving like lunatics thru traffic, a lot of them ending in fiery, sometimes deadly crashes.  As someone who was hit by a truck at 15 due to my own stupidity, it made me much more aware of the fact that it only takes one accident to thoroughly fuck your world up.  I feel like if more kids experienced even a fraction of the pain and suffering I did (or anyone who has been in a serious accident) they would have an entirely different approach when it came to behavior that had the potential for serious injury/death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我看到很多人在reddit上談論twitter如何糟糕，但我也看到twitter的截圖經常被張貼出來，並得到大量的支持。我開始認爲，人們不喜歡的其實不是twitter，而是有不同觀點的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[每當討論到twitter的時候，人們似乎都非常討厭那個
網站。然而，現在首頁上有幾條推文，更不用說
更不用說專門關於發佈twitter截圖的subreddits了。我不
我不經常使用twitter，所以我很困惑，人們在...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcrynf/cmv_i_see_lots_of_people_on_reddit_talk_about_how/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcrynf/cmv_i_see_lots_of_people_on_reddit_talk_about_how/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 21:31:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whenever discussions about twitter comes up, people seem to absolutely hate that site. And yet, there are several tweets on the front page right now, not to mention the subreddits specifically about posting twitter screenshots. I don&amp;#39;t use twitter frequently, so I&amp;#39;m confused about what people on reddit mean when they say twitter is awful. Sure, it&amp;#39;s possible that there&amp;#39;s two different groups of people who like or dislike twitter, but then you&amp;#39;d think only one of either criticisms of twitter or twitter screenshots would be highly upvoted, not both.  Is it twitter occasionally having a good content thing, and being bad the rest of the times?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：把雞蛋放在碗邊而不是放在臺面上，是完全可以的，甚至是更好的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在YouTube上看了很多烹飪視頻，似乎廚師們總是在臺面上打雞蛋。
似乎廚師們總是在臺面上打雞蛋，而且有些人會直接說這是正確的方法。
這是正確的方法。也許他們的做法與我的做法不同，但
但我每次嘗試都會得到一個更糟糕的結果。

櫃檯裂縫。我得到一個...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcpxvu/cmv_its_perfectly_fine_better_even_to_crack_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcpxvu/cmv_its_perfectly_fine_better_even_to_crack_an/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 19:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I watch a lot of cooking videos on YouTube, and it seems that the chefs always crack their eggs on the countertop, and some will come right out and say that it&amp;#39;s the right way. Maybe they&amp;#39;re doing it differently from how I do it, but every time I try I get a worse result. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Counter crack: I get a flattening of the round surface, maybe it goes concave instead of convex, with some spider-web cracks emanating from the point of impact. I still have to pierce the egg with my thumb, usually making contact with the white. Often the membrane underneath the shell is still intact. When I do get the shell apart, it is often uneven, which if I&amp;#39;m trying to separate the white and yolk using the &amp;quot;back-and-forth&amp;quot; method, is less useful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bowl crack: the edge of the bowl cuts into the egg, leaving a gash at the point of impact. If the break is insufficient, I can go back for another shot. At that point I can turn the egg so the break is at the top, letting the white move down so that I touch little or no white when I complete the crack. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what am I not seeing that makes cracking them on the counter better?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：孩子們長大後對他們的父母完全沒有義務。]]></title><description><![CDATA[很多父母[尤其是在亞洲文化中（我是亞洲人）]，父母期望他們的子女在他們年老時能照顧他們，並拋出藉口。
他們的子女在他們年老的時候要照顧他們，並拋出各種藉口
諸如 "我們爲你遮風擋雨，讓你喫飽穿暖，所以你需要在我們年老時做同樣的事。
我們老了也要這樣做。"

是的，我絕對不相信，....]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pclw4n/cmv_children_have_absolutely_no_obligation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pclw4n/cmv_children_have_absolutely_no_obligation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 15:39:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of parents [especially in Asian culture (I am Asian)] where parents expect their children to take care of them when they are old, and throw around excuses such as “We sheltered you, fed you, clothed you, so you need to do the same when we are older.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yea I absolutely do not believe in that. I’m referring to all kinds of parents. Children aren’t obligated to take care of them in old age. 
Even if you  did a good job as a parent and treat your children well, your children aren’t obligated to take care of you. Parents decide to bring children into this world, they have no say in this, so if they choose to not take care of you when you are older, then you can’t blame them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m mostly trying to talk about toxic and abusive parents where they treat their children like shit and expect to be treated well in return. Fuck that. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why I even posted this CMV is because there are actually some people in the world who believe that “&lt;em&gt;you need to take care of parents regardless of how they treated you / brought you up&lt;/em&gt;” and to me that is a BS fallacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV："呼籲 "Reddit刪除公然的錯誤信息，這只是在爲N8的賬戶添磚加瓦而已。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit作爲一個整體，傾向於允許有爭議的甚至是完全不正確的
信息在這個網站上。這一點在以下子版塊中得到了一次又一次的證明
如Sino，它認爲/相信天安門大屠殺從未發生。
這可以說是很危險的，因爲這又給了他們更多的彈藥。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcjmrq/cmv_calling_upon_reddit_to_delete_blatant/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcjmrq/cmv_calling_upon_reddit_to_delete_blatant/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 15:39:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit as a whole tends to allow controversial or even downright incorrect information on this site. This is demonstrated time and time again within subreddits such as sino, which argues/believes tianmen massacre never happened. This is arguably dangerous as well as it gives them more ammo again the USA being against China and creating lies to hurt them. While I completely disagree with antivaxxers and think vaccines are both safe and important, just like any social media there will be people who disagree with you. The information they post is no different to Facebook or Instagram or even tiktok. Is Reddit allowing them to broadcast it more? Of course, but Reddit is not exactly breeding this misinformation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The misinformation is killing people but that is not the fault of Reddit. It is the fault of those who choose to believe it despite the overwhelming scientific evidence that proves what they fear most; the vaccine is effective and safe. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Reddit does step in and remove these subreddits they are only beginning the process of converting Reddit into an echo chamber/circle jerk social media. It is not nor should it be Reddit’s responsibility to protect antivaxxers from their own information. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand this is a controversial take but I struggle with understanding why some subreddits with blatant and somewhat harmful misinformation are allowed to stay and other subreddits cannot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：安樂死的輔助自殺應該是合法的（我知道我不會拼寫）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果一個人患有嚴重的精神或身體疾病，並且不能過上幸福的生活
如果一個人患有嚴重的精神或身體疾病，不能過上幸福的生活，他們應該選擇和平的輔助自殺，他們自己的條件。
讓這些人活着是很自私的，唯一反對的人是那些從未見過這些人的人。
反對的人是那些從來沒有見過這些人的人，或者是......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcba0l/cmv_assisted_suicide_by_euthanasia_should_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcba0l/cmv_assisted_suicide_by_euthanasia_should_be/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 11:32:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;if a person is suffering from a serious mental or physical illness and cant live a happy life they should have the choice of peaceful assisted suicide  their own terms. its selfish to keep these people alive and the only people who are against it are people who have never met these people before or people who have never wanted to commit suicide. this also includes depressed people who got help but it dident work. life just isent for everyone a lot of people are alone their entire lives and im not talking about the fake &amp;quot;covid loneliness&amp;quot; im talking about actual loneliness and no one should deal with that for 60 plus years&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：Onlyfans並不是因爲色情內容而令人厭惡，而是因爲一些用戶通過提供 "消息 "服務來剝削孤獨的男人，從而創造出一種不健康的寄生社會關係。]]></title><description><![CDATA[據我所知，說寄生社會關係並沒有什麼爭議
是破壞性的。
[https://www.pbs.org/wgbh/nova/article/parasocial-relationships/]

這些關係往往採取名人崇拜或極端迷信的形式。
其中一個人將會迷戀上一個公衆人物......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcfkev/cmv_onlyfans_is_not_distasteful_because_of_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcfkev/cmv_onlyfans_is_not_distasteful_because_of_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 10:33:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As far as I know, it&amp;#39;s not controversial to say that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pbs.org/wgbh/nova/article/parasocial-relationships/&quot;&gt;parasocial relationships are destructive.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These relationships often take the form of celebrity worship or extreme fandom, wherein a person will become obsessed with a public figure to an unhealthy degree. This causes them to neglect and eventually completely ignore other aspects of their lives, especially their social lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my view, the OnlyFans messaging &amp;quot;services&amp;quot; are the worst form of parasocial relationships. It takes men who are already clearly suffering from extreme loneliness and sexlessness and sells them a bizarre fantasy wherein they have a &amp;quot;girlfriend experience&amp;quot; which is completely hollow and disingenuous. This causes them not only to neglect their relationships with people face to face, but it intertwines complex and deep-rooted feelings of loneliness and desire for love and sex. I imagine it&amp;#39;s a delicate &amp;quot;carrot and stick&amp;quot; dynamic where the idea of the girl actually caring about the subscriber must be dangled just out of reach in a perpetual manner in order to keep the money coming in. This is extremely destructive and this practice should be shamed in society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, it&amp;#39;s also bad when this happens digitally on Twitch, or in any other context. But at least in this case the relationship is more distant and clearly less &amp;quot;personal&amp;quot;, since there are dozens or even hundreds of other lonely men who are vying for a girl&amp;#39;s attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, it&amp;#39;s also bad when &amp;quot;sex workers&amp;quot; offer this service in reality, face to face - but at least it&amp;#39;s face to face. In that sense the men might at least incidentally pick up some social skills, even if the interaction is completely artificial. The digital, text-based aspect of the Onlyfans messaging services is about as distant as you can get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/confessions/comments/mazkok/onlyfans_girls_arent_personally_messaging_you/&quot;&gt;hard to confirm&lt;/a&gt;, but there&amp;#39;s also the idea that some of the users who offer these services &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/some-influencers-have-ghostwriters-to-respond-to-onlyfan-messages-2020-12&quot;&gt;aren&amp;#39;t even the ones the subscribers are talking to&lt;/a&gt;. They may be outsourcing/delegating this service to others, probably men. I can&amp;#39;t imagine what kind of intense psychological break might occur if one of these subscribers learned that this was going on. Can you imagine? They might even do &lt;em&gt;something really stupid&lt;/em&gt; in a fit of rage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made this post because I strangely never hear talk about this aspect of Onlyfans &amp;quot;culture&amp;quot;, which in my opinion is the most harmful. But maybe there&amp;#39;s a reason others don&amp;#39;t seem very concerned about it. Change my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：應該禁止酒店的強制性度假費。]]></title><description><![CDATA[度假村費是你在酒店開房時需要支付的額外費用。
理論上，你有權享受酒店提供的某些設施。我認爲這種
我認爲這種費用應該被禁止，因爲它是一種誘餌和轉換策略，任何強制性費用
任何強制性費用都應該包含在所有的廣告價格中。我是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcbc52/cmv_mandatory_resort_fees_at_hotels_should_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcbc52/cmv_mandatory_resort_fees_at_hotels_should_be/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 05:31:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Resort fees are an additional fee you are required to pay for a room at a hotel which in theory entitles you to certain amenities the hotel offers. I think this sort of fee should be banned as a bait and switch tactic, and any mandatory fee whatsoever should be built into all advertised prices. I am thinking of this along the lines of airline price regulations in the US, which require that advertised fares include all taxes and fees that are mandatory to travel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the fee is optional, then I think it&amp;#39;s fine to not include it in the price, much like a checked bag fee is not included in advertised prices. But a mandatory fee is just an increased room rate, and advertising a rate at a hotel of $X, when in fact the rate is $X+40 is just false advertising and should be banned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m reposting from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/comments/oi9ojb/cmv_mandatory_resort_fees_at_hotels_should_be/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, since none of the replies made any good points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：現在說民主是否是最好的政府形式可能還爲時尚早。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美國被看作是民主成功的典範，但實際上美國在大部分時間裏是非常不民主的。
在其大部分歷史中，美國是非常不民主的。事實上，婦女只能從
投票是在20世紀20年代。根據當地的政策，對誰可以投票有更多的限制。
政策。我們也都知道，早期的美國只有（白人）男性...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcd4u5/cmv_it_may_still_be_too_early_to_say_whether/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcd4u5/cmv_it_may_still_be_too_early_to_say_whether/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 04:36:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is looked as an example of a success of democracy, but US was actually very undemocratic for most of its history. In fact, women could only start voting in the 1920s. There were more limits on who could vote depending on local policy. As we all know also, early America only (white) male landowners could vote, and there was a slow democratization over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The US is not a pure democracy but it is democratizing more over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, most Western countries are relatively new to democracy as we know it today compared to the size of human history. Democracy as a concept was considered very early on. Historically, throughout much of human history it was treated with disdain because of the unrealibility of the averge voter. Aristotle for example thought that a better alternative would be an enlightened monarch or an enlightened aristocracy purely focused on studying and governing to improve the nation--I don&amp;#39;t prescribe to this view necessarily, this is an example of people&amp;#39;s views on democracy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 西方國家與沙特進行貿易並支持沙特，同時又聲稱要與恐怖主義開戰，這是一種虛僞的行爲。]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特阿拉伯是中東地區乃至全世界最大的恐怖主義資助者和支持者。
也可能是全世界的。他們創建了ISIS，並資助該恐怖組織。
沙特的錢資助了伊斯蘭國家，沙特公民爲他們大規模作戰，而
瓦哈比主義政府視而不見，因爲他們的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcd1ml/cmv_its_hypocritical_for_western_nations_to_trade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcd1ml/cmv_its_hypocritical_for_western_nations_to_trade/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 04:36:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia is the biggest funder and supporter of terrorism in the Middle east and likely around the world. They created ISIS and fund the terrorist group. Saudi Money funds the Islamic state, Saudi citizens fight for them in mass, and the Wahhabism government turns a blind eye because their ideology is almost identical to ISIS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How we can claim to be against terrorism yet economically and militarily support the most religiously radical state in the world is sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of punishments that Saudi Arabia and ISIS use. Lets see if you can tell the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Group 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by death- Blasphemy, Acts of Homosexuality, Treason, and Murder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Following is punishable by an undetermined number of lashes- Slander and Drinking Alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by death by stoning - Adulatory if married.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by 100 lashes- Adulatory if unmarried&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by cutting off ones right hand- Stealing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by cutting off one foot and one hand- Banditry theft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by death- Banditry murder and theft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Group 2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by death- Blasphemy, Acts of Homosexuality, Treason, and Murder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Following is punishable by 80 lashes- Slander and Drinking Alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by death by stoning - Adulatory if married.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by 100 lashes and exile for a year- Adulatory if unmarried&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by cutting off one hand- Stealing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by cutting off one foot and one hand- Banditry theft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by crucifixion- Banditry murder and theft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am leaving the name of which one is ISIS and which one is Saudi Arabia to make a point. Both are barbaric, murderous groups the only difference is one took over a state and got legitimately recognized. Removing all support from Saudi Arabia ends a lot of Terrorism because the money source would be cut off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：社交媒體正在毀掉我們這一代人]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一個20歲的男性，我認爲社交媒體對我們這一代人來說是弊大於利。
請聽我說。他們不教人包容，因爲有幾個種族被排除在外
因爲一些種族被排除在外，還有較瘦/正常的體型。他們幫助美化了
他們幫助美化性工作，並鼓勵性工作，這是有辱人格的......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcawwd/cmv_social_media_are_ruining_my_generation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcawwd/cmv_social_media_are_ruining_my_generation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 03:36:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a 20 years old male and I think social media are more bad than good for my generation, hear me out.
They don&amp;#39;t teach inclusivity cause several races are left out from the equation and also thinner/normal body types. 
They help glorify sex work  in an ill way and encourage it, which is degrading and has several mental effect on women and men of all ages.
They push women to be slutty to feel empowered confusing the two concepts and push men to be too masculine and to view women as objects and to not respect them. Also don&amp;#39;t get me started on the body dysmorphia.
Also reaserch show that seeing your friends always posting their best self on social media and comparing yourself to them makes u depressed and unsatisfied with your life, and no, the &amp;quot;remember social media is fake&amp;quot; trend is like pissing into a fire  trying to estinguish it, it does t solve the problem. 
the only thing they&amp;#39;re good is to keep in touch with poeple but the posting part is totally useless and it&amp;#39;s just a way to get validation for a generation that is willing to do the dumbest shit to get it. 
Also tik tok should be canceled. It is basically a p*do/horny guys/creeps dream come true where they can see underage girls dressing and acting in revealing &amp;quot;clothes &amp;quot;  desperate for likes but they don&amp;#39;t know where they come from. Also it is a Chinese company that doesn&amp;#39;t give a shut about your privacy just saying... 
They are also the worst source to get information from cause 90 percent of the time reaserch and statistics is manipulated or not cited(like this post lol) and fake news are spread like crazy 
Hope someone will change my point of view since I have the sin to still using them daily and I need to feel good about myself even tho we all know  these things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：有6英尺0英寸以上的身高偏好，甚至是一種要求，並沒有什麼錯，只要你不因爲自己的偏好而貶低別人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一個5英尺9英寸的男性，所以我不符合這個標準，但並沒有什麼問題。
的問題。身體上的吸引力是一段關係的重要組成部分，而且是非常重要的。
很重要（外表確實很重要）。任何時候一個女人說她更喜歡或只願意和
6'0以上的男人，矮個子男人就會生氣，並表現得像她是......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc8t95/cmv_theres_nothing_wrong_with_having_a_60_height/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc8t95/cmv_theres_nothing_wrong_with_having_a_60_height/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 23:37:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a 5’9 male, so I don’t fit the bill for that standard, but don’t have an issue with it. Physical attraction is a huge part of a relationship and is very important (looks do matter). Anytime a woman says she prefers or will only date 6’0+ men, short men will get pissed and act like she’s the biggest bitch in the world (which is an obvious projection of their insecurities). If you’re not attracted to men below 6’0, then you shouldn’t have to date them, the same way a man shouldn’t have to date an obese woman if he doesn’t find her attractive. People can have whatever preference they want, even if it’s ridiculous, as long as you aren’t shallow towards people who don’t fit your preference. It’s not just easy to “look past it” and find other things thst make up for it, it’s ok to have things you’re solely attracted to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：現場表演的專輯是所有世界中最糟糕的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這並不是說錄音室的專輯比演出好，或者反之亦然。兩者都是
驚人，給音樂帶來不同的方面。

工作室專輯提供了高度拋光和製作的歌曲版本，這是
很好。如果一個樂隊要使用效果器或讓成員演奏多種樂器
樂器，它允許...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc20ch/cmv_albums_of_live_performances_are_the_worst_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc20ch/cmv_albums_of_live_performances_are_the_worst_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 19:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not about studio albums being better than gigs or vice versa. Both are amazing and bring different aspects to music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studio albums provide highly polished and produced versions of songs, which is great. If a band whats to use effects or have members playing multiple instruments it allows them to do so. This is good. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Live shows can provide an amazing atmosphere and performance, at their best creating an almost religious experience for those attending, as well as bonding experiences for friends going together. This is also most excellent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;However&lt;/em&gt;, my issue is that with an album of a live recording, you lose what is best about both. Getting neither the production quality of studio albums, nor the raw experience of being at a mindblowing performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can kind of understand having a recording of a gig you went to, for posterity&amp;#39;s sake, but even then, it isn&amp;#39;t going to match the experience of actually &lt;em&gt;being&lt;/em&gt; there. There is perhaps an accessibility argument, but even then, I&amp;#39;d suggest watching a video of the gig, to get the full AV show, instead of just an audio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT&lt;/strong&gt;: I didn&amp;#39;t think I&amp;#39;d have to write this, but can you explain &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; a certain recording of a live show is not worse than either seeing it live or a studio version, instead of just listing your favourite recording.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT 2&lt;/strong&gt;: After a few responses, I&amp;#39;ve hit on the crux of this CMV; &amp;quot;what does a live recording bring that neither IRL gigs or studio albums do?&amp;quot;. Answer that, and I&amp;#39;ll be putty in your hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美國的監獄系統是破碎的，對任何人都沒有幫助]]></title><description><![CDATA[讓我們把這個問題說清楚，監獄的目的是爲了懲罰一個人，因爲
他們的行爲，並教導他們不要再犯。美國的監獄系統並沒有
實現這些，它甚至沒有接近。看看歐洲的
(特別是挪威/斯堪的納維亞半島）的監獄，他們對待囚犯就像...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc2l9d/cmv_the_us_prison_system_is_broken_and_doesnt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc2l9d/cmv_the_us_prison_system_is_broken_and_doesnt/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 19:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s get this out of the way, the purpose of a prison is to punish someone for their actions and teach them not to repeat it. The US prison system does not accomplish any of this, it doesn&amp;#39;t even come close. Look at the European (specifically Norway/Scandinavia) prisons, they treat prisoners like humans and provide them with in-demand skills, and their recidivism rate is just 20%, compared to the US&amp;#39; massive 70% recidivism rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not surprising, given how the US system is basically throw them in a shithole, treat them like shit and slaves, force them to disclose the fact that they&amp;#39;re a felon on job applications, then going all suprised pikachu face when they can&amp;#39;t find employment and turn back to crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I should clarify, what I mean, is that prisons do help people, just not the prisoners. Instead, they line the pockets of the  contractors who build and maintain them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我們應該讓男性在託兒所和學前教育中工作正常化]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的侄子最近開始上學前班，我只是順便想了一下，我不認爲
我從來沒有見過一個男的學前班老師。如果一個男人不被信任能照顧好孩子，他怎麼能在需要照顧孩子的領域中發揮作用呢？
如果他不被信任去做兒童的基本護理工作，他怎麼能在需要照顧兒童的領域發揮作用呢？
父親經常給孩子換尿布，幫助孩子上廁所，並把...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc318e/cmv_we_should_normalize_males_working_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc318e/cmv_we_should_normalize_males_working_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 18:37:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My nephew recently started pre-k and I just had a passing thought, I don’t think I’ve ever seen a male pre-k teacher. How can a man have a role in a field requiring care for children if he is not trusted with children’s basic care? Fathers often change diapers, help children use the toilet, and put children down for naps. And maybe that’s what distinguishes early childhood education from other female-dominated professions. Declaring men unfit to provide such care is not only about sexism against men, it’s also about sexism against women. The greater the fear of men in caring professions, the more women are left to shoulder the responsibility of care work. If women experienced equality in all professions, then perhaps they wouldn’t regard child care as their exclusive domain, and wouldn’t feel threatened by the participation of men. How can we teach U.S. children not to regard early childhood education as the exclusive domain of women, when they see only women caring for them? What message are we sending today’s youth when we glorify involved fathers and stay-at-home dads but vilify male child-care workers? We should encourage more men to enter this field, and celebrate them rather than fear them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：黑水公司以6500美元一個人的價格從阿富汗撤走人是一件好事。]]></title><description><![CDATA[很多人都在爲黑水公司撤離阿富汗難民而大吵大鬧。
願意並能夠支付6,500美元的阿富汗難民。我明白，這似乎
黑水公司的邪惡暴利行爲，也許是這樣，但事實是
但事實是，他們這樣做，世界會變得更美好。他們並不打算...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc1eam/cmv_blackwater_evacuating_people_from_afghanistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc1eam/cmv_blackwater_evacuating_people_from_afghanistan/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 17:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of people in an uproar because Blackwater is evacuating Afghan refugees who are willing and able to pay $6,500. I understand that this seems like evil profiteering by Blackwater, and maybe it is, but the truth is the world is a better place for them doing this. They are not going to do it for free, and this way more people who want to leave, can. If Blackwater did not evacuate these people, some of them will end up stuck and some of them will even end up on free flights, taking the seat of others. Who is worse off for Blackwater doing this? The constraint on evacuations is a lack of planes, not a lack of runway time (to be clear, some flights did have to divert, but it was because no one could land because refugees had taken over the runways). Blackwater is solving that problem, albeit it a profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Several commenters have made great points that ultimately boil down to how one defines &amp;quot;good,&amp;quot; which is a very nebulous concept. So let me briefly define good as I used it in my title: Good is the absence of bad. We should stop people from doing bad things. We should not stop Blackwater from evacuating people for a price, so long as the constraint on evacuations is planes and not runway time. Blackwater is doing a good thing under my (admittedly binary) definition of good and bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在審議公共政策的範圍內，如果不援引神性就不能爲一個論點辯護，那麼這個論點就是無效的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在這個國家，即美國，據說有一堵故意的牆
教會和國家之間。國家能夠在公民的公共和私人生活中揮舞巨大的權力和
對公民的公共和私人生活產生影響。教會與國家之間的分離
是爲了保護每個機構不受對方的影響。國家...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbzkp5/cmv_within_the_scope_of_deliberations_on_public/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbzkp5/cmv_within_the_scope_of_deliberations_on_public/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:35:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this country, the United States, there is supposedly an intentional wall between church and state. The state is capable of wielding enormous power and influence in public and private lives of citizens. The separation between church and state is to protect each body from the other. The state should not be able to reach into the church and dictate except in extreme cases. Similarly, the church isn’t the government. It doesn’t have the same writ as the government and shouldn’t be allowed to reach into the government or lives of non-followers—ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why I believe decisions based on religion (especially the predominate monotheist versions) are invalid in discourse over public policy comes down to consent and feedback mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every citizen* has access to the franchise and is subject to the government. The government draws its authority from the governed and there are ways to participate, have your voice heard, change policy, and be represented. Jaded as some may be there are mechanisms in place to question, challenge, and influence policy in the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not every citizen follows a religion—further, not even all the followers in America are of the same religion, sect, or denomination. Even IF there was a majority bloc of believers, that is a choice to follow an organization based on faith which demands obedience and eschews feedback/reform. The rules and proclamations are not democratically decided; they are derived, divined, and interpreted by a very small group which does not take requests from the congregation. Which is fine if you’re allowing that to govern your own life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arguments about public policy must allow conversation, debate, introduction of objective facts, challenges to authority, accountability of everyone (top to bottom), and evolution/growth/change with introduction and consideration of new information—all things which theist organizations don’t seem to prioritize. Public policy must be defensible with sound logic and reason. Public policy cannot be allowed to be made on the premise of faith or built upon a foundation of a belief. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aside from leaving the country, we do not have a choice in being subject to the government. Following a faith is a choice. If the government is going to limit my actions, I have few options but to comply and if I disagree then exercise rights. If a church is going to limit my actions and I do not agree, then I can walk away. The church can not be allowed to make rules for those outside the church.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When defending a position on public policy, any defense which falls back on faith, conforming to a religion, or other religious dogma is invalid. If you cannot point to anything more tangible than your own choice in faith or what some parson or clergy dictates, then it should not apply to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any form of, “the law should be X because my faith believes X” is nothing more than forcing your faith on others. CMV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Yes, I’m aware of people under 18, felons, and others denied the right to vote. That isn’t the scope of this conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：種族滅絕並不比其他種族滅絕 "糟糕"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[沒有所謂的種族滅絕的等級。對土著人的滅絕。
宗教、同胞等等，都是一樣可怕的。大屠殺
大屠殺並不比美洲的種族滅絕事件 "好 "或 "壞"。

柬埔寨人、盧旺達人、希臘人，以及這麼多的人都有種族滅絕。

我不會...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pby7dy/cmv_genocides_arent_worse_than_other_genocides/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pby7dy/cmv_genocides_arent_worse_than_other_genocides/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 14:30:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s no such thing as ranked genocides. The extermination of natives, religions, countrymen, etc., are all just as horrible as the other. The Holocaust was not &amp;quot;better&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;worse&amp;quot; than the genocides of the Americas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cambodians, Rwandans, Greeks, and so many more have genocides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wouldn&amp;#39;t be surprised if all countries committed or have been apart of a genocide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If these people were capable of completely erasing a civilization, they would. The lack of the killer&amp;#39;s capabilities, supplies, and logistics are the ONLY reasons that some aren&amp;#39;t completely destroyed. It&amp;#39;s because they literally can&amp;#39;t sustain or prolong it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, numbers and speed can be devastatingly different, but in my opinion, the &amp;quot;idea&amp;quot; of genocide is completely disgusting, evil, hateful, gross, and so much more. You can&amp;#39;t compare one to another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I genuinely love how we&amp;#39;re having adult conversations about something so serious. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在這一點上，審查和禁止社交媒體上的反疫苗社區，將創造更多的反疫苗者]]></title><description><![CDATA[將antivaxx定義爲反對所有疫苗的人。真正的原始
在COVID發生之前的真正原始定義。

我真的相信，我們已經過了審查直言不諱的人到不知名的
平臺，因爲他們現在無處不在。這不僅僅是reddit，或Facebook。
或推特。它是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbontx/cmv_censoring_and_banning_social_media_antivaxx/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbontx/cmv_censoring_and_banning_social_media_antivaxx/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 04:30:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Defining antivaxx as people who are against all vaccines. The true original definition before COVID ever happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I truly believe that we&amp;#39;re past the point of censoring the outspoken to unknown platforms, because they are now everywhere. It&amp;#39;s not just reddit, or Facebook, or Twitter. It&amp;#39;s Instagram and NextDoor and I saw it in descriptions and feedback on Airbnb. It is now everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think various people dropped the ball. I think that it was very unwise of various politicians and news companies to &amp;quot;raise a concern about the vaccine being rushed to help Trump&amp;quot;, and I think that it was unwise for platforms like reddit and Facebook not to foresee this exact thing happening and nipping it in the bud when it started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, your next door neighbor heard something about something, and more people than ever have become truly &amp;quot;vaccine hesitant&amp;quot;. Not just COVID vaccines; all vaccines. The same people I was trying so hard to understand before all of this happened, are now all around me eager to share their thoughts, even in person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think at this point, the only way out is to combat the misinformation, not pretend it doesn&amp;#39;t exist. Reddit and other platforms can ban subreddits, but it&amp;#39;s been complicit in letting it get here, and I don&amp;#39;t think there are too many people left who have no opinion at all. A true crowd-sourced campaign to explain why misinformation is misinformation, including in the communities that are anti-authority--which really, these communities are--is the only way forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply banning them and assuming that they&amp;#39;ll at least go elsewhere is helping the rest of the reddit community feel good about ourselves, but addresses no issues, makes no strides forward to change the narrative, and may even hinder the potential progress. Everyone has heard of the COVID vaccines. Some people are hesitant. Removing any platforms that say anything but positive views, will drive them toward more &amp;quot;research&amp;quot; that will create more hardcore antivaxxers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我們在大流行期間學到的東西導致了這樣的結論：即將發生的氣候災難是不可避免的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，這對我來說是一個很大的問題，但我想盡量客觀地對待
儘可能地客觀和合理。我還想指出的是，我最希望的是
我最希望的是在這裏被說服，我的觀點是錯誤的，因爲我想更多的
充滿希望。

的觀點。

 1. 這是大多數專家的觀點，在...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbhj3v/cmv_what_we_learned_during_the_pandemic_leads_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbhj3v/cmv_what_we_learned_during_the_pandemic_leads_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 04:30:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, this is a big one for me emotionally, but I want to try to be as objective and reasonable as possible. Also I&amp;#39;d like to point out that I&amp;#39;d like nothing more than to be convinced here that my view is wrong, because I want to be more hopeful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The View:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is the opinion of most experts on the matter that we&amp;#39;re heading towards a serious climate disaster if we do nothing to reverse certain trends. Essentially we&amp;#39;re releasing too much carbon and methane from our industrialization/food production/garment industry/etc. and are causing a serious warming trend, more extreme weather and the like.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Those same experts tend to agree that there &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; things we can still do to avert disaster, but in general they seem to me like fairly major changes for most (or at least some) people. For instance, meat production results in a lot of methane emission, which is a worse greenhouse gas than CO2, so if everyone were vegetarian that could be a big help. Also there&amp;#39;s plenty of talk about basically planting a billion trees to store the carbon that would otherwise be in the atmosphere. I don&amp;#39;t know &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the big-picture solutions, nor how much a person&amp;#39;s day-to-day impacts the bigger picture, but it does seem that there are things we &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The pandemic has shown us that there&amp;#39;s a segment of the population that are unwilling to do even something &lt;em&gt;small&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;obviously helpful&lt;/em&gt;, such as wear a mask during a pandemic, or maintain social distancing. I know there&amp;#39;s definitely a loud minority making this segment seem probably larger than it is, but basically my takeaway from it has been that even if you give people something fairly small to do to avert an &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;obviously real and serious&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; risk (Covid), there will still be people who play the &amp;quot;personal freedom&amp;quot; card or science-denial, or some combination of them. So essentially, if you try to get a very large subset of the population to do something &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;even more major&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and to avert a crisis that&amp;#39;s a bit more invisible (i.e. there&amp;#39;s still doubt in the minds of many people that they should or even can do anything to avert the climate disaster) I am of the belief that it&amp;#39;s unreasonable to expect that it would happen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve broken this down into the three distinct points that I feel comprise the whole view as I recognize that any part of the three could have logical holes or problems, or even my notion that they follow in this progression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I said earlier, I&amp;#39;d really love to turn out to be wrong on this one, so let&amp;#39;s have a discussion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt; After posting, I realized that of course there&amp;#39;s more to the climate disaster beyond just the actions of us as individuals. However, I feel that it is a separate discussion to dive into the &amp;quot;who&amp;#39;s at fault&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;corporations vs. individuals&amp;quot; and all of that. My view here is more about individuals and modifying their behavior as individuals. If you feel corporations are more to blame, then I &lt;em&gt;still&lt;/em&gt; blame the individuals who have voted (or not voted) and led to the power and size of our largest corporations who are doing most of the damage. It&amp;#39;s still about people and their choices as far as I&amp;#39;m concerned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：經濟拮据時生孩子是不負責任的做法]]></title><description><![CDATA[我並不是說這很可怕。它只是不負責任。如果財政緊張，那麼生孩子會使財政更緊張。
那麼生孩子會使財政更加緊張。如果你住在農村地區。
我認爲當整個家庭的收入超過8萬/年時，生孩子會更好。
(兩個人的收入都是4萬/年)，如果你住在一個昂貴的地方，我認爲最好在整個家庭收入超過8萬/年的時候生孩子。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbfchx/cmv_it_is_irresponsible_to_have_children_when/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbfchx/cmv_it_is_irresponsible_to_have_children_when/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:30:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m not saying it’s horrible. It’s just irresponsible. If finances are tight, then having kids will make finances tighter. If you are living in a rural area, I’d say it’s better to have kids when the entire household income exceeds 80k/yr (both people making 40k/yr) if you are living in an expensive city, the household income should be higher. The same people who have kids when finances are tight are the same people who complain that they have nothing in savings. No savings for retirement. No savings for emergencies. No savings for their children’s college.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：主要社交媒體平臺上缺乏不喜歡/反對的按鈕，使得反疫苗的觀點能夠更有效地傳播。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的看法。西方最流行的社交媒體平臺，即Facebook。
Instagram和Twitter，都缺乏相當於 "降票 "的反應。正如
在過去十年多的時間裏，Reddit已經向我們展示了收到更多的
的內容在算法中的排名會上升，並且是...。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbepyr/cmv_the_lack_of_a_dislikedownvote_button_on_major/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbepyr/cmv_the_lack_of_a_dislikedownvote_button_on_major/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 21:30:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My view&lt;/strong&gt;: The most popular social media platforms in the West, namely Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter, all lack the equivalent of a &amp;quot;downvote&amp;quot; reaction. As Reddit has shown us over the past decade+, content which receives far more upvotes than downvotes moves up in the algorithm&amp;#39;s ranking and is more likely to be seen. Additionally, from a psychosocial standpoint, humans &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; to be viewed as agreeable, and tend towards views and behavior that the masses consider good. On reddit this often leads to a positive feedback loop, where highly-upvoted content receives even more upvotes because, well, it&amp;#39;s already been upvoted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the aforementioned platforms only have positive reactions for posts and comments (outside of Facebook which has angry/laugh reactions) there&amp;#39;s no true way for a person to tell the relative popularity of a person&amp;#39;s post. This means content that only a small minority of people agree with can end up looking very popular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This leads me to my opinion that beliefs which are truly on the fringe, or at least used to be - such as anti-vaccine or anti-mask - appear more socially acceptable than they really are, and leads people down that path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What I&amp;#39;m not saying:&lt;/strong&gt; The content ranking algorithm on platforms which feature a downvote button, such as Reddit, are &amp;quot;ideal&amp;quot;. I&amp;#39;m only stating my view in the context of enabling and unintentionally promoting false information surrounding vaccines, specifically the COVID-19 vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：女權主義應該改名爲性別平等主義]]></title><description><![CDATA[好的，所以請忍受我。讓我把這個問題說出來。我認爲自己是一個
我認爲自己是一名女權主義者（我使用這個詞的意思是，支持婦女應
根據牛津詞典，"擁有與男性相同的權利和機會"）。)
但是，我更喜歡使用性別平等主義這個詞......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbcmt1/cmv_feminism_should_be_renamed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbcmt1/cmv_feminism_should_be_renamed/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 20:39:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay so bear with me.  Let me get this out of the way: I consider myself a feminist (I&amp;#39;m using this term to mean a supporter of the idea that women should &amp;#39;have the same rights and opportunities as men&amp;#39; as per the Oxford dictionary).  HOWEVER, I much prefer to use the term Gender-Egalitarianism because I think it&amp;#39;s a title that better represents feminism&amp;#39;s central message and thus better promotes the movement&amp;#39;s agenda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I see often on the Internet (and sometimes in real life too) is people being reluctant to identify as a feminist because they see feminism as being about getting more things (rights, freedoms, opportunities, political power, etc.) for women FULL STOP.  What I mean by this is, they see feminism as being about lifting up women, with little to no regard to how this leaves men off at the end of the day.  Now, true feminism of course rejects this and takes the issues that disproportionately affect men (like being far less likely to receive custody of their children in divorce, for example) as real problems that need to be solved if men and women are going to be equal in society (of course, this doesn&amp;#39;t mean that a feminist needs to say that men and women have it equally hard, as long as a feminist is willing to admit that both &amp;#39;female&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;male&amp;#39; issues are legitimate issues and deserve addressing, then they&amp;#39;re free to think whatever they want about the current balance of hardship between the sexes).  SO, because feminism is looked at by many people as a women&amp;#39;s power movement, rather than a movement about achieving equality with respect to gender/sex, there a great number of people who have negative connotations with the term feminism, and are far less likely to hear out feminist thinkers/arguments with an open mind.  The is evidenced by the fact that (and I don&amp;#39;t have the stat to point to but it shouldn&amp;#39;t be hard to find) that the discrepancy between people who believe the sexes should be equal and people who self-identify as feminists is massive in the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SO, in order to get more people in a state where they can hear the feminist message with an open mind, we need to ditch the (frankly) shitty name &amp;#39;Feminism&amp;#39;.  It simply does not reflect its core message as well as Gender-Egalitarianism does, and this is costing the movement its ability to be heard out by many potential allies.  Imagine if Racial-Egalitarianism (the idea that the races should have the same rights and opportunities) was called &amp;#39;Blackism&amp;#39;.  You&amp;#39;d probably think, well, that&amp;#39;s a shitty name, not only because there&amp;#39;s a lot of disenfranchised races and it&amp;#39;s weird to pick out one, but because it just SOUNDS like a black power movement full stop, which is bound to turn off many potential allies before they have a chance to dig into the movement and see that its core message is something that is actually very desirable.  How could &amp;#39;Feminism&amp;#39; be any different?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a note, I&amp;#39;m not suggesting that Feminism would become universally accepted overnight if it had the name change I&amp;#39;m advocating for, I&amp;#39;m saying that it would make it easier for at least some people who currently view Feminism in a negative light to be more open minded to the movement.  If it would help to recruit at least some more supporters (whether they be people alive today or future persons who might have been turned off the movement by the name &amp;#39;Feminism&amp;#39;), then why wouldn&amp;#39;t we want to do it?  What would be the countervailing harm the name change would or might cause that could justify us keeping the name &amp;#39;Feminism&amp;#39;?  Also, if you&amp;#39;re tempted to respond that &amp;#39;those who are stupid enough to view Feminism as a women&amp;#39;s power movement shouldn&amp;#39;t be our concern&amp;#39;, or &amp;#39;people who make that mistake should educate themselves&amp;#39;, then I would respond that 1) one of the central goals of Feminism is the widespread acceptance of the core Feminist message, and to do this we’ll need to get comfortable marketing the movement to people who view the movement in ways people who support the movement might find &amp;#39;stupid&amp;#39;. 2) why wait for uneducated people to educate themselves, when you can do something right now (that is very easy to do I might add) that makes them less likely to make the mistake you consider to be so stupid in the first place?  It seems very arrogant and even reckless to prefer to sit back and wait for others to see the light, so to speak - especially when leaving gender inequality unresolved has real consequences that are measured in human suffering!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I know there is no central organization to the feminist movement, so I know that there is no governing body that can unilaterally decide on the name change I&amp;#39;m advocating for.  However, if feminists started referring to themselves as Gender-Egalitarians and said that they were moved to this name change out of a concern that the name alienates many people who they hope to one day call allies, I think the movement could for all intents and purposes be considered renamed in fairly short amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m very curious to see what people think are good reasons for resisting the name change I&amp;#39;m advocating for! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果我們真的關心結構性不平等問題，我們的首要重點應該是降低生活成本。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大多數圍繞不平等的討論往往集中在收入方面。在我看來
在我看來，在一個像住房、醫療和教育這樣的基本東西的成本正以極高的速度膨脹的世界裏，這意義是有限的。
住房、醫療和教育的成本正以極高的速度膨脹。真正解決
真正解決這個問題的更好方法是利用技術知識。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbd8xk/cmv_if_we_really_care_about_structural_inequality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbd8xk/cmv_if_we_really_care_about_structural_inequality/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 19:34:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the discussions around inequality tends to focus on income. In my opinion this has limited meaning in a world where cost of basic stuff like Shelter, Healthcare and Education are inflating at extremely high rates. The better way to genuinely tackle the issue is to utilize technological know how and planning to deflate the costs of these basic things along with food and clothing down to a very low level. Example: like how TVs and computers have gotten cheaper while also becoming much better. In such a world it would be much harder to exploit people and even if there would be inequality, it would not hurt as much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>