<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 04:34:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：Netflix應該讓社區的《高級龍與地下城》迴歸。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix刪除了《社區》的這一集，因爲Chang穿了 "黑臉"。

我的立場不是很複雜。

首先，我理解黑暗精靈可以說是基於種族定型觀念的
我認爲支持刪除這一集的唯一理由是
支持一些基於...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pyq93v/cmv_netflix_should_bring_back_advanced_dungeons/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pyq93v/cmv_netflix_should_bring_back_advanced_dungeons/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 22:39:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix removed this episode of Community because Chang wore &amp;quot;blackface&amp;quot;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My stance is not very complex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firstly, I understand that dark elves are arguably based on racial stereotypes and I think the only argument in favor of removing the episode is that supportting something based on a stereotype. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To argue that point. The second paint ball episode Chang and Jeff are getting attacked by the Math club and Chang says &amp;#39;Are you guys Asian?&amp;#39;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you would say &amp;quot;this is based of a good stereotype where as dressing up as a Drow is based on a negative stereotype.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And my response to that is, lol. We are now categorizing good and bad racism?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please someone change my view on why Netflix removing this episode is not only arbitrary, but also inconsistent and unnecessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This sets a terrible precedent and removes one of the greatest Community episodes from easy viewing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV："中心主義是壞的/錯誤的 "這一共識以及對中心主義的普遍推動是相當令人震驚的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這一次可能會是一個漫長的過程。讓我先說一下，我
我認爲自己是 "LibCenter"，使用PCM的術語。此外，我的經驗
我在Reddit的經驗主要是：非政治性子，如視頻遊戲的子，或小衆話題的子。
小衆話題的子站，還有一些左翼傾向的子站，因爲......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pyod3b/cmv_the_consensus_that_centrism_is_badwrong_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pyod3b/cmv_the_consensus_that_centrism_is_badwrong_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This one is probably going to a long one. Let me preface this by saying, I consider myself &amp;quot;LibCenter&amp;quot;, using PCM terminology. Additionally, my experience with Reddit is largely with: non-political subs, like subs for video-games or subs for niche topics, and then also some Left leaning subs since the really popular subs like Selfawarewolves, murderedbywords, worldnews, askreddit, etc. tend to have a very noticeable Left-leaning slant. I&amp;#39;m not saying that this is a bad thing, or that this is fundamentally wrong. I&amp;#39;m just acknowledging that this is the case. There are 2 other subreddits that I frequent which are a lot more right leaning: PCM and walkaway. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The motivation for my view comes from an increasing use of the term &amp;quot;Enlightened Centrism&amp;quot;. As I outlined above, aside from the non-political subs, most of the rest are Left-leaning, and this general push against Centrism is commonly found in those Left leaning subs, and not so much in the Right leaning ones from my personal experience. All this is to say, in general my argument will be geared more towards people that are deeply Left, because those are the people that I most commonly see taking issue with my Centrist position. However, it is important to note that this phenomenon happens in both communities and is not exclusive to the Left. I just chose to focus on that aspect for my post, since I don&amp;#39;t really spend too much time on Right wing places in general. I realize now that my entire last sentence is the perfect embodiment of Centrism itself: I disagree with side A, but side B also has a lot of the same issues. Lol. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, to define the issue, let me paraphrase what I think is the general view that some Left leaning people hold on this issue:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Centrists largely play both sides in an attempt to shield themselves from criticism as they can deflect any argument by saying they do not agree with that aspect of that ideology. Moreover, most Centrists on Reddit are just people who are closet Right-wingers that know they will be attacked for their views so they choose to play it under the guise of Centrism. Essentially, most Centrists are just people who are looking for a way to present their Right-leaning views without explicitly calling themselves right-wing, and they aren&amp;#39;t being actual Centrists by doing that. Lastly, Centrists choose to ignore important issues, and by adopting the Centrist position they choose to forego the progressive nature of the Left and don&amp;#39;t speak up about certain injustices because they feel like they don&amp;#39;t need to. Their silence on these topics is inherently wrong in this case.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As will be the common theme, I KNOW that I do not speak for everyone with that summary. I&amp;#39;m not claiming that the paragraph above perfectly describes everyone&amp;#39;s issues with Centrism. That is just the amalgamation of the most common arguments I&amp;#39;ve seen and it&amp;#39;s what I&amp;#39;m basing my post around. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to shielding against criticism, I can understand the issue. Way too many people use Centrism as an umbrella defense for almost anything, and this ends up in no real arguments taking place. I personally think this is more a fault of the person and not of their political views. The view that most Centrists are inherently people with Right wing views looking for an &amp;quot;acceptable&amp;quot; way to voice them is just stupid. Of course they have Right wing views, they are a CENTRIST. They have views from both ends of the spectrum, and to varying degrees; that&amp;#39;s literally what it is. When I see people use this argument, to me what it says is: yea they have some Left wing views but they also have some Right wing views which I think are bad and wrong so I&amp;#39;m gonna chose to focus on the Right wing aspect and deem them as Right wingers posing as Centrists.&amp;quot; This misses the whole point. I do not call myself a Centrist so I can hold right wing views without being ostracized from certain communities, and pretending that I do is disingenuous. What I&amp;#39;m essentially hearing is that if you call yourself a Centrist but have more right wing views than what I deem acceptable (which is 0 in most cases), then you aren&amp;#39;t a real centrist or you&amp;#39;re an &amp;quot;Enlightened Centrist&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That last point is a bit of a weird one. Just because you consider yourself in the center doesn&amp;#39;t mean that you can ignore pertinent issues from either side. Obviously, many people will disagree with which issues are actually important and consequently they may choose to stay silent on these topics. That doesn&amp;#39;t mean that they are ignoring their responsibilities. It is a political choice/view. Moreover, you do not need to actively fight for something to believe in it. For instance, you do not need to be waving around a pride flag and joining in pride marches if you agree with equal rights for all sexual orientations. Claiming that you do, and that by choosing not to speak you are actively harming the cause, is a very presumptuous and alarming mindset. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wholeheartedly believe that a majority of people, both online and offline, are closer to the center than the extremes of their respective ideologies. I also believe that there is a very meaningful and increasingly overlooked difference between far-right, right, and center-right/moderate-right (and vice versa for the left). I believe that, naturally, Centrism or rather being closer to the center is a more desirable world view for people to hold. You can have your cake and eat it too! As a Centrist, you get to cherry pick the best parts of the Left&amp;#39;s ideology, and the same for the Right, and then you can discard the aspects that you think are wrong. Politics is becoming increasingly binary and people seem to think that, &amp;quot;Yea, Leftism has it&amp;#39;s flaws but in general, when looking at the bigger picture it is a better and morally superior ideology to the Right, so naturally everyone should fully embrace Leftism and all its flaws because the only alternative is embracing Rightism.&amp;quot; Why do things have to be this way? This is not a religion, it is a political spectrum. There is nothing wrong with choosing the best parts of certain ideologies and crafting your own world view using the sum of those best parts. There are no &amp;quot;rules&amp;quot; in that regard, and pretending like there are, and using that as an argument against Centrism is not only wrong but also harmful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To conclude with a stereotypical Centrist phrase, both sides have good and bad. Both sides have their issues and strengths. Trying to push people away from a position that takes both ideologies at face value and forcing them to choose one or the other is alarming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Lots of good points. My main takeaway from this post is that I&amp;#39;m not actually a centrist it seems. My reasoning for considering myself center is because I take the best aspects from whatever ideologies are on display and kind of use it to make the best ideology I can, incorporating something from everywhere in a way. Clearly this isn&amp;#39;t Centrism, because I am not actively trying to find a middle-ground, or argue that the &amp;quot;middle&amp;quot; will always be better than either extreme, even thought I think this is largely true in a LOT of cases, just not all of them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To elaborate further, maybe I should use some examples. I am pro-choice, pro-LGBT rights, and pro-weed/drug decriminalization. I am also pro-gun rights, against taxes in general, and support the death penalty to a certain degree. I don&amp;#39;t know how else to classify myself aside from considering myself &amp;quot;center&amp;quot;. Perhaps the issue lies in the words Centrist/Centrism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：不希望與變性人約會，因爲你沒有被吸引，這不是變性人的問題。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你不想和變性人約會，因爲你對他們懷有仇恨，那是錯誤的。
這是錯誤的。我將解釋我的個人觀點，因爲這是我的觀點，而且
我真的想證實或反駁我的觀點，因爲我最終希望
儘可能地充滿愛和接受。我被吸引到...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pyn1ps/cmv_it_is_not_transphobic_not_to_wish_to_date_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pyn1ps/cmv_it_is_not_transphobic_not_to_wish_to_date_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 18:46:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you do not want to date a trans person because you hateful towards them, that is wrong. I will explain my personal perspective since this is my opinion and really I want to either confirm or disprove my view since I ultimately want to be as loving and accepting as possible. I am attracted to women. We have come very far in treatments (surgeries, hormonal therapy, etc) so that a trans woman can feel happy and at peace with their bodies. And I wish them nothing but happiness. Yet there is still a discernible difference between a biological woman from birth, and a trans woman. For example, I have noticed that trans women tend to have facial structures that are more traditionally masculine. And with no hatred or bias against trans women or anyone, that visual appearance makes it that my mind cannot go there and feel attracted towards them. I recognize that these treatments have come very very far. And so it might very soon come to the point that my perspective is nullified once trans women and women are practically indiscernible physically. And genuinely I hope for that, assuming that’s what trans people would want to be the happiest with their appearance and identity. Yet as it stands right now, for someone like me, I find myself turned off by trans women and cannot find them attractive as I do women from birth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: For all I know my words are insensitive or accidentally hateful. Please in addition to your rebuttals, feel free to tell me how to make my words more correct and courteous towards the community. I’m not the part of any minority and grew up in a well meaning but homophobic household. I’m trying to be a good person towards everyone but have a lot to learn. Much love and looking forward to our conversations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：大多數 "回到我的時代 "類型的聲明都值得傾聽，特別是當比我們年長的人說的時候，在很多情況下，承認我們不比他們更清楚是可以的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我承認這可能是一個有缺陷的觀點，但我認爲大多數人需要停止
自以爲是，接受年長者往往有更好的建議。
因爲他們有更多時間做錯事，犯錯誤，然後找到比年輕人更好的處理方法。
然後找到比年輕人更好的方法來處理它們。有...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pyjr7y/cmv_most_back_in_my_day_type_statements_are_worth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pyjr7y/cmv_most_back_in_my_day_type_statements_are_worth/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 17:30:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I accept that this could be a flawed view, but I think most people need to stop being so self-righteous and just accept older people often do have better advice because they have had more time to be wrong and make mistakes and then find better ways to deal with them than younger people have. There are a surprising amount of things that can be true for multiple generations&amp;#39; experiences, so &amp;#39;back in my day&amp;#39; is completely appropriate way to preface advice for those kind of things. Why is it such a controversial buzzword and why are we so afraid to be proven wrong? If anyone can give me a convincing argument as to why we should devalue advice given by older generations to younger ones, then please let me know because I genuinely don&amp;#39;t know them but I want to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：變性人的包容、公平和安全在許多運動中無法共存。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這不僅僅是我個人的觀點，這也是E.S.A.對變性人融入體育運動的廣泛評論的結論。
的結論，也是 "體育平等 "組織對變性人融入體育的廣泛審查。
[https://equalityinsport.org/docs/300921/Guidance%20for%20Transgender%20Inclusion%20in%20Domestic%20Sport%202021.pdf]
在英國進行的廣泛審查的結論。

長期以來，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pylydc/cmv_transgender_inclusion_fairness_and_safety/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pylydc/cmv_transgender_inclusion_fairness_and_safety/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 17:30:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;#39;t just a view I personally hold, it&amp;#39;s also the conclusion of a wide ranging review of transgender inclusion in sport by &lt;a href=&quot;https://equalityinsport.org/docs/300921/Guidance%20for%20Transgender%20Inclusion%20in%20Domestic%20Sport%202021.pdf&quot;&gt;Equality in Sport&lt;/a&gt; in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a long time now it&amp;#39;s been a concern of many that the inclusion of MtF transgender athletes in natal female category sports risks undermining fairness and risking safety. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately it&amp;#39;s a topic that can rarely be discussed maturely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, I believe sports are a unifying force in society. I believe they should be open and available to everybody and I believe efforts must be made to enable Transgender representation at the highest levels of sport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not however believe, that it is fair or safe for people born biologically male, to compete alongside biological females in a number of sports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This need to ensure safety cannot be reconciled with the right to self-identify in sports categorization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like for that view to be challenged, albeit maturely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：幾乎沒有理由按性別劃分空間，但性別是劃分空間的一個依據。]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，我並不否認性別認同或性別的存在。然而。
沒有任何重要的理由因爲一個身份而將社會的物理空間分開。
身份。大多數男性/女性的劃分（浴室、監獄、更衣室等）都是由於身體的差異而分開的，而不是
是由於身體上的差異而分開的，而不是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pyjita/cmv_there_is_virtually_no_reason_to_have_spaces/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pyjita/cmv_there_is_virtually_no_reason_to_have_spaces/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 15:44:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;To start, I am not denying the existence of gender identity or gender.
However, there is no significant reasons to separate societal physical spaces due to an identity.  Most male/female divisions (bathrooms, prisons, dressing rooms, etc.) are separated due to physical differences in bodies, not mental states.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example: Dressing rooms are traditionally separated by sex, as males and females have different body parts that are revealed while getting dressed.  Someone&amp;#39;s gender identity is not visible at all in a dressing room, and isn&amp;#39;t relevant to separate people by.  I do know if the person next to me has a penis, I don&amp;#39;t know if they identify as a man/woman/neither/both/other.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another is sports.  Sports are separated by sex due to the huge physical differences males and females have.  Gender identity has no relevance when assigning sports teams (for example there is no issue with the non-binary, female soccer player in the olympics, she was placed on the team due to sex, not gender identity.). It is irrelevant in the race what gender people identify with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if there is a division needed, it will virtually always be regarding sex.  There is really no basis to have any divisions based on gender identity (excluding groups that need support for gender identity issues, for example, this post is discussion separating the population in two.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Separating spaces such as sports, bathrooms, dressing rooms, prisons, shelters, etc. by gender identity has no purpose, as gender identity is invisible, can be changeable, and isn&amp;#39;t relevant to the physical basis why these were originally separated.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, this isn&amp;#39;t to discount gender identity, it is just saying it isn&amp;#39;t a basis for physical separation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don&amp;#39;t believe there should be separations by sex, then there is definitely no reason to separate due to gender.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to clarify, this isn&amp;#39;t arguing that spaces need to be sex segregated (that is a different debate), but that sex does have a legitimate basis for separation, &lt;strong&gt;there is no reason that gender identity would be the basis for separating these spaces.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: r/gunfights中的帖子如果要上頭條，應該是模糊的nsfw，字面上顯示人們被槍殺。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我意識到，該子在進入時有一個nsfw標籤。這是一個不同的故事，因爲
滾動頭版，看到一個沒有警告的帖子，你將看到一個視頻的開始，這和滾動頭版不同。
在沒有提示的情況下，你將看到一個視頻開始，該視頻將以圖形方式顯示槍支暴力，在某些情況下，槍支暴力導致的死亡。
在某些情況下，槍支暴力導致的實際死亡。我還沒有...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/py6h11/cmv_the_posts_in_rgunfights_should_be_blurred/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/py6h11/cmv_the_posts_in_rgunfights_should_be_blurred/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 01:16:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I realize that the sub has a nsfw tag upon entry. That&amp;#39;s a different story than scrolling the front page and seeing a post with no warning that you&amp;#39;re about to see a video start, unprompted, that will graphically show gun violence and in some cases actual death from that gun violence. I haven&amp;#39;t been aware of the sub until the other day when I saw a person gets killed before I even realized what I was watching. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find it hard to justify how this is ok, it&amp;#39;s possible there&amp;#39;s something I&amp;#39;m missing as to how there&amp;#39;s a right or benefit to this sub getting allowed to show incredibly graphic violent content without any warning signal. I also realize that scrolling the front page at any given time probably means that I&amp;#39;ll see some things that aren&amp;#39;t interesting to me, I don&amp;#39;t think that&amp;#39;s what I&amp;#39;m saying. I&amp;#39;d like to try to understand how the exact instance of this sub is accepted by someone who agrees with this content not being marked and blurred nsfw.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：一個藝術家是一個糟糕的人，並不意味着他們的藝術就不偉大。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我告訴別人我最喜歡的系列和故事（浪客劍心）後，聽到的第一句話是："你聽說過那個漫畫家嗎？
我告訴別人我最喜歡的系列和故事（《浪客劍心》）後聽到的第一句話是："你聽說過那個漫畫家嗎？"就像沒有人知道一樣。
我真的只是說這是我最喜歡的系列，我可能一直在追蹤作者和他目前的作品。
作者和他目前的作品和交易。

爲那些快速注意...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxphej/cmv_an_artist_being_a_terrible_person_doesnt_make/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxphej/cmv_an_artist_being_a_terrible_person_doesnt_make/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:39:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;the first thing I hear after telling people my favorite series and story of all time (rurouni kenshin) is &amp;quot;Did you hear about that mangaka?&amp;quot;. like no duh person I literally just said it&amp;#39;s my favorite series I probably keep track of the author and his current works and dealings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quick note for those of you who don&amp;#39;t know he was found basically being a pedophile&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am I just supposed to stop finding the story compelling? am I supposed to stop enjoying the story? am i supposed to stop finding the characters relatable? Honestly do I even hate the idea of my money going to this man? no not really, what I really want though is for him to get him, I don&amp;#39;t want him to die and wither in a gutter despite his actions If he&amp;#39;s willing to change and apologize. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are of course other less serve cases, the creator of DMC is a notorious dick head, should I stop liking Dante?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also what about the person making cutting you meat? the person employing that person? any order you make on amazon? everything we do money goes to bad people, I don&amp;#39;t see why I should stop consuming something I really enjoy just cause we find out a specific bad thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：那些因爲支持某個政黨或對某個話題有某種看法而譴責其他人的人，本質上誤解了民主的概念。]]></title><description><![CDATA[編輯：我來自德國。這通常意味着，大多數政黨不會無視
你不可能通過告訴我如何在德國人的生活方式上改變我的想法。
你不會因爲告訴我某個美國政黨有多可怕而改變我的想法。

西方世界的大多數國家都生活在民主制度中，其基本原則之一是
是多元主義。多元主義...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxwvvx/cmv_people_who_condemn_other_people_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxwvvx/cmv_people_who_condemn_other_people_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 17:00:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Edit: I am from Germany. This generally means that most parties do not disregard any human rights and you are not going to change my mind by telling me how horrible a certain American party is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the western world lives in a democracy and one of its basic principles is pluralism. Pluralism encourages the support of a variety of opinions and viewpoints and is arguably one of the most important parts of democracy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent times, I&amp;#39;ve seen many people fixated on one thing and they then claim everyone supporting a certain viewpoint is wrong/immoral. This concept of trying to erase other opinions, regardless how moral or immoral one regards them to be inherently contradicts the basis of democracy and therefore people who do this and yet claim to be democratic are hypocrits. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, everyone is allowed to disagree with opinions and even publicly arguing against them, but &amp;#39;cancelling&amp;#39; people over viewpoints or things they said has no part in a democratic system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t necessarily think that this is wrong but everytime I voice this I get downvoted so there seems to be a flaw in my logic. I&amp;#39;m always open to change if someone can convince me :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I am solely talking about viewpoints that are within the democratic system. This means issues like racism, genocide or any other form of discrimination are not included.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：手機上的 "鍵盤點擊 "聲對用戶體驗沒有任何幫助，只會讓用戶周圍的人感到厭煩。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是一個很多手機都有的功能，但它對提高用戶體驗沒有任何作用。
用戶體驗。如果你在打字，你知道你在打字。如果你
如果你盯着屏幕，你就知道你不是在打字。聲音能帶來什麼？
該死的，如果你的手機有一個鍵盤，它甚至都沒有聲音...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxv9fs/cmv_the_keyboard_click_sound_on_phones_does/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxv9fs/cmv_the_keyboard_click_sound_on_phones_does/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 15:41:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a feature plenty of phones have, and it does not do anything to enhance user experience. If you&amp;#39;re typing something, you know you&amp;#39;re typing. If you&amp;#39;re staring at your screen, you know you&amp;#39;re not typing. what does the sound add? Hell, if your phone has a keyboard it&amp;#39;s not even as loud as the sound AND you actually get haptic feedback from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The artificial sound doesn&amp;#39;t add anything to the satisfaction of typing out a text. It is also making unnecessary noise that nobody else cares to hear. Especially with the volume that it&amp;#39;s at. It is a feature that serves no purpose and should not exist on any smart phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am i missing a point to this feature? CMV...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: what wont change my view: &amp;quot;i like it&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s not about everyone else, it&amp;#39;s about what i like&amp;quot; that&amp;#39;s just selfish. im guessing you use speaker phone in public places too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：相當多的Redditors沒有細微差別的概念，並贊同弊大於利的籠統說法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這指的是你在這個網站上發現的任何政治帖子。按以下方式排序
最熱門的評論，你會發現有很多籠統的概括，攻擊對方的
對立黨派。例如，早些時候，我看到一個r/all [/r/all]的最高評論，說 "共和黨人是種族主義者，但否認他們的權利"。
帖子說："共和黨人是種族主義者，但否認它，因爲他們不是......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxqkrm/cmv_a_significant_amount_of_redditors_have_no/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxqkrm/cmv_a_significant_amount_of_redditors_have_no/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:30:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This in reference to any political post that you find on this website. Sort by top comments &amp;amp; you’ll find multiple sweeping generalizations attacking the opposing party. For example, earlier I saw a top comment on an &lt;a href=&quot;/r/all&quot;&gt;r/all&lt;/a&gt; post that said “Republicans are racist but deny it since they’re not actively lynching people. If you tell them this they’ll claim you’re the one being racist, it’s exhausting.” I don’t browse the conservative subreddits but I’m sure I wouldn’t have to search hard to find comments with a similar theme. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some background on me, I’m from a very liberal part of California and I’ve voted Democrat every presidential election that I’ve participated in. Prior to joining the military I had little to no exposure to people aligned with the Republican party. Over the course of 5 years, I became close with more stereotypical gun-toting, F-150 driving, dip-spitting rednecks than I can count. For the most part, they were good people and the only racism/bigotry I saw happened on two occasions out of the 5 long years that I was in. Incidentally, I’ve also heard that sort of vitreol coming from people that would identify as Democrats. It’s a different kind of racism, it’s more casual but it exists. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This shouldn’t be news to anyone, but I’ve come to the conclusion that someone’s political affiliation is not enough to accurately judge their character or morals. As it turns out, there are hateful &amp;amp; rotten humans on both sides of the political spectrum. Generalizing the opposite party in a negative manner only serves to widen the political divide whilst embittering the other side even more. A common tell that Detectives look for is visible within the reaction of a suspect that has just been accused of committing a crime. Normally, if someone is accused of doing something that they haven’t done, their initial reaction is one of anger and indignation. Everyday on Reddit these accusations are thrown around and instead of hearing the accused out, we plug our ears and look to our peers for approval &amp;amp; agreement. The anger from being wrongfully accused turns into resentment and I believe that resentment eventually breeds hatred. I think as a whole we lack nuance &amp;amp; free-thought. It’s much easier to digest the narratives &amp;amp; headlines that we are fed than it is to seek the truth ourselves. People seem to forget that although there are two extremes on the political spectrum, there is a LOT of space to exist in between and I think that’s where you’ll find most people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 如果一個領導人是民主選舉產生的，那麼他或她在國內或國外所做的壞事，人民是絕對要承擔責任的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[人們總是談論人與政治家是不同的，你不應該根據他們的政治家所做的事情來判斷一個人。
你不應該根據政治家的所作所爲來判斷一個人。然而，我
我認爲，這只是一種用來逃避責任的策略。我並不
我不想在我的實際帖子中指責具體國家，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxeibe/cmv_if_a_leader_is_democratically_elected_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxeibe/cmv_if_a_leader_is_democratically_elected_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 04:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;People always talk about how people are different from politicians, and you are not supposed to judge a person based on what their politicians do. However I would argue that this is simply a tactic used to avoid responsibility. I do not want to point fingers at specific countries in my actual post, even though I will probably do so in the comments anyway, so my apologies if the names of these fake countries sound cheesy to you, but anyway, here we go anyway. Imagine the following hypothetical scenario:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The people of Awesomeland elect President X, who wins by a landslide. Then, President X makes some very unpopular choices domestically, and many people say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It is what it is, it’s not up to us.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes it is, you specifically gave him power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But OK, to make up for his shitty domestic choices, President X now invades Evilstan. A lot of Evilstanjans are killed by airstrikes and Awesomeland soldiers. Their economy is crippled by sanctions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet the people of Awesomeland will argue, that the average Awesomelandian should not be blamed, because they’re just people. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reality, no. Every single Awesomelandian who voted for President X now has blood on his hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, not directly naming any countries, so as to not get shit in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 強迫你的狗和貓喫素是錯誤的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[雖然狗和貓可以靠植物性飲食生存，但理想的營養--良好健康的基礎--在這種飲食中得不到很好的滿足。
但理想的營養--良好健康的基礎--在這種飲食中得不到很好的滿足。

特別是貓，在無肉飲食中表現不佳。因爲它們是強制性的
肉食動物，或 "真正的 "肉食動物--這意味着它們只依賴營養物質
發現...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxl7on/cmv_forcing_a_vegan_diet_on_your_dogs_and_cats_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxl7on/cmv_forcing_a_vegan_diet_on_your_dogs_and_cats_is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 03:32:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though dogs and cats can survive on plant based diet, ideal nutrition- the foundation of good health- is not well served on that diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cats, in particular, don’t do well on a meatless diet. Because they’re obligate carnivores, or &amp;quot;true&amp;quot; carnivores — meaning they depend only on the nutrients found in animal flesh for their survival — their bodies (specifically, their gastrointestinal tracts) are not ideally suited to digesting non-meat foods. Though cats seem to do well on vegan diets once they’ve acclimated to them, the long-term effects of feeding felines diets that lack animal protein have not been established.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And dogs, long considered omnivores, have been reclassified as carnivorous by some leading pet nutritionists. Which means, given our current understanding, that it’s not reasonable to expect best results in health and longevity if you’re feeding them a vegan diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe that forcing carnivores to consume vegan diets because of our philosophical beliefs is tantamount to animal abuse. I mean, if you really want to feed your pet a vegan diet, consider getting a rabbit. Or a goat. But don’t keep a carnivore and think you can subject him to your own dietary choices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在美國廢除精神病院是個錯誤]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我提出我的觀點之前，我覺得提供一些背景資料和
一個個人軼事將有助於澄清我對這個問題的看法。

我對困擾美國醫療系統的問題有一定的瞭解，但是
我完全沒有意識到醫療系統的待遇有多差。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxescs/cmv_abolishing_mental_institutions_in_the_us_was/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxescs/cmv_abolishing_mental_institutions_in_the_us_was/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 23:38:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before I present my view, I feel that providing some background information and a personal anecdote will help clarify my view on this issue: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been somewhat aware of the problems plaguing the US healthcare system, but I was completely unaware of just how poorly the healthcare system treats mental health before having first-hand experience. Basically, long story short, I was placed on a seven day involuntary psychiatric hold after  an alcohol-fueled, depression related incident almost ended in a suicide attempt. Fortunately, I&amp;#39;m doing much better now, and I&amp;#39;ve been directed towards the right therapy and prescribed medications that are working. Unfortunately, I can&amp;#39;t say the same for most of the patients I was with during my hospital stay. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was placed in a psychiatric unit at a standard urban hospital with about fifty or-so patients, and I&amp;#39;ll have to admit that the cases of some of the other patients, which I won&amp;#39;t go into detail here, were truly frightening. Basically, these people have completely lost all contact with reality and have very little chance of ever coming back to what we experience as &amp;#39;normal.&amp;#39; These patients have mental illness that&amp;#39;s progressed to a point where they are completely incapable of doing simple tasks like preparing their own food, taking care of themselves, and basically functioning like a normal human being. These are the people who need the most help, yet they are thrown out by the system. Literally. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These patients, who obviously are in need of long-term support, treatment for substance abuse, I&amp;#39;d even say assisted living in some cases, are literally given a bus ticket and thrown out on the street after their involuntary psychiatric hold ends after three to seven days (which is the standard length that most people are hospitalized). It&amp;#39;s absolutely absurd that people who are basically unaware of their own physical existence are being thrown out on the street and are expected to fend for themselves without any support or therapy. From what I&amp;#39;ve seen, a lot of these people are homeless, elderly, disabled, living on their own, addicted to substances, or a variety of things all at once. For the short time that their involuntary psychiatric hold stays in effect, these people are given guidance and care, but once that hold ends, there&amp;#39;s pretty much nothing the system can do except discharge them and provide a referral to a mental health provider. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is also what happened in my case: I was discharged after my seven day hold ended and I was told to follow up with a mental health provider. I turns out that there isn&amp;#39;t a single mental health provider within a twenty mile radius of my home that is accepting new patients because of the overload of the system. I was able to get an hour long internet-call appointment, almost two months after my hospitalization. And they won&amp;#39;t even talk with you unless you provide proof of insurance and a credit card. This is absolutely absurd, and there&amp;#39;s no way that patients with severe psychiatric issues will get the help they need unless they are privileged with insurance and good finances (which the majority of aren&amp;#39;t). But insurance is a whole other topic that applies to the entire healthcare system that I won&amp;#39;t go into here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now it seems that the only thing that hospitals are able to do with these severe-case patients is discharge them and expect them to follow up with another provider. This is absolutely absurd. What I&amp;#39;m basically saying is that there&amp;#39;s nothing more they can do expect throw them out and let them rot on the streets. These sorts of things shouldn&amp;#39;t be happening in a country with as much wealth and resources as the United States, or anywhere as a matter of fact. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My view is that the US needs to reopen its psychiatric institutions. Providing appropriate care to severe-case psychiatric patients is an urgent matter and little to nothing is being done with those who are the most disadvantaged. In my view, the disestablishment of psychiatric facilities in the 70s-80s has been a big mistake and has contributed to the growing mental health crisis and homeless crisis, both of which have grown out of proportion. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yes, I&amp;#39;m also aware that psychiatric institutions were shut down due to abuse and abhorrent living conditions, and I definitely don&amp;#39;t believe that people should be subject to sub-standard treatment under any circumstances. But throwing out these patients and leaving them to fend on their own is just as bad and should not be acceptable under any circumstances. It&amp;#39;s heartbreaking to see, but there are some people who truly cannot exist on their own. Their perception of reality is so skewed that they are a threat to both themselves and other people. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deinstitutionalization occurred because patients in mental hospitals were treated more as prisoners instead of being rehabilitated. The idea was that with the abolishment of mental institutions, these patients would find better treatment elsewhere. The truth is, that people end up receiving no treatment at all, and mental health care has only become more and more inaccessible. Here&amp;#39;s a statistic that illustrates this fact: &amp;quot;In 1955, for every 100,000 US citizens there were 340 psychiatric hospital beds. In 2005 that number had diminished to 17 per 100,000. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5201314/&quot;&gt;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5201314/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; This statistic is strongly correlated with the abolishment of mental institutions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also don&amp;#39;t believe that people should be institutionalized indefinitely but there are people who desperately need long-term mental health care until they are stable enough to provide on their own. If we are unable to resolve the problem of health insurance in this country, the least we can do is provide government funded institutions that will take care of these patients. It is a social and moral obligation to take care of the most disadvantaged in our society, and as of now little to nothing is being done. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is obviously no ideal solution to the problem, but reopening mental institutions would at least keep these people out of the streets and in a place where they are fed and taken care of. There might be more I don&amp;#39;t know about, but I truly feel that abolishing all mental institutions in this country has been a mistake that&amp;#39;s only caused more harm than good. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is how I&amp;#39;ve come to my conclusion based on my own experiences, but I&amp;#39;m open to different perspectives that might change my view about bringing back mental institutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：對於那些沒有出售的人，美國應該有一個單獨的康復中心，專門針對與做毒品和可能擁有毒品有關的指控。]]></title><description><![CDATA[似乎很奇怪，你可以因爲吸食一種毒品而入獄幾十年。我並不
但如果這個想法真的是爲了 "康復"，那麼給人們提供一個機會，讓他們能夠重新做人，不是更有意義嗎？
讓人們有機會通過其他方式戒毒不是更有意義嗎？
而不是僅僅坐在牢房裏？難道沒有更好的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxb2sg/cmv_for_those_who_arent_selling_the_us_should/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxb2sg/cmv_for_those_who_arent_selling_the_us_should/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 22:34:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seems pretty odd that you can go to jail for decades for doing a drug. I don&amp;#39;t advocate it by any means, but if the idea is truly to &amp;quot;rehabilitate&amp;quot; wouldn&amp;#39;t it make more sense to give folks an opportunity to get clean through other means other than just sitting in a cell? Are there not better programs that could be used and funded/created to assist folks getting put of a cycle? Chances of repeat seempretty high under the current system. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I at times research how other countries deal with certain issues successfully. Perhaps other countries may have some decent alternatives as well. I&amp;#39;m all for using tax dollars to &lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;actually&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt; rehabilitate and prevent repeat cases while minimalizing time served whenever possible. A lot of folks do drugs largely due to their environment as well and not necessarily due to wanting to harm others or even themselves. I would just like to see other things tried as clearly the current system isn&amp;#39;t the best by any means. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why is the goal to punish more so than rehabilitate and help prevent future uses? A crap ton of these cases also come from impoverished communities where folks get very desperate. Could tax money not be used to build safer spots for youth to hang out and stay off the streets? Folks against spending tax dollars to improve communities would be against what tax dollars are for in the first place. Why would you not want to invest in the future? Rather than ignore or try to imprison these communities why not try to improve it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least attempt to offer safe spaces and perhaps safe transportation to it. I don&amp;#39;t know. I am just curious if folks think the current way things are handled are truly the best way? Someone could have ounces of weed and go to prison for a VEEERY long time. Meanwhile, in another state it&amp;#39;s not even an issue. Even hard drugs the idea is to punish and not help really. Put someone in box with bars does nothing to actually address the underlying behavior or upbringing that leads to folks being there in the first place and returning. There are other countries like Sweden that actually have systems in place with super low return rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are for criminals actions in general (in Sweden) and not just drugs, but the idea was to actually treat folks more human and &lt;strong&gt;actually&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt; help rehabilitate them. The way they are treated would likely shock most folks. This has actually led to jails being shut down due to not enough inmates (a good thing for society despite there being stupid private prisons that want prisoners and probably lobbying for more for profit off folk&amp;#39;s souls). Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：當我做/說一些冒犯他們的事情時，LGBTQ+社區的成員有責任通知我。我的工作不是要積極努力保持信息。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我覺得每隔一天就會有新的代名詞或聲明被宣佈爲不敏感的。
敏感。這對我來說並不是一個問題。我很高興叫別人什麼
他們想怎麼稱呼他們，就怎麼對待他們。然而，由於什麼語言是
是如此頻繁地變化，這不是我的責任......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxf1uy/cmv_it_is_the_responsibility_of_members_of_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pxf1uy/cmv_it_is_the_responsibility_of_members_of_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 22:34:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I feel like there are new pronouns or statements that are declared insensitive every other day. This isn’t a problem for me. I am happy to call people whatever they want and treat them however they want. However, since what language is acceptable is changing so frequency, it is not my responsibility to stay informed about it. I will live my life independently from yours and if my actions or words offend you then it is your job to correct me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I often see people post on social media a link to a website that explains the difference between pronouns/sexual orientations. These posters expect everyone to click on it and often shame people for not staying informed if they don’t read about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it is asking too much from people to always be aware of what is acceptable without telling people yourself. I don’t want to offend anyone, but I shouldn’t be expected to put in the work to stay informed. However, it is fair to say that I should be expected to change my behaviors if they are offensive. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another point: I am way less likely to listen to a straight person who says “Bi people don’t like to be called X, they prefer to be called Y”. If I only hear about people complaining on behalf of another community of people then I won’t value their input as much. If no bi person thinks it’s important enough to tell me then I don’t think I should listen to what straight people have to say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果你只是因爲飲食原因而喫素，那麼稱自己爲 "素食者 "是可以的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit上的大多數素食主義者會告訴你，素食主義是一種生活方式或意識形態。
你必須對動物權利感興趣才能成爲素食主義者，而且你必須非常嚴格地遵守。
它。如果你不是，那麼你就只是 "植物性"。

然而，在隨意的用法中，素食主義是指一種飲食。當人們談論到
素食主義者或...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/px7c9e/cmv_its_fine_to_call_yourself_vegan_if_youre_only/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/px7c9e/cmv_its_fine_to_call_yourself_vegan_if_youre_only/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 17:37:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most vegans on Reddit will tell you that veganism is a lifestyle or ideology. You must be into animal rights to be a vegan, and you must be very strict about it. If you aren&amp;#39;t, then you&amp;#39;re just &amp;quot;plant-based&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, in casual usage, veganism refers to a diet. When people talk about vegans or veganism gets marketed in ads and media, it&amp;#39;s always about the food. &lt;em&gt;Maybe&lt;/em&gt; you&amp;#39;ll hear that a soap or makeup product is &amp;quot;cruelty free&amp;quot; and/or &amp;quot;vegan&amp;quot;, but that&amp;#39;s usually an add on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dictionaries also refer to veganism as a diet. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You go to the average Joe on the street and they won&amp;#39;t know what they mean if you say you&amp;#39;re &amp;quot;plant based&amp;quot;. They are more likely to understand if you explain that you&amp;#39;re vegan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I obviously don&amp;#39;t personally know all the vegan celebrities, bloggers, and YouTubers out there, but I don&amp;#39;t know believe all of them are into animal rights. You only ever hear about the dietary element of veganism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of vegans are in it for health or environmentalism, not the animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, veganism is a stricter version of vegetarianism. Whether you believe in animal rights, and what &lt;em&gt;elements&lt;/em&gt; of animal rights you believe in, is up to you. With me, I can support some parts of animal rights but not others. You can be a vegan and go to zoos, you can be a vegan and buy pets, you can be a vegan and own cats, you can theoretically even be a vegan and buy leather boots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to change my view: Give me good reasons why using &amp;quot;plant-based&amp;quot; instead of &amp;quot;vegan&amp;quot; is preferable&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：投票權永遠不應該從現在的公民身上取消。]]></title><description><![CDATA[(編輯：我已經換成了臺式機，現在找不到新的帖子...如果我
如果我沒有回覆你的帖子，我很抱歉......我可能還在尋找它）。)

據我所知，在美國，你可以被剝奪選舉權（永久或臨時）的唯一方法是
暫時）的方法是。1) 犯罪 2) 債務 3) 殘疾 4) 地方...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/px3zc1/cmv_the_right_to_vote_should_never_be_removed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/px3zc1/cmv_the_right_to_vote_should_never_be_removed/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:52:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Edit: I have switched to desktop and am having trouble finding new posts...if I don&amp;#39;t reply to yours, I apologize...I&amp;#39;m probably still looking for it.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only ways I know of that you can be disenfranchised (permanently or temporarily) in the US are:
1) Crime
2) Debt
3) Disability
4) Place of residence&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of these, I can’t see any legitimate reason for them.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the cases that have potentially understandable reasoning (e.g. complete mental incapacity) would seem to have such a small impact on an election as to be negligible.  A couple of non-vetted sources estimate numbers on the scale of thousands to a couple million of Americans…less than 1% of the general population by the most recent census.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remainder of cases are by definition reasons I don’t even see the potential for legitimacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be clear, I am not referring to practices of voter suppression (preventing legal voters from legally voting).  I am referring to legally stripping a voter from their legal right to vote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I have agreed that severe mental incapacity would be a reasonable exception.
Edit: I have some homework to figure out the difference between depriving rights such as lift/liberty (capital punishment/imprisonment) and voting.
Edit: There are methods of voter suppression that amount to disenfranchisement.  In the interest of staying on topic I am avoiding encouraging discussion in that grey area and staying in clearcut &amp;quot;officially removed right to vote&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：厭惡女人的說唱音樂助長了強姦文化，與女權主義不相容。]]></title><description><![CDATA[正如維基百科上的文章 "說唱音樂中的厭女症"。
[https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Misogyny_in_rap_music]"，顯示出了在毛利
厭女症是說唱音樂的一個突出和普遍的特徵--特別是在其最流行的表現形式中。
在其最流行的表現形式中。有幾個原因可以說明這一點。
有幾個原因，這對我來說是很重要的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwngya/cmv_misogynistic_rap_music_fuels_rape_culture_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwngya/cmv_misogynistic_rap_music_fuels_rape_culture_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 02:05:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the Wikipedia article, &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Misogyny_in_rap_music&quot;&gt;Misogyny in rap music&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;quot; demonstrates in gross detail, misogyny is a prominent and prevalent feature of rap music — especially in its most popular expressions. There are several reasons why this has weighed heavily on my mind recently:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The continued dominance of rap music — including its misogynistic expressions — on the Billboard charts and among young people (even up into the 40s) suggests that American society still has a long way to go in terms of respecting women as human beings equal and not subservient to men.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Women I know and care for enjoy this music, singing/rapping right along to lyrics that degrade them and other women. This sickens me to think about.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Society is quick, on the one hand, to condemn and punish certain men who behave inappropriately toward women (as they should); yet we continue, on the other hand, to reward the powerful entertainers and media moguls who normalize misogyny, sexual assault, and rape on a mass scale. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This disconnect between the explicit cultural norms of respect/equality and the implicit norms of objectification/exploitation hinders genuine progress toward harmonious male-female relationships.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I suspect there are also significant economic consequences of this sort of male-female relational dysfunction, especially when illegitimate/unwanted pregnancies result from rampant promiscuity and rape. (The statistical links between poverty and single parenthood are well-attested.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consequently, I don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s unreasonable to suspect that popular (misogynistic) hip-hop music plays a role in the denigration, oppression, rape and even murder of women, and in the economic depression of impoverished families and communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see this as very different from the critiques of &amp;quot;edgy&amp;quot; (i.e., youth-driven) music of previous decades/generations. The onset of gangsta rap (followed by club rap) introduced a whole new ballgame. It&amp;#39;s time we stop rewarding misogynistic entertainers and media enterprises. How?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raise awareness of the misogyny in rap music by sharing info with your personal networks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stop consuming this media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In sum: You cannot be a feminist or an advocate for women while consuming anti-female media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change my mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在一段關係中，沒有任何藉口可以欺騙。]]></title><description><![CDATA[編輯：我說的是美國、加拿大和其他類似國家，不是那些
而不是那些離婚是非法的或幾乎不可能的國家。

我看不出有什麼合理的理由對配偶或男女朋友進行欺騙。
男朋友/女朋友。特別是當它涉及到婚姻時，因爲你說過你的
誓言並承諾...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwn722/cmv_there_is_no_excuse_for_cheating_in_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwn722/cmv_there_is_no_excuse_for_cheating_in_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Edit: I am talking about the USA, Canada, and other similar countries, not those where divorce is illegal or practically impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I cannot see there being a valid reason for cheating on a spouse or boyfriend/girlfriend. Especially when it comes to marriage, since you said your vows and promised yourselves to each other. I can think of a few reasons I have heard but none seem like valid arguments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person is just figuring out their sexuality. That isn’t an excuse to cheat at all. They should break up with their current boyfriend/girlfriend if they want to try other people out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are in an abusive relationship. I can’t see this as a valid argument because I don’t believe anyone needs sex so badly they are willing to cheat if they are so scared of their abusive partner they can’t just leave the relationship. You would think they would be more scared of the consequences of getting caught if their partner was truly that abusive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their partner isn’t meeting their needs. If that’s a case, find a new partner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe someone will bring up a good point I haven’t heard of of explain one of these points in a way that makes it a valid argument, but I can’t see why anyone would have an excuse to cheat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclusion: While my views definitely haven’t en entirely changed, I do see that there is basically divergent severities to cheating. Someone cheating because they are abused is more justified than other cheating, and cheating just for the thrill of it or just because you want to try out other people is far worse than cheating when you can’t leave due to kids and financial reasons. While I still don’t think anything is a good reason to not just leave the relationship, not all cheating is the same and some cheaters deserve second chances while others deserve to never find love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for the discussions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果你是非二進制的，那麼陌生人對你的性別有誤是可以的，而且完全正常。]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位AFAB的非二元朋友剛剛在Instagram上發表了一篇關於一個完全陌生的人如何在電話中對他們進行誤導的抨擊。
一個完全陌生的人在電話中誤導了他們! 然後有人迴應說
他們應該舉報這家企業，並且還分享了被陌生人誤導的故事。
被陌生人誤導的故事，以及人們認爲這是多麼可怕的事情。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwro0y/cmv_if_you_are_nonbinary_it_is_ok_and_completely/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwro0y/cmv_if_you_are_nonbinary_it_is_ok_and_completely/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 23:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;An AFAB non-binary friend just posted a tirade on Instagram about how a complete stranger misgendered them over the phone! Then someone else responded about how they should report the business and also shared stories about being misgendered by strangers and how horrible it is for people to assume gender (they also are AFAB and present quite feminine). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I get that it can be triggering if you have gender dysphoria but you just can’t expect strangers to just guess or never speak in gendered terms when it is so ingrained in our experience. I understand generally questioning why our experience and culture is so gendered but you can’t expect individual strangers to never assume gender because a small percentage of the population is non-binary. Many other issues have triggers…and you learn you are responsible for managing your own triggers (unless someone does it deliberately).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a different story when it isn’t a stranger and they are aware of your gender identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m cisgender and of course don’t really understand what it is like to be non-binary and what dysphoria is like for my friend. I respect their identity without truly understanding it. But I feel if you are going about the world with these kinds of expectations for complete strangers, you will just be angry all the time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m interested in hearing other perspectives on this to see if it changes my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cmv: 任何有喜歡按鈕的社交媒體都應該有不喜歡按鈕。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果沒有能力（在功能上）對社交媒體上的帖子進行降權或不喜歡的情況下
你就等於創造了一個環境，在這個環境中，人們可以說任何話。
他們喜歡的東西，並且幾乎只得到積極的反饋。假設你有一個人發佈
一些令人難以置信的種族主義者。雖然有一萬個人可能有...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwpl1s/cmv_any_social_media_that_has_a_like_button/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwpl1s/cmv_any_social_media_that_has_a_like_button/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 23:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without the ability to (functionally) downvote or dislike posts on social media you are in away creating an environment where people are able to say whatever they like and get almost only positive feedback. Say you have someone who posts something incredibly racist. Though 10,000 people may have seen that post, and only 100 people liked it (1%) that person still thinks that their opinion is valid because they get 100 likes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now with a dislike button the people who did not appreciate the original post are given an opportunity to basically self govern the social media site in a way. Through disliking the post they may not be changing the OP’s opinion, but anyone looking at the social media page will be able to quickly determine that the post goes against the social norm since it is heavily downvoted, making the opinion less valid, and less likely to change the way someone thinks or acts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: functional dislike button, and getting rid of “echo chamber” because I think I misused that terminology and it was taking away from my overall message&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美國的Covid疫苗接種工作實際上做得相當好。而且，疫苗接種率與已經有的其他疾病的疫苗相當。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我將盡力使之儘可能簡潔。

最近，我一直聽到有人說美國的疫苗接種工作有多麼糟糕。
由於反疫苗主義者和所有這些，美國的疫苗接種工作做得很糟糕。經常提到的是
55%的總人口接種疫苗的數字，以及它是如何像
第30屆...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwm9bw/cmv_the_united_states_is_actually_doing_a_pretty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwm9bw/cmv_the_united_states_is_actually_doing_a_pretty/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 20:34:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll try my best to keep this as succinct as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of late, I have been hearing about how terrible of a job the United States is doing with vaccinations because of anti-vaxxers and all that.  Often cited is the number of 55% of the total population vaccinated and how it is something like 30th globally in terms of population vaccination rate (cited here for example &lt;a href=&quot;https://coronavirus.jhu.edu/vaccines/international&quot;&gt;https://coronavirus.jhu.edu/vaccines/international&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, like most subjects, taking this at face-value can be misleading.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://covid.cdc.gov/covid-data-tracker/#vaccinations_vacc-total-admin-rate-total&quot;&gt;According to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;, yes only 55% are fully vaccinated, &lt;em&gt;relative to the total population.&lt;/em&gt;  Not all vaccines are available to the entire population.  For instance, none of the vaccines are yet available for people under 12.  When you look a bit closer at the numbers, they actually look pretty good.  These few stand out to me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;93.5% of people 65 and older have received at least one dose.  This is the group of people most prone to the virus too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;77% of people 18 and older have received at least one dose&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;390 million doses administered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;471 million doses delivered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think it is unreasonable to assume that the vast majority of people who have received at least one dose will get the second dose.  There are always exceptions of course, but for the sake of argument I don&amp;#39;t think those exceptions will change the numbers drastically.  Assuming this, within the next X months, 77% of the adult population will be vaccinated fully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;471 million doses delivered in 10-ish months from when the vaccines were first deployed is pretty dang amazing.  Not to mention, the USA has donated another &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/09/covid-us-is-the-worlds-largest-donor-of-vaccines-data-shows.html&quot;&gt;100 million&lt;/a&gt; doses globally and plan to donate another &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-vaccine-us-donation-500-million-pfizer-doses-global-supply/&quot;&gt;500 million&lt;/a&gt; in the coming year.  Yes, relative to population, USA might be lower than some nations.  However, in terms of gross vaccines administered, the USA is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2021/world/covid-vaccinations-tracker.html&quot;&gt;third globally in terms of total doses administered&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On top of that, &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.gallup.com/poll/353081/one-five-americans-remain-vaccine-resistant.aspx&quot;&gt;this study&lt;/a&gt; from August states that only 18% of Americans are dead set against the vaccine.  There is still a percentage of people planning on getting the vaccine and people who are open to changing their opinion on not getting the vaccine.  Assuming just a few percent of those planning or willing to change their stance get vaccinated, we could see an 80%+ vaccination rate in the USA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, no vaccine ever gets administered to 100% of the population.  It is folly to think the Covid vaccine is any different.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://usafacts.org/articles/data-centric-look-vaccines-and-immunizations-united-states/&quot;&gt;According to this article&lt;/a&gt;, the highest vaccination rates in the USA are MMR and Polio which are roughly 91%.  Many vaccines hover around the 80% mark which is what is seems the Covid vaccine is tending toward.  Some are only around 50% (flu).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to shed some light on this issue, share some ideas that are not often discussed for whatever reason, and take a look at some numbers a little bit more in depth than a 10 second news clip would lead us all to believe.  Very rarely, is it ever a good idea to look &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; at relative percentages or &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; gross values.  Often, you need to look at both to get the complete picture of what&amp;#39;s happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok Reddit, I posted my view.  Time to tear it up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: added total dosage link and use some less polarized wording.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：住宅應該只賣給個人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，人類夥伴們，這將是一個有爭議的問題，所以我將詳細說明問題和計劃。
問題和計劃。

問題：大筆資金正在購買房產，直接與普通人競爭。
競爭，因爲他們不可能。正常公民被限制購買
基於他們的個人收入的房產；持有...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwithn/cmv_residential_homes_should_only_be_sold_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwithn/cmv_residential_homes_should_only_be_sold_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:46:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alright fellow humans this will be a contentious one so I&amp;#39;m going to detail the problem and the plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Problem: Big money is buying up properties, competing directly with normal people who couldn&amp;#39;t possibly. Normal citizens are restricted to buying properties based on their personal income; holdings and properties can be used for collateral, but the mortgage/purchase price of a home is generally directly proportional to their personal taxable income (for example, I own 1-2M+ in assets, but I can&amp;#39;t get a mortgage because at the moment my income is 0). This situation results in major inequality and eventually the endgame is businesses own most residential and everyone else rents. That is terrible for an economy and a middle class. Rent is also sky-high across the country, increasing faster than wages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My solution: Individuals are able to purchase as much land/as many residential properties as they want, however their total property purchasing ability is based on a 2-3 years average of taxable income. So, even if you have the assets to buy a property cash, you need to have your taxable income at a certain point to even qualify for the purchase, and if you&amp;#39;re over the total limit, tough luck, go buy another asset. Homes are too important to sell to the highest bidder. Individuals would also be able to rent out those properties, however (and this is a separate post) the amount should be heavily rent controlled. So landlords don&amp;#39;t necessarily go away, but the market is freed up and the rent controlled. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Businesses would not be allowed to purchase residential properties any more. They would still be able to do business and entertainment properties. Existing residential properties are purchased from the companies at retail cost. This has precedent; it just happened in Germany, and Trump seized several properties for his Border Wall. Seizing property for the greater good is acceptable already. Any large business-owned apartment buildings would then be partially owned by each tenant, and HOA would govern each building, sharing costs and profits. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This would result in a few benefits, and I don&amp;#39;t see a con.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-More regular people would own property, improving the vitality of the middle class and reducing income inequality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Rich individuals would have to increase their taxable income (and pay more tax) to be able to take their advantage on the situation. They are still rewarded for having higher incomes as they can purchase larger/more homes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Businesses won&amp;#39;t be able to corner the market and exploit people who live cheque to cheque.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could change my view by showing me a major flaw that actually results in worse situation for the regular people. I do not believe businesses should have the right to buy whatever they want just because they have the money so that won&amp;#39;t change it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Let&amp;#39;s use the USA as an example&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 堵塞高速公路/主要道路的氣候變化抗議者會適得其反]]></title><description><![CDATA[每隔幾天，英國的新聞就會報道在主要道路/高速公路上發生的逮捕事件。
因爲氣候變化活動家阻擋了道路/高速公路。這似乎是
這似乎是他們抗議的一種常見方式，在我看來，這是適得其反。

顯然，我很關心環境，但作爲一個司機，如果...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwfp6f/cmv_climate_change_protesters_who_block/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwfp6f/cmv_climate_change_protesters_who_block/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 15:39:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every few days the UK news shares about arrests taking place on major roads/motorways because of climate change activists blocking them. This seems to be a common way for them to protest and in my opinion it’s counterproductive. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do care about the environment obviously, but as a driver myself, if I couldn’t get to work or wherever I was going because of people laying on the motorway, that would only make me more hateful towards the cause. Unfortunately car travel for some is essential albeit damaging to the environment, those people are not to blame for the crisis and are being stopped from going about their day, could risk their job etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t bring attention to the problem I don’t think, it just causes delays and ruins peoples moods, I don’t think any of the motorists sat in traffic are deciding to ditch the car and become green. There are other forms of protest that are less distributive that would work better IMO, but it’s also not us that need targeting, it’s corporations, the government etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：性工作應該非刑事化而不是合法化]]></title><description><![CDATA[有很多理由不應該將性工作合法化。人們說這與其他工作沒有什麼不同
與麥當勞等其他工作沒有區別，但我們知道這不是
真實的。一張你爲別人點菜的照片可能不會傷害你的
而你的裸體照片會傷害你的未來。你總是聽到關於如何...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwd4wg/cmv_sex_work_should_be_decriminalized_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pwd4wg/cmv_sex_work_should_be_decriminalized_not/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 14:34:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are many reason sex work shouldn’t be legalized. People say it’s no different than working any other job such as McDonald’s but we know that’s not true. A picture of you taking someone’s order probably isn’t going to hurt your future while a picture of you naked will. You always hear about how empowering and glamorous the porn industry is but it’s always by the top paid performers which are the loudest voices, and not much about the drugs, abuse and STDs. Look at the porn industry which is legal and how much craziness is going on there. It would also just create huge contradictions about how we want our society to be. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I don’t think it should be legal. Still I think it should be decriminalized and sex work should not hurt the sex worker. At most I think they should be fined but also provided resources on how to leave that life and health resources too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：要解決住房危機，我們應該打破房地產帝國，限制任何一個人/實體可以擁有的房屋數量。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果我們打碎房地產帝國，並對個人和公司可以擁有的房屋數量設置上限
個人和公司可以擁有的房屋數量，這將迫使他們出售，並推動房價回落到現實世界。
價格回落到真實世界，同時向需要的人開放住房。
- 爲什麼不給個人設定上限，比如說，5套房子（慷慨地）--更小的房地產...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pw6k5o/cmv_to_solve_the_housing_crisis_we_should_just/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pw6k5o/cmv_to_solve_the_housing_crisis_we_should_just/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 03:32:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we broke up real estate empires and capped the number of homes that individuals and companies can own, it would force them to sell and drive the prices back down to real-world, while opening up housing to people who need it.
- Why not cap individuals at say, 5 homes (generously)
- Smaller real estate companies could own, say, 20-50 and be taxed at a smaller rate
- Cap the size of large real-estate companies to prevent them from amassing thousands of homes
- Titrate the limits over say 5-10 years to allow staggered sell-off
- Institute a nation-wide property tax on someone&amp;#39;s 4th or more home (who needs more than a house, a summer, and a winter house) that funds first-time mortgages &amp;amp; housing assistance 
- Obviously do more to cap AirBnB whales
- Ban foreign countries/entities from buying investment real estate in the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s so disheartening that this isn&amp;#39;t the national conversation. Both dems and gop both either say:
&amp;quot;We should just eliminate single-family zoning to build giant condos&amp;quot;
   or...
&amp;quot;We should expand urban boundary lines and build more&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My point is, there are already enough homes in the country (assuming this as common knowledge). The problem is, no one can afford them, or they never get back on the market. You can &lt;em&gt;try&lt;/em&gt; to legislate price/rent control but it&amp;#39;s not going to work everywhere or last. Urban boundary lines likewise exist to protect any number of things, such as habitats, traffic, distribution, and general quality of life (not to mention climate change). And, as someone in a raging gentrification zone myself, I don&amp;#39;t see the efficacy of building condos that working-class people can&amp;#39;t afford, driving up prices even more, and pricing families out of their homes. There are a lot of ways to label housing as &amp;quot;low-income&amp;quot; but really not have it be affordable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The general point is, tons of companies have hoovered up mass quantities of homes (of all kinds and sizes) and will never, ever turn around and say &amp;quot;Hey, family of 3 who needs a starter, let me sell you this at a fair price.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using market forces, force a sell-off and re-circulate the homes that are being hoarded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open to any and all discussion, thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：社交媒體造成的問題多於它的價值]]></title><description><![CDATA[將社交媒體定義爲Facebook、Instagram、Tiktok和任何其他平臺
其中面孔/身份與似乎是真實的人聯繫在一起。

社交媒體使人們能夠進行遠距離交流，分享故事。
併爲那些在其他方面過於遙遠或 "不同 "的人提供聯繫。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvwycj/cmv_social_media_causes_more_problems_than_its/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvwycj/cmv_social_media_causes_more_problems_than_its/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 02:38:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Defining social media as Facebook, Instagram, Tiktok, and any other platform where faces/identities are tied to what seems to be actual people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social media allows people to communicate over long distances, share stories, and offers connection to those otherwise too remote or “different” in their communities. These are known positives, but I believe the following negatives make social media dangerous as it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the use of filters, photoshop and other technologies that change the appearance of individuals in photos and videos creates unrealistic and unattainable beauty standards, leading to negative self-image, eating disorders, mental health issues such as depression and body dysmorphia, and is generally harmful. Instagram influencers and celebrities profit off of this — see “that family that starts with a K” as evidence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the algorithms used on Facebook for news promotes disinformation. This disinformation is legitimized, though, because it seems “real”. Since this information is sent by people in a person’s group, or by someone they are following, they trust it. From vaccines making your skin magnetic, to giant space lasers orchestrated by a certain minority group, if it comes packaged as a news article, people will believe it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the algorithms create “bubbles” where people are generally presented with the information that feeds their general viewpoints, in effect creating an echo chamber. This makes people think that their views are correct, that most people agree with them, and discourages critical thinking. It also impedes healthy conversation and debate with people who hold different viewpoints.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the “bubbles” also create an “us vs. them” mentality, and de-humanizes people who hold differing viewpoints. For example, protesters are labelled as “animals”. People are categorized as being less intelligent or overall less worthy for coexistence. Middle ground, agreeing to disagree, learning to accept differences and worth collaboratively are seriously eroded by social media. There’s also a degree of anonymity which increases online bullying and trolling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bots and paid shills and paid trolls obscure how people really feel, and are becoming more difficult to parse. This means those 12,000 people who are part of a certain Facebook group agreeing about something might actually be 10 people and 11,990 bots and trolls. This in turn emboldens the “us vs. them” mentality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need to seriously revamp social media and label things for what they are. Pics should say if they’ve been digitally altered, news and information should be fact checked by an set of independent checkers, algorithms need to be upgraded so that conflicting viewpoints are presented.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：爲了生活而工作/每週40小時的工作，其實並沒有什麼錯誤和可怕的地方。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我聽到/看到很多人在談論人們必須爲生活而工作是多麼的荒謬。
爲了生活而工作是多麼可笑。自人類誕生之初，我們就不得不爲生存而工作。
無論是在田間勞作以獲取食物，還是在一些不那麼直接的事情上
與生活直接相關的事情。所有的動物都必須工作和狩獵，以...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvkg56/cmv_theres_nothing_really_wrong_and_terrible/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvkg56/cmv_theres_nothing_really_wrong_and_terrible/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:38:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve heard/seen lots of people talk about how it’s ridiculous that people have to work just to live. Since the very beginning of humans, we have had to work to survive - whether this was working the fields for food or something less directly connected to living. All animals have to work and hunt to be able to live, it seems to me that that is the natural order of things. Though I absolutely think if/when it is achievable it would be awesome to not have to work to live, I don’t understand the outrage and the idea that this isn’t the most normal way for things to be - e.g people that say that the government should cover all the basics like food, water, and shelter to an extent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：資本主義做法正在嚴重地對社會造成負面的心理健康影響。]]></title><description><![CDATA[編輯：消費主義的做法可能更貼切--在我的腦子裏，它們有點像
一樣的。

我一直在努力解決這個問題，這有點複雜。
但我會盡力把它分爲幾個段落
觀點，供你參考。

一切...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvsvkp/cmv_capitalist_practices_are_seriously_causing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvsvkp/cmv_capitalist_practices_are_seriously_causing/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 15:41:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDIT : Consumerist practices is probably more apt - in my head they kinda went one and the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understand that I’v been trying to come to terms with this issue and it’s a bit complicated - but I’ll do my best to keep it kind of sectioned into paragraphs with points for you to CMV on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything in society feels as though it’s geared to make you spend money - &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If something gives you pleasure - there will always be a company to make you feel like you’re missing out and need to buy more to enjoy it fully. This is mainly in the realm of media for me - think Disney “You like marvel movies? - here’s a new one pay this premium price to see the new one.”, new games, “like Pokémon? Make sure you buy the newest games to get the latest and greatest” etc. Of course you can always choose to not buy into the hype. Get the show or game later. But then -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social media - perhaps just media in general - there seems to be a trend to me - of constant posts/ memes etc on all accounts relating to these newest shows/games etc. If you’re not with latest - you’re kind of “excluded” because your not in the loop. I know that a lot of these posts etc may be sponsored content or viral marketing - but that paired with adverts etc can cause a feeling of exclusion within society (or at least your bubble)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to this is advertising - just in general - isn’t the base aim of an advert to make you feel like you’re lacking or not enough - and you should buy this product to feel better. Be it something to make you look better or feel better - or try this limited edition whatever (the base idea of a limited edition anything is to create scarcity and cause fear that you will miss out to induce a purchase). Every food company has limited edition flavours - shoes have limited edition sneakers - every product category I can think of does this - and it can all kind of culminate - &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If something gives you pleasure - the company behind it will always try to find a way to milk your happiness for money - and with the advent of subscription services this is feeling almost like a literal milking sometimes. Do you like Mario? Prove it. Buy the Mario shirt - and cereal - see the movie - get the limited edition Mario branded console and don’t forget you like Levis jeans and Mario and Levi’s are now doing a limited edition collab - you might miss out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR; Everything in my life feels soured and tainted by advertising and capitalism. I no longer can find any way to enjoy things because there’s a cynical advertising executive in my head who points out all the ways I’m being marketed to and to like or enjoy something is just giving companies a new way to exploit you. Please try and change my view if only for my ability to find pleasure in something again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我把美國Covid-19大流行的現狀完全歸咎於反免疫者和反面具者。]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至本帖發表時，美國現在每天約有2000人死於
Covid-19造成的。自3月以來，我們還沒有看到每天有這麼多的死亡，而且隨着
隨着病毒的delta變體的傳播，我們正在開始倒退，因爲
就克服這種大流行病而言，我們開始倒退。我們開始回到...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvugat/cmv_i_solely_blame_the_current_state_of_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvugat/cmv_i_solely_blame_the_current_state_of_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 15:41:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of the creation of this post, the US now sees about 2000 deaths per day due to Covid-19. We haven’t seen this many deaths per day since March, and with the delta variant of the virus spreading, we’re starting to regress as far as getting over this pandemic is concerned. We’re starting to go back to the point where schools are closing again, businesses are being forced to limit themselves and the people they serve, mask mandates, basically we’re going back to the kind of limitations and restrictions that we had to work around with during the beginning stages of the pandemic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The culprit behind the rise in Covid-19 cases, deaths, and the subsequent reactions is due to the tens of millions of people that refuse to get the Covid-19 vaccine and refuse to wear a mask in settings where they’re around multiple people. The vast majority of people being hospitalized and dying of Covid-19 are unvaccinated, and now it’s getting to the point where they’ve overburdened hospital’s quite badly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So with that being said, I completely blame every anti-vaxxer and anti-masker for the current state of the pandemic. This is all their fault. If these people had just worn masks like they were told to without being stubborn assholes and gotten the vaccine months ago when they became widely available, this pandemic would have been greatly reduced and we would be on the back end of it, perhaps even eliminating it. Every person that refuses the vaccine and doesn’t wear a mask when required to is part of the problem, and I’m tired of pretending that they have a point or could be half right. They’re making everything worse for all of us and holding us back from beating this God awful pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 在確定一個人有多大的特權時，膚色起着相當小的作用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，我不是什麼憤怒的白人（遠非如此），但在我看來。
一個人的膚色在決定一個人的特權時起着相當小的作用。

很多特權來自於某人擁有的幫助他們過上充實生活的各種手段。
充實的生活。一個身體健康的有色人種，有很高的文化修養，有很強的社會責任感。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvnjye/cmv_skin_color_plays_a_pretty_minor_role_when/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvnjye/cmv_skin_color_plays_a_pretty_minor_role_when/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 11:39:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For starters I am not some angry white guy (far from it) but in my opinion, someone&amp;#39;s skin color plays a fairly minor role when determining one&amp;#39;s privilege.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of privilege comes from the types of means someone has to help them live a fulfilling life. A person of color who is able-bodied, highly educated, does not have medical struggles, lives in an urban setting with easy access to all the modern commodities, and is an executive at a large company is certainly more privileged than a straight white male living in a trailer in some random backwoods part of Appalachia with little to no education, is hooked on drugs, has loads of red flags concerning his health, never left his county since birth, and can&amp;#39;t seem to get any source of income in spite of the former not being white and latter being Caucasian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And above isn&amp;#39;t just some pulling from straws comparison, there are many non-white people in America who enjoy much higher living standards and quality of life than white people depending on other aspects of their living&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not denying that skin color is part of the equation but it&amp;#39;s only one of many many things that determines how &amp;quot;privileged&amp;quot; an individual is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美國應該有稅收資助的醫療保健]]></title><description><![CDATA[1）除了美國之外，還有許多其他國家也有。

2）目前它太貴了。花幾百塊錢得到一個診斷是
荒謬的

"但我的個人主義"

這種說法讓我很惱火。我們是否應該剝奪警察的權利，迫使你自力更生？
自己，因爲你有那麼多的隱私？

另外，只是因爲...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvh0l8/cmv_america_should_have_tax_funded_healthcare/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvh0l8/cmv_america_should_have_tax_funded_healthcare/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:52:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;1) So many other countries have it besides the US&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) It’s way too expensive currently. Paying hundreds to get a diagnosis is ridiculous &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But my individualism”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This argument annoys me. Should we take away police and force you to fend for yourself since you live privacy so much?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, just because you an afford something doesn’t mean everybody else can. Not everybody can afford healthcare. And if it’s possible that we can make it universal to lower the cost, let’s do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Higher taxes”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Money isn’t more valuable than human lives. Weird how Americans love their superheroes so much, yet they’re willing to prioritize money over human lives. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“it’s unfair for the doctors”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But they’re still getting paid. Just by the government&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Wait times”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d rather wait 6 hours for an appointment than have to possibly go into debt to get a diagnosis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 延長付款期限應該被廢除。它們是目前經濟中的一股強大力量，但沒有人談論它們。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我將快速解釋它們是如何工作的，然後提供一個快速的論證，論證爲什麼你
應該關心這個問題。

首先，我不是一個經濟學家或會計師，我是一個在大公司工作的商業領袖。
我是一個在大公司工作的企業領導，他通過觀察發生在我身邊的事情得出了一些結論。
我是一個在大公司工作的企業領導，通過觀察世界一角發生的事情得出了一些結論，並且已經...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pv8mqo/cmv_extended_payment_terms_should_be_abolished/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pv8mqo/cmv_extended_payment_terms_should_be_abolished/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 23:30:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ll explain quickly how they work then offer a quick syllogism arguing why you should care about this issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I’m not an economist or an accountant, I’m a business leader working in a large corporation who has drawn some conclusions watching what happens in my corner of the world and has done a little research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A large corporation that has lots of leverage over its vendors simultaneously negotiates the shortest possible payment terms (when one party actually has to pay another) for all of its receivables and the longest possible payment terms for its payables. Doing so adds to free cash flow, a key metric Wall Street looks at to determine the health of a business- it is how much money the business has to spend on stuff at any moment. If you are a small business with the capital to float all of your expenses (or the ability to borrow to cover them) while you wait four months to get paid for the service or good you provided your customer (the large corporation), then you can play ball. Almost invariably you will include your cost of borrowing in your bid- and there’s the rub, as the large corporation you actually pay more in the long run because the cost of borrowing for the little guy (almost certainly more than the big guy) gets added into the cost of the contract. On the other hand, if you’re a small business who can’t wait four months to get paid you are excluded from the potential work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extended payment terms hurt small businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Numerous taxpayer funded programs and tax credits exist to prop up small businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Small businesses could be made healthier as a result of dialogue/legislation around this issue and consequently less reliant on this taxpayer funded backstop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are a taxpayer and/or you benefit from taxpayer funded stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore you should care about this issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: To rearrange first sentence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 在互聯網接入廣泛的國家，高中應該有一個所有學生都需要參加的強制性 "互聯網知識入門 "課程。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我認爲，爲什麼人們往往最終會在互聯網上給對方造成如此多的
的壓力、痛苦和其他不良情緒，往往是因爲在某種程度上
在某種程度上，沒有一本我們都在操作的手冊，如果我們用公共的
如果我們用公共教育來建立一個互聯網知識的基線水平...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvew60/cmv_highschools_in_nations_with_wide_internet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pvew60/cmv_highschools_in_nations_with_wide_internet/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 23:30:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think a large degree of why people often end up causing each other so much stress, anguish, and other ill feelings on the internet is often because to some degree there is no handbook that we&amp;#39;re all operating out of, if we used public education to establish a baseline level of internet knowledge and behavior then it would help give us a communal touchstone to work from and thus arguments/discussions/interactions would be less likely to engender bad feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The class could cover such important topics as...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1: Recognizing a troll and knowing when to disengage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2: Phishing scams or why there isn&amp;#39;t a Nigerian prince who needs your money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3: Cancel Culture, the internet is forever, and why you should consider reviewing your own posting history every five years before someone else does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4: Poe&amp;#39;s Law, or why it isn&amp;#39;t other people&amp;#39;s fault if they can&amp;#39;t tell you were being sarcastic if you did not expressly declare your sarcastic intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5: Hunbots or why MLMs are just Pyramid Schemes that you end up investing your time into as well as your money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6: Catfishing and the importance of &amp;quot;trust but verify.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7: Echo chambers, media presentation algorithms and how the internet will make your political views the worst versions of themselves if you&amp;#39;re not careful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:  How to help your parents/grandparents/relatives set up their email accounts and also avoid getting sucked down one of the internets rabbit holes....&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By covering important topics like these in a school setting society can better prepare children for their futures/present interactions with the internet and raise a generation of internet users who are less likely to suffer the possible negative effects of the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To change my view you&amp;#39;d need to prove that either such a class already exists, isn&amp;#39;t necessary as this knowledge is already being provided in another uniform setting,  or that such a class wouldn&amp;#39;t be effective at teaching high-school level children this information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[META: 關於第5條的簡要說明]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們對第5條規則的刪除信息一直不明確，而且經常被誤解。
長時間以來，我們正在對其進行修訂。以前的內容是

> 評論必須對對話做出有意義的貢獻。評論如果是
> 只有鏈接、笑話或 "書面加註 "的評論將被刪除。幽默和肯定
>的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pv79q7/meta_a_brief_clarification_on_rule_5/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pv79q7/meta_a_brief_clarification_on_rule_5/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 19:30:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our removal message for rule 5 has been unclear and frequently misunderstood for too long, so we are revising it. Previously it read:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comments must contribute meaningfully to the conversation. Comments that are only links, jokes or &amp;quot;written upvotes&amp;quot; will be removed. Humor and affirmations of agreement can be contained within more substantial comments. See the wiki page for more information.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But as of today it will now read  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comments should be on-topic, serious, and contain enough content to move the discussion forward. Jokes, contradictions without explanation, links without context, and &amp;quot;written upvotes&amp;quot; will be removed. Read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules#wiki_rule_5&quot;&gt;the wiki&lt;/a&gt; for more information.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What rule 5 is and is not for&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of rule 5 is to make sure that discussion is on topic and that meaningful progress is being made within conversations at all time. The aim is to increase the signal-to-noise ratio. Most comments that are removed fall under one of a few categories:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contradictions - just saying &amp;quot;you are wrong&amp;quot; without any expansion on why they are wrong doesn&amp;#39;t help further anyone&amp;#39;s understanding.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jokes - humour is permitted, but a joke doesn&amp;#39;t in of itself warrant a comment. It creates distracting, off-topic fluff that doesn&amp;#39;t contribute to changing OP&amp;#39;s view&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Non-sequiturs - wildly off-topic comments that don&amp;#39;t pertain to anything being discussed in any way.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Link dumps - unless it&amp;#39;s extremely obvious from conversation context &lt;em&gt;exactly&lt;/em&gt; what is contained within the link, you should explain why the link is relevant, and what the most important parts are if any&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simple affirmations of agreement - the upvote button exists. Adding a comment just to state that you agree without re-emphasising any specific points or making expansions again just adds noise and doesn&amp;#39;t help change views&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to be clear, the following does not constitute a violation of rule 5&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Politeness - for instance, thanking someone for giving you a delta&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humour contained within substantive comments - the wild examples CMV commenters come up with when arguing &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reductio_ad_absurdum&quot;&gt;reductio ad absurdum&lt;/a&gt; not only make me smile, but are also good persuasive devices. The more absurd the better when trying to illustrate why certain logic is faulty.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information, take a look at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules#wiki_rule_5&quot;&gt;the wiki&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any thoughts on how we moderate, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/ideasforcmv&quot;&gt;r/ideasforcmv&lt;/a&gt; is open as ever and will pretty much always receive a response from at least one mod. Alternately if you have feedback, feel free to express it civilly in this thread, we&amp;#39;re always looking to improve how we run things. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, thank you as ever for making this place great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 9/10 在發佈日購買全新的iPhone 13的人絕不會注意到，如果你把每個內部組件都換成iPhone 8的組件。]]></title><description><![CDATA[CMV：蘋果公司的營銷非常有殺傷力，他們有數百萬的 "終身客戶"
資助這些設備，而這些設備爲他們提供的性能價值升級爲零。如果
如果你更換了新iPhone的每一個部件，除了外觀之外
9/10的人購買他們不會注意到，而且會......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pv5lgb/cmv_910_people_buying_the_brand_new_iphone_13_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pv5lgb/cmv_910_people_buying_the_brand_new_iphone_13_on/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 15:40:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CMV: Apple&amp;#39;s marketing is so killer they have millions of &amp;quot;lifetime customers&amp;quot; financing these devices which provide 0 performance value upgrade to them.  If you replaced every single component of a new iPhone other than the exterior appearance, 9/10 people buying them would not notice, and would happily trade the device in without complaint for the iPhone 14 or 15, when that time comes in a year or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friends and I played Tetris and messed with/created other text-based games in secret on TI-83 calculators in High School.  Now the vast majority of these folks lined up to spend $1k+ have no clue how any of the tech works or where it came from, and totally take it for granted.  To me,  I see the &amp;quot;normies&amp;quot;  and &amp;quot;jocks&amp;quot; that would have made fun of us at the table 20 years ago, paying nerds an extra $X amount monthly for something they don&amp;#39;t even use or understand. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s the same phenomenon at the car dealership, no gritty hardened race car drivers walk in and buy the beast on the lot, it&amp;#39;s generally someone geriatric who made their money in banking and can&amp;#39;t even drive a stick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I get it if you say you like the iPhone for it&amp;#39;s sleek design and you have the money to upgrade, but that&amp;#39;s really not the case for most of these folks.  They are in a blind trade-up cycle.  The 1 in 10 is the aficionados and geeks who &amp;quot;have to get their hands on it.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：波巴-費特（至少在原三部曲中出現的時候）是《星球大戰》中最被高估的角色]]></title><description><![CDATA[讓我指出，我是一個星球大戰的超級粉絲，至少當涉及到
迪斯尼典籍。我看過所有的節目，玩過所有的遊戲，定期重看每一部電影，甚至還讀過幾本書。
電影，甚至還讀過幾本書。

在這種情況下，我覺得我可以肯定地說，波巴-費特是
是最...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pv630v/cmv_boba_fett_at_least_as_he_appears_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pv630v/cmv_boba_fett_at_least_as_he_appears_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 15:40:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let me point out that I am a Star Wars super-fan, at least when it comes to the Disney canon. I&amp;#39;ve seen every show, played every game, regularly rewatch every movie, and have even read a couple of the books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being the case, I feel that I can definitively say that Boba Fett is the most overrated character in the entire canon. Don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, I don&amp;#39;t dislike him by any means, but he isn&amp;#39;t nearly as cool as people make him out to be. Here are some of the most common arguments I hear:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;He&amp;#39;s one of the greatest bounty hunters in the galaxy!&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yeah, so great that in the two movies in which he appears (in the OT) he doesn&amp;#39;t kill a single person, barely fires his blaster at all, and gets eaten by a sarlaac when his jetpack stops working. The only thing he does of any note at all in the original trilogy is tattle to Vader that the Falcon is headed to Bespin. *insert cheems image here*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;He&amp;#39;s such an interesting character!&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;His dad died in front of him. Wowee. Not like we&amp;#39;ve ever seen a more interesting character lose their parent figures before. *cough*Anakin, Luke, Rey, etc*cough*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But he was so badass in The Mandalorian!&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yes, he was, I agree! I think The Mandalorian was the first time that Boba could ever conceivably have been called badass. But people have been calling him a badass and iconic since the 80s, which I don&amp;#39;t think is vindicated by a show in 2020 retroactively making him a cool guy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[insert piece of no-longer-canon Legends media that develops his character]&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Might be a controversial take, but Legends was such a far-reaching and frankly jumbled mess of plotlines that it may as well have been an expanded universe of fanfiction, and I think Disney simplifying the canon in the way it did was helpful for making the universe feel more cohesive. So the only argument I&amp;#39;ll accept on this point is pointing to something in the current canon, but even still, again, that media can only be newer than 2012.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll consider my mind changed if you can point to a canon reason that Boba Fett has been so beloved for more than four decades. Because as it stands now, in the original trilogy Boba was about as badass as Salacious Crumb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：爲什麼男性問題沒有得到關注，至少有一部分原因是由於男性團體的存在。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這個標題可能聽起來很奇怪，但請允許我解釋一下。

作爲一個男人，有很多社會問題影響着男人，例如
家庭和刑事法庭中的偏見，無家可歸，更多的成功壓力，更少的對各種疾病的支持等等。
對各種弊病的支持較少，等等。這些問題沒有得到（積極）的
關注...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pv4a43/cmv_at_least_part_of_the_reason_of_why_mens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pv4a43/cmv_at_least_part_of_the_reason_of_why_mens/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 14:32:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The title may sound weird, but allow me to explain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking as a man, there are a lot of societal issues that affect men, such as bias in family and criminal courts, homelessness, more pressure to sucess, less support for a variety of ills,etc. These issues do not receive the (positive) attention they need to be adressed. However, the behaviour of men´s groups like MRAs, MGTOWs and Incels does &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; help matters at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lowest hanging fruit to critic are Incels and MGTOWs. These are utter jokes at best and echo-chambers of misogyny and downright pseudoscience (redpill, blackpill, bitemyasspill) at worst. Incels have downright spawned a few mass-murderers. Complain about feminist how much you like, I never heard of a feminist spree-killer.Needless to say, not many people are going to be receptive towards helping with male issues when they are forefronted by those types.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MRAs are much more reasonable, and actually occasionally bring valid issues. But their rhetoric is highly flawed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-They focus heavily on competing with, opposing and discrediting feminism instead of actual male issues (and even blame male issues on feminism).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-MRAs rarely offer solutions to male issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Focus on bogus issues like conscription (the USA has no true conscription since vietnam and is extremely unlikely to actually start to draft people again in any foresable future) comparing circumcision with FGM ( is simply not remotely comparable from an anatomical and medical perspective), and women getting free drinks and favors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Misogyny. Just as much, if not much more, than there is misandry in feminism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Identifing with conservatives, despite the fact that a lot men´s issues can be solved with progressive policies (cultural biases and pressures can be solved with cultural debate and change, legal issues with a reformed and more lenient judicial system, etc)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, there is that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 一個 "勤工儉學 "計劃，讓活躍的吸毒者得到住房、食物和他們的DOC來學習/工作，將是解決我們的精神健康/無家可歸禍害的一個好辦法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[正如任何曾經或認識的癮君子一樣，對他們來說，除了下一次的興奮，什麼都不重要。
高。像房租/賬單/食物這樣的事情可能是切碎的肝臟。一旦這些人
一旦這些人在街上被絞死，麻煩就開始了。

如果我們能夠爲海洛因成癮者啓動一個職業項目，等等。他們可以...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/puqq7n/cmv_a_workstudy_program_where_active_addicts_get/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/puqq7n/cmv_a_workstudy_program_where_active_addicts_get/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 08:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As anyone who has been or known an addict, nothing matters to them but that next high. Things like rent/bills/food might as well be chopped liver. Once these people are strung-out on the streets is where the trouble starts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we could start a vocational program for heroin addicts, etc. They could get small doses of H in a controlled settings to &amp;quot;get them through&amp;quot; to study and care about something. Perhaps integrate the H into a counseling course or two. Of course, you would want to wean them off somehow when it comes to actually working them, but could it be a start? Maybe focus on industries that don&amp;#39;t involve heavy machinery?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：制定適當的最低工資標準，而不是執行 "小費 "文化。]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天早些時候，我偶然發現了一個關於美國小費文化的對話。
我個人認爲這很荒謬。意料之中的是，大多數美國人
都支持小費，並以低級趣味爭論說
如果顧客付不起小費，就應該完全避免外出就餐。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pumx0q/cmv_institute_a_proper_minimum_wage_rather_than/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pumx0q/cmv_institute_a_proper_minimum_wage_rather_than/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 18:30:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I earlier today stumbled on a conversation about the tipping culture in America, which I personally consider ridiculous. Expectedly, most Americans that contributed to the topic, were pro-tipping, and argued in poor taste, that eating out should be avoided in its entirety if a customer cannot afford a 20% tip at minimum - ludicrous. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe the vigour with which tipping is being propped up, should rather be used to push for a reasonable wage culture that ensures Servers gets handsomely rewarded, thus making tipping optional from anyone based on the quality of service received. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TLDR:&lt;/strong&gt; Employers should bear the full brunt of wage responsibilites rather than perfomatively coerce customers into susidizing employee income via tips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美國聯邦政府應建立一個框架，對發生數據泄露的組織進行財政處罰]]></title><description><![CDATA[美國有一個債務問題和一個數據安全問題，我認爲
有一個互利的解決方案：對有數據泄露的公司和機構進行嚴重的財務處罰。
對那些發生數據泄露的公司和機構進行嚴厲的財務處罰。我們有一個系統性的
我們有一個系統性的數據泄露事件，在美國的所有部門和組織中重複發生。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/puni86/cmv_the_us_federal_government_should_institute_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/puni86/cmv_the_us_federal_government_should_institute_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 18:30:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States has a debt problem and a data security problem that I believe have a mutually beneficial solution: severe financial ramifications for companies and institutions that have data breaches. We have a systemic reoccurrence of data breaches across all sectors in the US and organizations and companies face no serious consequences for their indiscretions. Class action lawsuits ultimately amount to a slap on the wrist and offer no tangible benefits to customers whose data was stolen.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Large fines for corporations that have data breaches would increase interest in data security as a deterrent to avoid fines. It would also provide a revenue source to offset the federal deficit when fines are levied. The goal would be to reduce breaches which would eventually also reduce federal income from fines if companies took this seriously, but that is a good thing.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is an example: T-Mobile is currently facing a class action lawsuit for a 70+ million customer record breach. That lawsuit will drag out for years and customers who were affected will ultimately get a fat check for $2.50 while the lawyers will get a third of the settlement. No real tangible benefit to consumers, no serious ramifications to t-mobile, and data breaches continue. If the fine from the federal government was something like $700m it would be a serious deterrent to allowing data breaches in the future. Garnish T-mobiles profits. Make some money.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same principle could apply to non-revenue generating organizations or institutions by reducing federal funding where applicable.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m tired of sitting by and watching while our data is pilfered and not taken seriously by businesses we interact with. We as citizens have no recourse. This would provide serious consequences for lack of action and ultimately foster an information security mindset in the United States that has been lagging behind the past few years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：軟件中的區域限制是不必要的，不應該存在。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。我意識到這可能是一個陌生的話題，對大多數
但是，作爲一個東歐人，我總是遇到一些限制。
說實話，對我來說毫無意義。

例子一。我有一個裝有Alexa的藍牙音箱。我有一個Spotify
高級版。當我試着把它連接起來的時候，它的聲音就會消失。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pu4cl9/cmv_regional_restrictions_in_software_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pu4cl9/cmv_regional_restrictions_in_software_are/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 16:51:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone. I realise this will possibly be an unfamiliar topic to the majority of reddit, but, as a Eastern European, I keep bumping into restrictions that honestly make no sense to me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exhibit A: I&amp;#39;ve got a bluetooth speaker with Alexa on it. I&amp;#39;ve got a Spotify premium. When I try to connect the two, the Alexa app just doesn&amp;#39;t let me use the two services I already paid for because of the region lock. This benefits noone, except maybe Jeff Bezos, who wants to force me into subscribing to an inferior and more expensive service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exhibit B: I used to have an EA Origin account, and most of the games I bought were only available in Russian, which is not our official language, and most young people don&amp;#39;t speak it. Again, what is the point?
Even if the developers don&amp;#39;t want the developed countries&amp;#39; citizens to abuse our regional prices through VPN, punishing the local players by forcing them to play the game in a specific irrelevant language is just evil and not an adequate solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exhibit C: Spotify again. It doesn&amp;#39;t let people listen to podcasts here. And no, no local app is being protected by our government, as I&amp;#39;ve heard people say, because we don&amp;#39;t have those apps at all. There is no one whose interests would be infringed upon by allowing spotify to play podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, maybe there is an aspect I am not seeing here, in which case please CMV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 喫人在本質上沒有什麼錯誤。]]></title><description><![CDATA[(1) 食人是最近（相對較近）的禁忌，也是徹底的西方禁忌。
的禁忌。它曾經（或正在）在每個大陸上實行，最著名的是美洲和太平洋地區。
美洲和太平洋地區。它甚至在歷史上的不同時期在歐洲實行過
歷史上的不同時期。"喫人 "源於加勒比人。

(2) 該...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/puksvs/cmv_there_is_nothing_intrinsically_wrong_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/puksvs/cmv_there_is_nothing_intrinsically_wrong_with/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 16:51:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(1) Cannibalism is a recent (relatively recent) taboo, and a thoroughly western one. It has been (or is) practiced on every continent, most famously the Americas and the Pacific. It was even practiced in Europe at various points in history. &amp;quot;Cannibalism&amp;quot; is derived from the Carib people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(2) The most reflexive objections to cannibalism are actually objections to seperate practices -- murder, violation of bodily autonomy, etc. none of which are actually intrinsic to the practice of cannibalism (see endocannibalism.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(3) The objection that cannibalism poses a threat to health (kuru) is not a moral or ethical argument. Even then, it is only a problem (a) in communities where prion disease is already present and (b) where the brain and nerve tissue is eaten.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is exactly nothing wrong with cannibalism, especially how it is practiced in particular tribal communities in Papua New Guinea, i.e. endocannibalism (cannibalism as a means for mourning or funerary rituals.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV："混蛋聚合" Subreddits致力於展示 "來自另一方 "的宣傳品來取笑，這只是給了宣傳品更多的曝光機會，而不是忽略它。此外，它還創造了對更多宣傳的需求，並鼓勵人們以 "另一方 "的身份進行草根化，以獲得記憶點。]]></title><description><![CDATA[像/r/vaxxhappened和/r/therightcantmeme這樣的子網站以及其他數百個子網站
這些子網站的存在是爲了突出 "另一邊 "的混蛋，最終只是
最終只是在爲他們的宣傳提供平臺，並增加他們的主流曝光率。
信息傳遞策略。

就像騙子和右翼分子一樣，他們會發布任何...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pu4oun/cmv_asshole_aggregation_subreddits_dedicated_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pu4oun/cmv_asshole_aggregation_subreddits_dedicated_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 05:30:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subs like &lt;a href=&quot;/r/vaxxhappened&quot;&gt;/r/vaxxhappened&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/r/therightcantmeme&quot;&gt;/r/therightcantmeme&lt;/a&gt; and the hundreds of other subs that exist to highlight assholes on The Other Side, are ultimately just platforming their propaganda and increasing mainstream exposure to their messaging strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like shills and right wingers will just post whatever right wing meme to &lt;a href=&quot;/r/therightcantmeme&quot;&gt;/r/therightcantmeme&lt;/a&gt; and get their propaganda to the front page of &lt;a href=&quot;/r/all&quot;&gt;/r/all&lt;/a&gt;.  They don’t give a shit if everyone is ironically upvoting it, it’s still getting way more exposure than if they only posted it to right wing circlejerk subs.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this applies to all the right wing “asshole aggregation” platforms too, but they actually know what they’re doing.  Like &lt;a href=&quot;/r/kotakuinaction&quot;&gt;/r/kotakuinaction&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/r/tumblrinaction&quot;&gt;/r/tumblrinaction&lt;/a&gt; are seeking out the most insane 16 year olds saying stupid shit on Twitter for attention and they prop them up as strawwomyn meant to represent everyone on “the left.”  They’re very intentionally and effectively using these platforms to fabricate a boogieman concept that their followers internalize and radicalize against.  While most of the “left wing” asshole aggregation subs are just crossposting actual propaganda from right wing subs with stupid titles like “I can’t even…” or whatever and allowing that propaganda to get mainstream exposure.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And all of this shit didn’t exist 10 years ago.  Wasn’t until 2014, after Reddit became a major platform for the Russian Internet Research Agency, that suddenly half the content here just started shifting to “look at what this random asshole said on Twitter” as a way to feed culture wars tribalism and agitate people against each other.  All asshole aggregation subs are toxic and malignant and they exist in bad faith, while actively encouraging everyone to make more propaganda and seek out more random assholes to hate.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of the platforms dedicated to posting random assholes from The Other Side to radicalize against should just be entirely nuked from Reddit.  They’re all implicitly “promoting hate,” which is something Reddit likes to virtue signal about caring about.  It’s mindless reactionary content that’s designed to create more and more assholes and literally increase real world instances of political violence and terrorism.  It’s not doing anything good for anyone (other than people getting rewarded for posting agitprop), and it’s doing real psychological harm to millions of internet-addicts.   It’s cancer that needs to be cut out.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make Reddit Reddit Again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 你的宗教信仰不應影響我的法律。]]></title><description><![CDATA[你的宗教是你的宗教，它不應該影響到我的法律。你可以
你可以選擇你想對自己的身體做什麼，以及你想和誰睡覺。
與誰上牀。我可以選擇我想對自己的身體做什麼，以及我想和誰睡覺。
和誰上牀。

我真的不明白，兩千年前的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pu8jp9/cmv_your_religion_should_have_no_effects_on_my/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pu8jp9/cmv_your_religion_should_have_no_effects_on_my/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 02:08:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your religion is YOUR religion and it should have no affect on MY laws. You can choose what you would like to do with your own body and who you would like to sleep with. I can choose what I would like to do with my own body and who I will sleep with. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I genuinely don’t understand how 2,000 year old religious texts that often encourage slavery and genocide have the ability to affect MY laws. I don’t think Bronze Age “morals” should be relevant in the 21st century. Our laws shouldn’t be based around any religion in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：1/6，雖然是一個歷史上的可怕事件，但不是有計劃的 "叛亂 "的結果。]]></title><description><![CDATA[


特朗普、克魯茲或共和黨中的任何其他人都沒有計劃讓
他們的支持者衝進首都並傷害國會議員，以便
讓特朗普繼續執政。

首先，如果是有計劃的，那...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pu50qh/cmv_16_while_a_historically_awful_event_was_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pu50qh/cmv_16_while_a_historically_awful_event_was_not/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 01:14:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My main point that I’m curious if my mind will be changed on is that nobody - Not Trump, Cruz, or anyone else in the Republican Party - planned on having their supporters storm the capital and harm members of Congress in order to allow Trump to remain in power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For starters, if it was planned, what was the end goal? Does it seem reasonable that Trump actually wanted to just kill every member of Congress who opposed him, and expect to somehow retain power after that? Trump is stupid, but is he really that stupid?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the flip side, think about how many moving parts there would have to be to pull this off. How many people would need to be in on the secret? At the very least, some of the cops, some of the protestors, some people in Trumps inner circle who helped coordinate, and probably more. If there really was a plan to storm the capital and harm political figures, how did they manage to keep it secret so well?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re basically left with a plot that was both too stupid for anyone to attempt, and too hard for anyone other than an absolute genius to have pulled off. How is that a likely possibility of what happened?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s been countless talk about “investigating the events of 1/6”. In my opinion, the only realistic possibility  that will be uncovered is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Trump constantly claimed fraud. Unclear if he actually believed in fraud or was using it as an excuse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Trump tried to convince as many people as possible that fraud was real. This was either because he really thought he could overturn the election, to provide an excuse for his loss, or both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-A fairly large number of people actually believed this fantasy that the election was fraudulent. As a result, some of them got rowdy at a protest and actually managed to breach the capital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Trump was very possibly not upset about this event. However, I can’t imagine a scenario where this event was part of an orchestrated plot to overturn the election, or remain in power by force.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在美國沒有充分的理由反對爲兒童（<18歲）提供全民醫保]]></title><description><![CDATA[CMV：在美國，沒有充分的理由反對爲兒童（<18歲）提供全民醫療保健。
美國

 1. 兒童無法獲得自己的健康保險，因爲健康保險是與就業掛鉤的。
    與就業掛鉤，而他們的全職工作應該是學校。
 2. 兒童是弱勢人羣的一部分，作爲一個社會，我們...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pu21g3/cmv_there_is_no_good_reason_against_universal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pu21g3/cmv_there_is_no_good_reason_against_universal/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 20:37:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CMV: There is no good reason against universal health care for children (&amp;lt;18) in the US&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Children can&amp;#39;t get their own health insurance because health insurance is tied to employment and their full time job should be school &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Children are part of a vulnerable population who as a society we deem deserving of extra protections and support regardless &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Children shouldn&amp;#39;t be punished if their parents can&amp;#39;t afford to give them health care or if their parents made or didn&amp;#39;t make smart financial decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intervening early with solid routine health care means less medical issues when they are adults &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;It&amp;#39;s too expensive&amp;quot; - sure but it is certainly more cost efficient to have a single payer who can negotiate more strongly. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Something like this already exists for low income&amp;quot; - I&amp;#39;m talking about automatically registering every children upon birth for universal health care. You go into any clinic or hospital in the country and can receive healthcare upon showing your state health card. For healthcare for low income families, they have to apply for it, or if the child is housing insecure or living in shelters, that serves as even more hurdles to receive health care. In a system where only low-income children can qualify for state funded health care, the child has to prove they are low income usually involving an application. I want to move to a system where every child upon birth will automatically receive their health care, and free at the point of care, unlimited health care until they are 18. Minimize these hurdles &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One could make the argument that universal health care for everyone is better. This argument won&amp;#39;t change my view because it is out of the scope of this CMV. This CMV is basically saying &amp;quot;at the very least, universal health care should be provided to children&amp;quot;. Other vulnerable groups or universal health care for everyone is out of scope.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：保險是一個騙局]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽車保險和房主保險是一個騙局。它的運作往往像一個
金字塔計劃。你提出索賠，你的費率就會上升。爲什麼我們要支付
如果我們必須向他們償還，隨着時間的推移，我們從他們那裏得到的任何錢。
通過增加費率...

我知道有的時候，你有一個...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ptxdb1/cmv_insurance_is_a_scam/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ptxdb1/cmv_insurance_is_a_scam/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 19:30:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Car insurance and homeowners insurance is a scam. It often operates like a pyramid scheme. You file a claim and your rate goes up. Why do we pay for insurance if we have to pay them back, over time, any money we get from them, through an increased rate...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know there are times that you have an accident and they cover it and maybe it doesn&amp;#39;t affect your rate. In my experience and from taking to others most the time your rate goes up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What has your experience been?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do we pay them more and more just to end up getting a claim denied or a raised rate regardless of fault and circumstance&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美國共和黨不是法西斯，美國民主黨也不是共產黨]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你相信其中一個說法，那麼你就應該相信另一個。

這就是原因。

我們還有8個月就將權力從共和黨領導的分裂政府轉移到民主黨領導的政府了。
政府轉移到一個民主黨領導的政府。我們離共和黨領導的政府還有3年時間。
共和黨領導的政府。如果我們正在經歷權力的轉移，那麼，我們就會發現，在我們的國家裏，權力的轉移是非常重要的。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ptztth/cmv_the_us_republican_party_is_not_fascist_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ptztth/cmv_the_us_republican_party_is_not_fascist_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 19:30:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you believe one of these statements, then you ought to believe the other.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s why:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are 8 months away from a transfer of power from a Republican-led divided government to a Democrat-led government.  We are 3 years away from a Republican-led government.  If we were experiencing transfers of power from a Fascist party, or to a Communist party, the amount of things that would be radically different than the way they were before the transfer of power would be causing society-wide whiplash; there would be chaos.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People are who they say they are.  People don&amp;#39;t go into politics with a &amp;quot;pretend&amp;quot; ideology and a &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; ideology that they secretly believe.  Even if they did, it doesn&amp;#39;t matter; they don&amp;#39;t govern the way that their supposed &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; ideology would dictate.  We still have capitalism, we still have democracy, and we&amp;#39;ve had it through both Democrat and Republican administrations.  Both Republicans and Democrats are more or less liberals: Republicans leaning towards so-called Classical Liberalism and Democrats towards so-called Social Liberalism; a right leaning liberalism or a left leaning one.  There are wings of both parties that are more extreme, sure.  Doesn&amp;#39;t change the broad outlook of the majority of members of both parties, and those &amp;quot;extreme&amp;quot; wings are still far off from being openly fascist or communist.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If somehow you can prove that either party has at least some fascist or communist elements, then you&amp;#39;d change my mind.  I&amp;#39;m expecting both sides to be trying to litigate what exactly communism and fascism mean, so maybe if you can give me a better definition than the ones that I think are warranted, you could change my mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>