<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 04:31:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：作为一个接种过疫苗的美国人，在这个时候叫我戴口罩，是希望我保护那些拒绝保护自己的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[接种疫苗并不能保证不感染COVID，但数据确实表明
接种疫苗的人与未接种疫苗的人相比，住院和死亡的几率可以忽略不计。
与未接种疫苗的人相比，住院和死亡的机会微乎其微。这说明了很多问题，因为许多人认为COVID的健康风险很大。
认为即使在接种疫苗之前，COVID的健康风险也是可以忽略不计的。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ovepiv/cmv_as_a_vaccinated_american_telling_me_to_wear_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ovepiv/cmv_as_a_vaccinated_american_telling_me_to_wear_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 23:37:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccination is not a guarantee of not catching COVID, but the data does show that the chances of hospitalization and death is negligible for vaccinated people in comparison to the unvaccinated. And that’s saying a lot since many consider COVID’s health risks to be negligible even before a vaccine existed. Since May, 99% of COVID deaths were unvaccinated people. Most of the unvaccinated are that way by choice, not medical necessity. We are at the point where anyone who wants the vaccine can get it.&lt;br/&gt;
I did my part. I wore my mask, practiced social distancing, and got my vaccine as soon as I could. I don’t have a problem with the unvaccinated choosing to have a 100x higher risk of dying to COVID but I should not bear any burden of mitigating that risk for them.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[edit] since so many are bringing up immunocompromised people: We were never expected to mask up to protect them from any viruses prior to COVID. Since COVID may not be eradicated with a vaccine, this is essentially an argument for wearing masks forever, since there will always be immunocompromised people. No.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 与私有化医疗的混乱局面相比，为全民医疗提供的非必要医疗而被要求向政府缴税以及更长的等待时间是值得的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[普及/社会化医疗利大于弊，特别是当
与完全私有化的医疗系统相比，我真的不明白
为什么不首先提供全民医疗，然后再选择以价格补贴的方式提供医疗服务？
我真的不明白为什么不首先提供全民医疗，然后再选择用私人医疗进行补贴？]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ovb9rp/cmv_being_made_to_pay_taxes_to_the_government_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ovb9rp/cmv_being_made_to_pay_taxes_to_the_government_for/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 19:33:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Universal/Socialised healthcare has greater pros than the cons, especially when compared to solely privatised healthcare systems, and I really don&amp;#39;t understand why it is not commonplace to offer universal healthcare first and foremost and then have the option be able subsidise it with private healthcare in all the developed countries that can afford it. I myself would find not being able to choose who I see, having to pay for everyone to have access to healthcare and slightly longer waiting times a small sacrifice, when faced with an alternative that would mean I risk being bankrupted for just wanting to be healthy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：社交媒体和 "新浪潮 "育儿法造就了以自我为中心的人，无法倾听或辩论。]]></title><description><![CDATA[虽然我很欣赏年轻一代更加开放和接受
人的多种生活方式，但我确实认为我们这一代已经变得
对任何持不同观点的人都无法容忍。

我（20岁）是在互联网边上长大的，并参与了社会活动。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ov92pw/cmv_social_media_and_new_wave_parenting_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ov92pw/cmv_social_media_and_new_wave_parenting_has/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 17:44:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;While I do appreciate that the younger generations are more open and accepting of the many ways people live life, I do think our generation has become insufferably intolerant towards anyone with slightly different views. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I (20M) have been raised alongside the internet and got involved in social media pretty early on 12/13 - this is the case for many younger people - and I can&amp;#39;t help noticing how we&amp;#39;re creating more and more labels to put people in boxes as racist, homophobic, 
... e.g. the term &amp;quot;microaggression&amp;quot; that is meant to represent a covert manner of attacking/ostracizing certain groups. As a black man, I&amp;#39;ve had people trying to touch my hair my entire life - I don&amp;#39;t like it, in fact I hate it but is it racist in any way shape or form? No. Is it a microaggression? F*ck no. It&amp;#39;s a person who&amp;#39;s seen something different to what they&amp;#39;re used to (my hair) and was thus curious about how it felt (differently from theirs, surely). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we keep trying to shun people by labeling them with this or that term as soon as they act in a way we perceive as wrong without even giving them the time of day to understand where they&amp;#39;re coming from, we&amp;#39;re going nowhere. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ve become so heavily politicized that instead of gaining an understanding through experience, we obtain an illusion of that through the skewed views of the people we follow on social media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(I&amp;#39;ll just say now that I know I am generalizing when I say &amp;quot;we&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;younger generations&amp;quot;, ... I do understand that not everyone is like this. My point is that social media has seeped through enough of us for this lack of communication to become obvious.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：政府只是在更大范围内的有组织犯罪，我们被洗脑后接受了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[CMV: 我几乎每天都在新闻中看到关于政府打击有组织犯罪的文章。
打击有组织犯罪，不管是贩毒集团还是网络犯罪，或者真的是
任何不属于政府的东西。他们没有告诉你的是，你的政府可能也在做这些事情。
政府可能也在做这些事情，就在你身后。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ov8smv/cmv_governments_are_just_organized_crime_on_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ov8smv/cmv_governments_are_just_organized_crime_on_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 16:57:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CMV: Almost everyday on the news I see articles about the government cracking down on organized crime, wether it be drug cartels or cybercrime or really anything that isn&amp;#39;t government owned. What they don&amp;#39;t show you, is that your government was probably doing these same things right behind your back. I&amp;#39;m not calling out any specific country, but there are governments that have done mass genocide, invasions, destruction of already functioning democratic governments, killing innocent civilians, deforestation, terrible over pollution, drug smuggling/dealing and much much more all just to turn a profit for themselves. Is that not organized crime that has gotten so big that we just have to accept it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Quick reminder that this is just a friendly CMV discussion, no need to get angry. I&amp;#39;d like to come out of this more appreciative of the people in charge, rather than just always thinking negatively of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 2: Thanks for all the insight! I&amp;#39;m out of time, but I&amp;#39;ve awarded the delta.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我认为大多数其他的性别认同都是在抢夺注意力。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我对变性人没有意见，我不认为他们这样做是为了引起别人的注意。
除了一些十几岁的 "变性人 "正在经历一个阶段之外

但我认为很多非二元人只是想成为特别的人
因为他们决定不想适应 "传统的性别角色"
这就是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ov5vt6/cmv_i_think_most_other_gender_identities_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ov5vt6/cmv_i_think_most_other_gender_identities_are/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 14:32:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transgenders I’m fine with, I don’t think they’re doing it for attention other than some teenage “transgenders” going through a phase&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I think a lot of non-binary people are just people who want to be special because they decided they don’t want to fit into “traditional gender roles” which is pretty stupid imo &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Genderfluidity is dumber. I think this is purely a symptom of the internet. I’m sorry, but there’s no such thing as genderfluidity, it’s called being a human that feels different at different times, and then assigning a term to yourself so that you can be different and special from all the “normies”. If femininity and masculinity defined your gender than we wouldn’t call butch lesbians women, we wouldn’t call twinks men, but we do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day it’s not really my business, but then again if you told me any other ridiculous BS I wouldn’t entertain you so 🤷‍♂️&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：白人可以和其他所有种族一起经历种族主义]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先我想说，我并不是想淡化许多黑人每天都会遇到的种族主义。
我相信这是一个巨大的问题，需要关注，以帮助找到解决方案。
我认为这是一个巨大的问题，需要关注，以帮助找到一个解决方案。

我经常在社交媒体上看到一些人的帖子，他们声称白人不可能经历种族主义。
遭遇种族主义。这是我的观点。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ov1clv/cmv_white_people_can_experience_racism_alongside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ov1clv/cmv_white_people_can_experience_racism_alongside/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 09:40:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to start off by saying that I am not trying to downplay the racism that many POC experience on a daily basis, I believe it is a huge problem and requires attention to help find a solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I often come across posts on social media of people claiming white people can&amp;#39;t experience racism. The argument I come across the most usually goes as follows:  &amp;quot;White people can&amp;#39;t experience racism as they are the oppressor&amp;#39;s, you cant oppress the oppressor&amp;quot;. This is a crappy argument as racism is clearly defended as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against a person or people on the basis of their membership in a particular racial or ethnic group, typically one that is a minority or marginalized. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just because the majority of racism is experienced by POC doesn&amp;#39;t mean you can&amp;#39;t experience it as someone who is white, this goes for other races as well. Especially on tiktok and twitter I will see people referring to white people as &amp;quot;ranch rodent, mayo monkey, etc..&amp;quot;. This is clearly racism as if I where to refer to someone who is a POC as anything similar to that I would be labeled as a racist. It is also evident when white people are made fun of when expressing that they have been the victim of a race related crime/ incident. I find people will often make fun of them and not take them seriously. Just because it doesn&amp;#39;t happen as often doesn&amp;#39;t take away from the fact that you are being racist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Claiming white people can&amp;#39;t experience racism is an incredibly flawed argument. Again I&amp;#39;m not trying to invalidate anyone, but it sets an unhealthy double standard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 我们对待诽谤的方式是奇怪的去道德化的，已经脱离了伤害原则。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在一个类似的主题上发过帖子
[https://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/comments/mkv0w5/cmv_normalising_the_use_of_slurs_is_bad_but_the/]
不久前，我也曾就类似的问题发过帖子，但在这一点上并没有收到多少挑战
所以我想我应该给它自己的CMV。说白了，这不是一个
支持诽谤...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ouuy0m/cmv_the_way_we_treat_slurs_is_weirdly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ouuy0m/cmv_the_way_we_treat_slurs_is_weirdly/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 04:33:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I posted on a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/comments/mkv0w5/cmv_normalising_the_use_of_slurs_is_bad_but_the/&quot;&gt;similar subject&lt;/a&gt; a little while ago, but didn&amp;#39;t receive much challenge on this point in particular, so I thought I should give it its own CMV. To be clear, this isn&amp;#39;t a pro-slurs freeze peach CMV, I&amp;#39;m more just a little puzzled by what is easily the most common reaction to a slur being referenced.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a massive degree of reverence that is given to slurs. A recent situation occurred in my (very politically inclined, and part of an extended discussion on the subject) friend group. I was talking about the racist origins of the southern strategy and while quoting Lee Atwood, the inventor of the racist southern strategy, quoted the n word.
  &amp;quot;By 1968 you can’t say “nigger”—that hurts you, backfires. So you say stuff like, uh, forced busing, states’ rights, and all that stuff, and you’re getting so abstract.&amp;quot;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This caused a brouhaha which I apologised for, despite being a bit puzzled. Everybody present was white. The context was in an explicit condemnation of racism, and was a quote of an individual who I was rather heatedly criticising at the time. It&amp;#39;s such an abstract rule to enforce in this context. Nobody can actually explain why they&amp;#39;re offended by it, but we&amp;#39;ve become so socially conditioned against the word, just a mere academic reference to it is enough to make us flinch. This is insane.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look, I understand that flippant use of slurs is bad. It&amp;#39;s bad because it harms people through the normalisation of racism. But somewhere along the way refusal to refer to slurs has become a weird irreducible deontological principle that nobody seems to be able to explain. I&amp;#39;m not suggesting we bring back the n word into common conversation, but surely just &lt;em&gt;referring&lt;/em&gt; to the word shouldn&amp;#39;t be offensive if there&amp;#39;s no racism or risk of normalisation being carried along with it implicitly. Racism is disgusting and isn&amp;#39;t just hurt feelings. It&amp;#39;s extremely damaging and its influences are incredibly deeply seated in people&amp;#39;s minds that an attack on racism is seen as an attack on a country itself.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we ban certain speech, usually I understand it as a method of mitigating some kind of harm. Shouting fire in a crowded theatre. Inciting violence. Needless verbal abuse. Abuse on the basis of a protected class. I get it.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But not tolerating the &lt;em&gt;word itself&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not upset, I&amp;#39;m just... confused. I just do not understand it. Not even a rhetorical lack of understanding, I&amp;#39;m genuinely puzzled why people think this way. Maybe there&amp;#39;s a good reason that&amp;#39;s blindingly obvious that I am missing. Please, change my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在帖子中以 "匿名的废弃账户 "作为开头，再加上一个令人难以置信的独特故事，是很愚蠢的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我经常看到这种情况。有人发布了一个故事，并在开头写道："抛弃的账户，因为我不想让别人知道这是我"，然后他们发布了一个 "我 "字。
账户，因为我不想让别人知道这是我"，然后他们发布了一个极其独特或具体的故事。
然后他们发布了一个非常独特或具体的故事，显然会被他们所指的人认出。
他们所提到的人。就像你们真的认为...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ouwcvg/cmv_starting_a_post_with_throwaway_account_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ouwcvg/cmv_starting_a_post_with_throwaway_account_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 02:32:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see this all the time. Someone posts a story and starts it off with &amp;quot;Throwaway account because I dont want anyone knowing this is me&amp;quot; and then they post an extremely unique or specific story that will obviously be recognized by the person/people they&amp;#39;re referencing. Like do y&amp;#39;all really think having a burner account keeps you anonymous when your story is something like &amp;quot;My husband threw my child in an octopus tank and then ran naked through the aquarium, should I divorce him?&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This actually just makes me chuckle more than anything but am I missing something here? Has anyone who&amp;#39;s done this and ended up on the front page ever actually remained anonymous from those they&amp;#39;re trying to hide from? And I&amp;#39;m referencing those  AITA posts or AskReddit that blow up. Not saying throwaways don&amp;#39;t work ever. But I have a hard time believing you stayed anonymous when the story you provided could have been an oscar winning screenplay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：每个人都应该从小学开始学习两门外语]]></title><description><![CDATA[有强有力的科学证据表明，一定年龄以下的儿童更容易学习语言。
掌握语言更容易，而且能够说一种语言是一个非常有用的工具。
能说一种语言是非常有用的工具。所以在我看来，让孩子们等到初中或高中才开始学习外语
开始学习外语是让他们错过了......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ourfq9/cmv_everyone_should_learn_two_foreign_languages/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ourfq9/cmv_everyone_should_learn_two_foreign_languages/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 01:56:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is strong scientific evidence that children under a certain age have a much easier time learning languages and being able to speak one is an increadibly usefull tool. So in my mind, having children wait until middle or high school to start learning foreign languages is having them miss an incredibile and never quite returning opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can of course never know if the specific individual is in fact going to need the languages in their life, but the majority of the world population does in fact use foreign languages fairly often. I&amp;#39;d argue far more people use foreign languages regularly than say advanced chemistry, chemistry being a mandatory class in most countries. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;d suggest that everyone should learn english or spanish and the language of a country neighbouring the one they live in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 如果你在正常工作期间在你的办公楼里拍摄OnlyFan照片，而你的同事发现了，他们有权对你进行指责。]]></title><description><![CDATA[请注意，在任何事情之前，有一条线，我不是说他们应该猫
打电话，或对你进行性骚扰。但是，如果你要去洗手间，你可以说："哦，你要去打拳吗？
的评论，如 "哦，你要去你的另一份工作打卡！"或 "不要忘了这是厕所，不是风扇服务室。
或 "别忘了这是个洗手间，不是风扇服务室 "等等。IS好了...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ounnoo/cmv_if_youre_taking_onlyfan_pictures_in_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ounnoo/cmv_if_youre_taking_onlyfan_pictures_in_your/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 18:30:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please note before anything, there is a line i&amp;#39;m not saying they should cat call, or sexually harass you. However, if you&amp;#39;re going to the bathroom simple comments like, &amp;quot;Oh you going to go punch the clock at your other job!&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t forget it&amp;#39;s a restroom, not a fan service room&amp;quot; etc etc. IS well within the realm of being ok. My argument is you opened that door the moment you let those 2 worlds cross over and you should be able to take it on the chin.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This only counts if you do things in your office building, if you&amp;#39;re running an OnlyFans strictly as a side hustle on your OWN none company time, then you&amp;#39;re still off limits in the office your private time is yours.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMV You do it in the office, you&amp;#39;re opening yourself up to the jokes and ribs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：产品植入广告和其他类型的节目中的广告，比起广告时间，给观众带来更好的体验。]]></title><description><![CDATA[流媒体电视已经让我习惯于按照编剧和导演的意图，不断地观看节目。
编剧和导演的意图。当我因为某种原因不得不回到电视直播的时候
不管是什么原因，广告时间是如此具有破坏性。不仅仅是占用了时间
不仅仅是占用了节目的时间，而且广告有不同的音量，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oubgfc/cmv_product_placement_advertisements_and_other/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oubgfc/cmv_product_placement_advertisements_and_other/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 15:47:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Streaming TV has gotten me so spoiled on watching a constant flow of a show, as the writer and director intended. When I do have to go back to live TV for whatever reason, the ad breaks are so disruptive.  Not just taking the time away from the show, but commercials have different volume levels, different art styles, different everything! From the other commercials as well as the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example: I’d way rather have a moment in a show where the main character has a 30 second car ride up a long driveway to walk up to the front door of a secondary character. Basically a car commercial with a bunch of glamour shots of a shiny car with a handsome driver. At least the sound design, and the direction, would fit with the rest of the show. Main character knocks on the door and we hit the ground running with the episode. Maybe they go inside and there are Heinekens on the table. Who cares? We’re in the universe of the show!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things that would change my mind:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;a strong financial argument that product placement things simply aren’t lucrative enough&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;a slippery slope type argument that the line between art and commercialism would be blurred even further to the point of being indistinguishable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;a full throated defense of commercials I guess? I’m not taking this so seriously, whatever ya got!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：24小时的新闻周期正在毁掉奥运会]]></title><description><![CDATA[全国广播公司、其附属电视台和其他所有人都急于在第一时间发布
突发新闻"，以至于几乎不可能避免剧透。女子体操全能冠军
女子体操全能比赛的冠军在NBC下午的节目开始时就被令人窒息地宣布了。
NBC的下午节目一开始就令人窒息地宣布，尽管该赛事本身...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ou3ryd/cmv_the_24hour_news_cycle_is_ruining_the_olympics/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ou3ryd/cmv_the_24hour_news_cycle_is_ruining_the_olympics/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 11:30:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NBC, its affiliate stations, and everybody else are so eager to be first with the &amp;quot;breaking news&amp;quot; that it&amp;#39;s nearly impossible to avoid spoilers. The winner of the women&amp;#39;s gymnastics all-around was breathlessly announced right at the start of NBC&amp;#39;s afternoon programming, even though the event itself wasn&amp;#39;t going to air until the main evening broadcast. If I&amp;#39;ve spent the day avoiding sports talk and social media so I could actually be surprised, why would NBC themselves spoil it in a quick blurb hours before I could see the event? What&amp;#39;s the advantage of this / how is it good for their ratings?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 没有人应该为工作申请 "量身定做 "简历或求职信。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这也适用于强迫候选人在ATS中重写他们的整个简历。
山寨行业的荒谬之处在于，教你重复使用工作描述中的词汇，以便通过一些懒惰的过滤器。
荒唐的是，一些山寨企业教你重复使用工作描述中的词汇，以便通过一些懒惰设计的过滤器，还有一种想法是，要想引起谁的注意，就必须
还有一种想法是，要想引起审查者的注意，就得靠你自己......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oudr3x/cmv_nobody_should_have_to_tailor_resumes_or_cover/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oudr3x/cmv_nobody_should_have_to_tailor_resumes_or_cover/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 08:40:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This also goes for forcing candidates to rewrite their entire resume in an ATS, the absurdity of cottage industries that teach you to reuse words in the job description so you pass some lazily designed filter, and the idea that it&amp;#39;s somehow on you to get the attention of whoever is reviewing applications within some incredibly short period of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HR is getting paid to go through this slog. Job applicants are not. It takes a long time to tailor resumes and cover letters to however many dozens of listings for however many companies to which you apply, whereas it&amp;#39;s literally the job of somebody in a position to hire to know what a given opening requires and who will be a good fit for their organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the case of Japan, there&amp;#39;s a standard resume format that everyone uses in which you list all of your academic and professional experience - and there is far less emphasis on the cover letter. It seems to work fine,  so how can it be the case that the &amp;quot;tailoring&amp;quot; expectation is anything other than an attempt to shift paid workload onto people who probably won&amp;#39;t even get a response about the job?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美国膨胀的军事预算要归功于承包商]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的观点是，军队已经被国防承包商腐蚀了。

这些公司从战争中赚钱，前五角大楼的官员是这些公司的工作人员。
凭借他们的关系，他们能够歪曲美国的外交政策。
外交政策包括干预，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ou9sl8/cmv_the_us_bloated_military_budget_is_thanks_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ou9sl8/cmv_the_us_bloated_military_budget_is_thanks_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 05:33:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;my view is that the military has been corrupted by defense contractors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;these corporations make money off of war. former pentagon officials make up the staffs of these corporations. with their connections, they’re able to skew US foreign policy. that foreign policy includes interventions that require weapons. that lines the pockets of defense contractors. perhaps they’re increasing their profits even more by charging the country too much for what they’re offering. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’m not an expert in military budgeting, so maybe it’s not as wasteful as i’ve laid out and maybe they’re more independent from the defense contractors then i’ve portrayed them. i look forward to some good responses!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：戴口罩和强制接种疫苗不是为了政府控制]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，我经常听到共和党人说，疫苗和口罩的授权是关于美国
政府的控制。

但这种说法似乎是无稽之谈。要求戴口罩和
接种疫苗是一种政府控制的形式？美国政府
通过免费赠送疫苗和...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ou9qt9/cmv_wearing_a_mask_and_vaccine_mandates_are_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ou9qt9/cmv_wearing_a_mask_and_vaccine_mandates_are_not/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 04:45:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, often I hear from Republicans that vaccine and mask mandates are about US government control. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this argument seems nonsensical. How can requiring wearing a mask and getting a vaccine a form of government control? What does the US government possibly gain by giving away free vaccines and requiring people to wear masks to stop the spread of the virus?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If anything, the government should be worried about masks, as it interferes with face recognition technology and makes catching criminals harder. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why would mask mandates be all about controlling the American public when it’s actually counter protective to catching criminals?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for vaccines, why would giving away vaccines be a form of government control? The government gains nothing and instead giving something away for free is actually a financial loss on those distributing the vaccines. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does free mRNA technology in your body possibly do to you that you’re now suddenly susceptible to government control?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find it weird that people who are anti mask and anti vaxx say this is government control and yet, they are still allowed to criticize vaccine and mask mandates and half the country’s politicians and citizens agree. That doesn’t sound like government control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：心理健康教育一直被故意忽视，让人们无法实现自己的真正潜力，无法突破大多数社会教条和污名，使他们处于自己的位置。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我相信，心理健康教育在我们的社会中一直被忽视，这是故意的。
故意忽略了...

当一个人处于消极的心理健康状态时，他们往往看不到自己的
自己的自我价值，并由于自己的不安全感而对他人进行评判。他们不太可能
他们不太可能接受新的想法。

我们的政府需要这样的人...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ou2pah/cmv_mental_health_education_has_been_neglected_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ou2pah/cmv_mental_health_education_has_been_neglected_on/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 01:05:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I believe, mental health education has been neglected in our society on purpose...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When someone is in a negative mental health state, they tend to not see their own self worth and judge others due to their own insecurities. They are less likely to accept new ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our government needs people who do not believe in themselves so they can do these menial jobs and not find out they are being exploited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe a solution to a lot of our current societal problems can be achieve with a major focus on mental health education and financial literacy for future generations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We rely on each individual on this planet to work on themselves and make it a better place and be more understanding of others differences and faults.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s either because the internet has existed for the past 30 years and information is allowed to flow freely and word about mental health can get out, or we are actually JUST now making these discoveries in mental health and finding out just how crucial it is. Either way, I feel mental health and financial literacy needs to be educated more to the masses as our next major step towards improving our society as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until we are able to work past our own traumas and problems causing us to think the negative ways we do, we will always have these same cycles of problems and will run around in circles for eternity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I have changed my view that they did not know what mental health was but I still think we are being hurt by ways that convenience&amp;#39;s Capitalism&amp;#39;s agenda (which leads to a lot of the unknowing mental health issues) and mental health education and financial literacy are what&amp;#39;s needed to combat this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Loli是恋童癖。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我看来，lolicon就是恋童癖。现在，在你说 "哦，它不是真的 "或
"哦，它不可能在动画片中出现"，让我解释一下

Lolicon是恋童癖，因为它是专门为儿童设计的，所以通过专门寻找它，你是在试图找到HITAI。
专门寻找它，你试图找到儿童的hentai。如果你
偶然发现...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ou3oxs/cmv_loli_is_pedophilia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ou3oxs/cmv_loli_is_pedophilia/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 20:39:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, lolicon is pedophilia.
Now, before you say &amp;quot;oh its not real&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;oh its impossible to tell in anime&amp;quot; let me explain&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lolicon is pedophilic because its specifically designed after a child, so by specifically looking for it, youre trying to find hentai of children. If you stumble across loli and cant tell its a child from looks and dont know the age, then its fine unless you learn the age because you dont know its a child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, yes, it usually is VERY hard to tell in anime, except when its meant to be loli hentai. The problem is being attracted to a minors body or the fact that they are underaged, that is what makes it pedophilia, so if theres a character that looks above 18 but is a minor and you dont know, its fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comss to adults with a petite figure, petite is different in many ways from a childs body, mostly the definition of the torso, arms, legs etc, so it shouldnt be hard to tell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：今天的清醒文化使许多人感到痛苦，因为他们只认为自己是社会的受害者，而放弃了自己对命运的责任。]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管我很高兴生活在一个我们越来越多地与少数民族斗争的时代，并停止对受害者的羞辱。
少数群体，并停止对受害者的羞辱。至少我们在努力。但是，尽管我认为它
我们变得更加理解人们，他们的背景和他们的
个人的斗争，但我讨厌看到我们如何创造一个社会...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otyhs5/cmv_todays_woke_culture_is_making_many_people/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otyhs5/cmv_todays_woke_culture_is_making_many_people/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 16:55:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though I am glad to live in a time where we more and more struggles of minorities and stop victim shaming. At least we try. But even though I think its good that we become more understanding for people, their backgrounds and their individual struggles, I hate to see how we create a society where no one is anyones fault ever. I have a lot of friends and acquaintances who blame every struggle they have on society, the patriarchy, capitalism or racissm. And sometimes thats definitely true! But other times it is not. Especially people living in developed countries (excluding the US) have many opportunities if they are willing to work for it. And yes - there are definitely societal issues that hold certain people back. But I often witness people who are actually quit privileged scapegoating society for the fact that they don&amp;#39;t get there shit together. And that bothers me af.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我们只能通过冷漠来实现平等。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这一代人一直在宣传某些群体的优点，并试图赋予他们权力。
但我认为这一切只是将钟摆摆回另一边。
我认为，我们要想获得真正的平等，唯一的办法就是不关心。

我认为说人们的优点同样具有破坏性......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otwng0/cmv_we_can_only_achieve_equality_through/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otwng0/cmv_we_can_only_achieve_equality_through/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 14:34:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This generation keeps promoting what&amp;#39;s good about certain groups and trying to empower them but I think all this does is swing the pendulum back the other way. I think the only way we will ever have true equality is by simply not caring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think saying what&amp;#39;s good about people is just as damaging as saying what&amp;#39;s bad about them. I get upset when I hear someone constantly brag about what&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;unique&amp;quot; about them just as I do when they&amp;#39;re attacked for being different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand that it&amp;#39;s important to promote awareness to fight ignorance but that&amp;#39;s not what I see today - people fighting fire with fire, people using it as a badge to feel important, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this a wrong way to think?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：允许俄罗斯以中华民国的名义参加奥运会并不是一个公平的惩罚。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，首先，我不认为允许俄罗斯队以ROC（俄罗斯奥林匹克委员会）的名义参加比赛是一个公平的惩罚。
我不认为允许俄罗斯队以ROC（俄罗斯奥林匹克委员会）的名义参赛是一个公平的惩罚。我认为
我认为，由于俄罗斯仍然以他们的名义参加比赛，因此没有达到预期的惩罚效果。
惩罚。

与其在这个名称下竞争，我相信...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otsj77/cmv_allowing_russia_to_compete_as_roc_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otsj77/cmv_allowing_russia_to_compete_as_roc_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:50:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So to start, I do not believe allowing the Russian team to compete under the name ROC, or Russian Olympic Committee, is a fair punishment. I believe that because Russia is still in the name they&amp;#39;re competing under, the intended punishment is missed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of competing under that title, I believe it would have been much more reasonable to allow their athletes to compete under an unaffiliated title. I don&amp;#39;t think this should be strictly a Russian grouping either. Instead, this would both allow athletes to choose to compete unaffiliated with a country, in addition to allowing athletes from countries stripped of their emblems to still compete in the games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change my view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[EDIT: grammar, and verb use for clarity]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：辩论宗教是不可能的，因为 "支持上帝 "的一方从来不会遵守辩论规则。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我曾多次尝试与救济金辩论，一个基本的缺陷是
宗教人士总是从 "上帝是真实的 "这一立场出发。这打破了
破坏了辩论的基本规则。神的存在是一个积极的主张，而你
你必须拿出证据来支持这一主张，否则它就会在本质上...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otsvkj/cmv_debating_religion_is_impossible_because_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otsvkj/cmv_debating_religion_is_impossible_because_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:50:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve tried debating reliigon many times, and one fundamental flaw is that religious people always start from the the stance that gos IS real. This breaks the basic rules of debate. The existance of god is a positive claim, and you have to bring evidence to support the claim, else it is inherently flase. Its like me saying &amp;quot;invisible passthrough elephants exist, prove me wrong&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cannot prove such a negative in this case, and therefore, you cannot protect your stance. To debate religion, we need the positive side to follow the basic rules of debate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：阴谋论并不因为是阴谋论就本质上是无效的]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想首先声明，我在这篇文章中使用的例子是
只是例子，可能反映也可能不反映我的个人观点。我将尽量不
对任何特定的理论采取立场，而只是陈述该理论。

阴谋论是一种解释某一事件或一组事件的理论。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otgata/cmv_conspiracy_theories_arent_inherently_invalid/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otgata/cmv_conspiracy_theories_arent_inherently_invalid/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:43:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’d like to begin with a disclaimer that the examples I use in this post are just examples, and may or may not reflect my personal views. I will try not to take a side on any particular theory, and instead just state the theory. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A conspiracy theory is a theory that explains an event or set of circumstances as the result of a secret plot by usually powerful conspirators. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This does not automatically invalidate the theory. They are simply alternative explanations of events and their causes. One can not invalidate a conspiracy theory without looking at the evidence claimed by the theorists. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, the moon landing conspiracy. There is a group that believes that humans have never landed on the moon, and that the Apollo 11 landing was filmed on a movie set. Their evidence includes shadow lines in different directions, which are typical of a secondary light source. They also use the video of the flag flapping after being twisted to claim that a flag can’t flap without an atmosphere. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, after examining their evidence, the second shadow can be created by the reflection off of the moon’s surface, and the flapping was from the inertia of the twisting and could be replicated in a vacuum chamber. There is also counter evidence, where Apollo 15 astronauts placed a mirrored reflector in a precise location on the moon, and we can shoot a laser at it from earth and get the laser bounced back. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That theory is not inherently invalid because it’s a conspiracy theory, it was proven invalid with evidence. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR you need evidence to disprove a conspiracy theory that also has evidence, change my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在这个时代，宗教还在挑战科学，这绝对是荒谬的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[现在不要误会我的意思，我仍然认为科学应该受到挑战；这就是科学的意义所在。
这就是科学的全部内容，用其他具体的想法来挑战假设，以形成一个理论或可能的事实。
形成一个理论或可能是一个事实。但宗教没有任何地位
挑战科学理论和思想。

宗教是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otjjxp/cmv_its_absolutely_ridiculous_that_religion_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otjjxp/cmv_its_absolutely_ridiculous_that_religion_is/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 06:47:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now don’t get me wrong, I still think that science should be challenged; that’s what science is all about, challenging hypothesis’s with other concrete ideas to form a theory or possibly a fact. But religion has no place what so ever in challenging scientific theories and ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Religion was created because humans are inherently afraid of the unknown. We didn’t know where the sun came from and what the stars were so we came up with the most convenient answer: God. God created the sun and stars, along with humans. This answered all of our questions, but now we have science and technology that can answer these questions and when it comes to answering questions, religion should be our very, very last resort. I still believe that religion can be used as a moral backbone for people or as a meaning to life but it should not challenge a concrete theory such as the Big Bang. Scientific theories should be challenged with other theories. I find it ridiculous that there are still christians trying to prove of their gods existence. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(When I say religion, I mean ‘man made’ organized religions such as Christianity or Catholicity.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Sorry for my ignorance if I am misinterpreting some of your views. I’m currently off middle school so I have been searching for somewhere to drain these thoughts haha&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：白种人没有任何固有的特点，导致欧洲人征服了美洲，如果其他种族处于同样的地位，他们也可能会做同样的事情。]]></title><description><![CDATA[征服 *

有很多人误认为美洲原住民是一个
同质化的群体。事实并非如此。战争和冲突并不是
带来的，而是由欧洲人引入美洲。当时有许多不同的原住民
美国有许多不同的土著部落，他们的理想和利益相互冲突，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otmxoh/cmv_there_is_nothing_inherent_about_whiteness/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otmxoh/cmv_there_is_nothing_inherent_about_whiteness/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 03:44:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conquer*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many people who have a misconception of  native americans being one homogeneous group. This was not the case. War and conflict was not something introduced to the americas by the european. There were many different native american tribes with conflicting ideals and interests that engaged in warfare, and yes, even engaged in slavery, far before european contact. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A very similar mad dash for survival and supremacy which was happening in the lands east of the Atlantic ocean was happening in the lands to the west, before the two had even known of each other, we simply know far more about the former, as those to the east of the Atlantic were far more concerned with the development of written language, the keeping of records, and the survival of those records. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lands to the east of the atlantic, as anyone who is aware of history knows, was constantly embroiled in conflict. The difference between this conflict and the conflict in americas, was that these combatants were far more able to benefit from each other, whereas the the americas were cut off from this participation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The players in the domains to the east of the atlantic were able to engage in a sort of hegelian dialectic by bronze, iron and steel. From conflict between Africa, the west, the near east, and the east, between each other and between themselves, they became stronger and more formidable in a feedback loop of being sharpened by conflict and using that sharpening to better engage with those who have also been sharpened by conflict. Not only through warfare, but also through the trade of goods and ideas on the silk road among other avenues, and also especially in contrast to native americans, a much more comprehensive immune system to certain illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is through exactly the heat caused by this crucible that the great conquerers east of the Atlantic were forged. A process which those west of the atlantic were cut off from, and thus greatly suffered from when they were introduced to a far more skilled and technologically advanced challenger in their domain from across the ocean. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is by mere happenstance that the europeans arrived in america before the great conquerers of the other players east of the atlantic. Every one of these groups had imperialistic and colonialistic factions, though obviously not all of them were equally as successful, and some got complacent. If another one of these groups had made it to the americas first, it is not unlikely we would live in a word where they had been the conquerers of America. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has nothing to do with there being any kind of inherent racial differences, any other group in the exact same circumstances would have done the same, as they had already been doing so and attempting to do so throughout history. To believe otherwise &lt;strong&gt;is&lt;/strong&gt; to believe in some inherent racial differences between races. It does however have much to do with luck. Luck when it comes to availability of resources and other luck of circumstance, the increasing refinement of the ability to utilize these advantages due to baptism and trial by fire, along with the compounding of these factors over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：BLM运动确实已经被黑人至上主义者和有白人负罪感的人所接管。]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，在任何事情之前。我确实相信 "黑人生命重要"。我只是不支持这个
运动了。作为2020年的拉美人，看到所有警察的暴力和虐待行为
虐待真的让我产生了共鸣，所以我在运动高峰期与黑人社区站在一起
在运动的高峰期，我支持黑人社区。但是，一旦拉丁美洲人、穆斯林、亚洲人......。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ot3puu/cmv_blm_movement_has_really_been_taken_over_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ot3puu/cmv_blm_movement_has_really_been_taken_over_by/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 01:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok before anything. I do believe Black Lives Matter. I just don’t support the movement anymore. As a latino in 2020 seeing all the police brutality and mistreatment really resonated with me, so I stood with the black community during the hight of the movement. But once Latinos, Muslims, Asians, natives, LGBT and other groups started advocating for our issue we were shot down by people saying that were stealing form the BLM movement. And as many other movements took place groupie took the ___ lives matter name and used it, Latino Lives matter, Muslim Lives Matter, Asian Lives matter, etc. Supporters of blm called us racist and belittling the movement for using those names. But they use the argument “it doesn’t mean only Black Lives Matter” yet when other groups use it apparently we can’t. And now u see people advocating for segregation from white people and other POC, the usage of slurs against white people and POC who think like me, and calling other black people the c word for differing from thought. And many white people encourage it bc they feel guilt for being white, just the color of their skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：微侵略应该考虑到意图。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的公司要求我参加DEI（多样性公平和包容）培训。
包容）培训，其中指出："不管侵犯者的意图是什么，伤害已经造成。
意图，伤害已经造成"。虽然我理解这种逻辑的由来，但对于工作场所、正义来说，这是一个糟糕的原则。
对于工作场所、司法或社会来说，这是一个糟糕的原则。

让我用一个...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otbfy2/cmv_microaggressions_should_take_intent_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/otbfy2/cmv_microaggressions_should_take_intent_into/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 18:30:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was required by my company to participate in DEI (Diversity Equity and Inclusion) training that stated, &amp;quot;It does not matter what the aggressor intended, harm was caused.&amp;quot; While I understand where this logic comes from, it is a poor principle for the workplace, justice, or society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me use a non-racial analogy: You tripped me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s say I am walking past you sitting down. Our legs make contact and I trip and fall. Let&amp;#39;s look at some possible intents:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You didn&amp;#39;t see me coming and accidentally tripped me, apologized for the accident, and helped me up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You did see me coming, intended to trip me, laughed as I fell, and did not help me up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I saw your legs were there, could have slightly altered my path in order not to trip, and tripped over your legs purposefully with the intent to shame you for having your legs in my path.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the &amp;quot;intent does not matter&amp;quot; logic, all of these scenarios deserve equal treatment. This is obviously wrong to me. Treating someone who does not intend to cause harm as harshly as someone who does is unjust. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And while this point is ancillary, this &amp;quot;intent does not matter&amp;quot; logic alienates would-be supporters of DEI goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：1月6日的委员会将不会追究任何人的责任。这都是政治戏码。]]></title><description><![CDATA[似乎需要听取委员会意见的人是那些最不可能收听的人。
最不可能收看。充其量，他们会从自己喜欢的媒体来源那里得到偷梁换柱的片段。
媒体来源，并由媒体人塑造他们的观点。

我们在弹劾案的审判中看到，传票可以被忽视，而...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osp1i8/cmv_the_jan_6_commission_will_not_hold_anyone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osp1i8/cmv_the_jan_6_commission_will_not_hold_anyone/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 13:36:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems like the people that need to hear the commission are the ones least likely to tune in. At best they’ll get cherry picked clips by their favored media source and have media personalities shape their outlook. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We saw during the impeachment trials that subpoenas can just be ignored with no repercussions. We’ve seen countless senators and reps break the law. We’ve seen people in power threaten politicians (Flynn revisiting an AR and saying maybe he’ll find someone in Washington.) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing gets done. No one is held accountable. This commission will be no different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 地球上的每一个人都需要一门关于 "意识到你周围环境 "的整个小学水平课程。在身体上、情感上、经济上、环境上。]]></title><description><![CDATA[标题说明了一切。我对有多少人不注意他们周围发生的事情感到吃惊。
我对很多人不注意他们周围发生的事情感到吃惊。

我目睹了许多涉及车辆的事故，人们只是简单地受到了伤害。
因为他们没有注意到他们所处的景观或环境。
他们所处的环境。

这包括...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osmu8n/cmv_every_human_on_earth_needs_a_entire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osmu8n/cmv_every_human_on_earth_needs_a_entire/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 10:33:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title says it all. I’m flabbergasted by the amount of people who don’t pay attention to what’s happening around them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve witnessed many accidents involving vehicles and people just plain getting hurt because they aren’t paying attention to the landscape or environment they’re in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This includes economics and planning for your future. It also involves being aware of people’s emotional states whom are close to you so you don’t do or say anything that’s going to hurt them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a survival level ideology. We’re too comfortable and place too much faith in societal safety mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: for clarity, I said “grade-school level.” Doesn’t need to happen in an actual school. Could be parents teaching these values. Sorry for being unclear!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT 2: I’m saying it should happen. I’m not trying to debate the actual semantics of making it happen. That’s an entire different convo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：对于那些被抓获的经营和组织人奴网络的人，特别是当他们使用暴力和威胁来控制受害者的时候，应该给予死刑。]]></title><description><![CDATA[现代奴隶制是西方民主国家最大的笑话之一，如美国。
美国主张反对奴隶制。奴隶制从未消失过，这完全是个笑话
人们更关心囚犯被剥削的问题，因为他们仍然受到法律的人道待遇。
与那些家庭相比，他们仍然受到法律规定的人道待遇，这完全是个笑话...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ot0zb5/cmv_the_death_penalty_should_be_given_to_people/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ot0zb5/cmv_the_death_penalty_should_be_given_to_people/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 05:34:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Modern day slavery is one of the biggest jokes in western democracies like the U.S. that advocates against slavery.
Slavery never went away, it&amp;#39;s a total joke that people care more about inmates labor being exploited when they&amp;#39;re still being treated  humanly under the law compared to the families with children who are smuggled into places like the U.K. and threatened into working for almost nothing but a meal, and are also forced to apply for welfare which is then taken away from them to feed the lavish lifestyle of certain gangs. Criminals and their cults are enduring prison time as it is now a rite of passage for some of them, organizations are ran behind bars, and at times it is prisoners who create dominant criminal organizations. Slaying these modern slave masters on sight should prevent experienced masters from passing their philosophy and experience to their disciples , and demonstrate that slavery isn&amp;#39;t welcomed in modern times. This could be a huge step towards reducing slavery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果我接种了疫苗，我不应该被强制要求戴上口罩，如果他们不打算强制人们接种疫苗。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在过去一年多的时间里，我已经做了我们应该做的一切。我已经在社会上
我在社会上保持距离，在任何地方都戴着口罩，我试着呆在家里，而且我已经尽快接种了疫苗。
我尽快接种了疫苗。我认识的人中唯一没有
至少在我所在的地区，唯一没有接种疫苗的人就是不愿意接种。我为什么要...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osz59q/cmv_if_i_am_vaccinated_i_shouldnt_be_mandated_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osz59q/cmv_if_i_am_vaccinated_i_shouldnt_be_mandated_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 04:41:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve done everything we were supposed to over the past year or so. I&amp;#39;ve socially distanced, I&amp;#39;ve worn my mask everywhere, I&amp;#39;ve tried to stay home, and I&amp;#39;ve gotten the vaccine as soon as I could. The only people I know who aren&amp;#39;t vaccinated, at least in my area, simply don&amp;#39;t want it. Why should I be mandated to wear a mask instead of just mandating people get the vaccine? They&amp;#39;re the reason cases are spiking, but I have to start wearing a mask again to protect them? Please, someone explain to me why I should be mandated to do something to protect people who could be mandated to get a vaccine and put an end to Covid-19.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在美利坚合众国（USA），成人卖淫应该在各地合法化。]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，我认为每一个不影响、不伤害别人的选择都应该
都应该被合法化。成人卖淫（18岁及以上）通常是一种相互之间的协议。
两位成年人之间的协议。一个成年人向另一个成年人支付亲密关系的费用
关系，而且他们都同意这样做。这意味着一个成年人有...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osp0nz/cmv_here_in_the_united_states_of_americausa_adult/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osp0nz/cmv_here_in_the_united_states_of_americausa_adult/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:52:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First of all, I think every choice that doesn&amp;#39;t affect, or harm someone should be legalized. &lt;em&gt;Adult&lt;/em&gt; prostitution(18 years old, and older) is generally a mutual agreement between both adults. One adult pays the other adult for intimate relations, and they both agree on it. This means one adult has the freedom to spend his/her money however he/she wants, and the other adult has the freedom to use his/her body however he/she wants. Therefore, since both choices aren&amp;#39;t harming anything else in society, it should be legalized. One could argue this negatively affects their &amp;quot;personal lives&amp;quot;, but there is some grey area to that statement. One could also argue drinking alcohol, and gambling(just two examples) negatively affects people&amp;#39;s personal lives, yet, both of them are widely legal beginning at 21 years old, so that argument is invalid. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second of all, we already have pornography widely legal in the USA, which is essentially prostitution with an audience. Most porn stars are solely doing porn because they can make quite a bit of money, so isn&amp;#39;t that the same dynamic as prostitution? The only reason I think porn is legal, and not prostitution is because porn helps big business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third of all, one main reason why pornography is illegal is due to it being &amp;quot;immoral&amp;quot;. I don&amp;#39;t think laws should be dictated solely on immorality. Murdering someone, raping someone, and stealing from someone else are actions that are widely considered immoral, &lt;em&gt;but&lt;/em&gt;, all three of those actions also grossly harm other people, and/or ends human lives. On the other hand, as I stated before, alcohol, gambling, and even tobacco use can be considered &amp;quot;immoral&amp;quot; to some people, yet, all of those are widely legal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fourth of all, there are sexually frustrated people who don&amp;#39;t want to  ruin their lives by risking getting caught seeing a prostitute. It may not sound like much, but it could cause someone to be terminated from their job, and being blacklisted from their careers. With legalized prostitution, this wouldn&amp;#39;t be an issue at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other than the flawed &amp;quot;immorality&amp;quot; argument, the only consistent argument I see against legalized prostitution is the notion it would increase human trafficking. However, I think that&amp;#39;s speculation more than anything, and we already have a human trafficking problem in the country anyway, so what difference does this make?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：大多数现代运动都向人们灌输受害者的心理，这是自我毁灭的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想我很难支持大多数运动的一个主要原因是我
只是真的，我是说真的不喜欢受害者的心态。

当我觉得自己是别人的受害者时，我总是处于我最糟糕的状态。
感到自己是别人的受害者，并在事后为自己的不良行为感到有道理。

我肯定不得不...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ostfak/cmv_most_modern_day_movement_instill_victim/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ostfak/cmv_most_modern_day_movement_instill_victim/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:52:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;i guess a major reason why i have a hard time supporting most movements is i just really, and i mean &lt;strong&gt;really&lt;/strong&gt; dont like victim mentalities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’ve always been at my worst as a person when i felt like a victim of someone else, and felt justified of my bad actions after the fact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i’ve definitely had to apologize to people i care about for some things i felt justified doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;at my core, i had taken the poisonous victim mentality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“they did this or did nothing while it happened to me, therefore i can be shitty back”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;victim mentalities lead to people feeling justified doing things they wouldnt let anyone else do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;yes it sucks when people truly are victims, and they definitely need help. dont get me wrong, if you are a victim of something, get the help you need, dig out of it, do what needs to be done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but dont make that apart of who you are and expect everyone else to owe you for what it is you suffered. thats just self destructive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that is what most modern day social movements do.
i see a lot of movements enshrining and making sacred the idea that they are the victim at all times, and when they do shitty things, to question them is akin to kicking a wounded puppy, when really they just did something shitty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;whether it’s BLM, a religion, LGBT, or Conservatives saying theyre being oppressed or having their rights taken away, doing shitting things to your neighbors says more about you than the people you claim to have been victimized by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 西蒙娜-拜尔斯因心理健康而放弃了一项团队运动的最后轮换，这不符合体育精神。]]></title><description><![CDATA[BIG序言。当大坂直美退出法国网球公开赛，而不是被迫参加新闻发布会时
当大坂直美退出法网而不是被迫召开新闻发布会时，我很兴奋，并为这个女人为心理健康站出来而感到骄傲。
为心理健康站出来。

我是心理健康意识的主要倡导者，也是消除对心理健康的污名的倡导者。
围绕它。这不是一个 "闭嘴和...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ospk4x/cmv_simone_biles_bailing_on_the_final_rotation_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ospk4x/cmv_simone_biles_bailing_on_the_final_rotation_of/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 20:37:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BIG preface: When Naomi Osaka withdrew from the French Open instead of being forced to do press conferences, I was hype, and so proud of that woman for standing up for mental health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a &lt;em&gt;massive&lt;/em&gt; proponent of mental health awareness, and removing the stigma around it. This is not a &amp;#39;shut up and dribble&amp;#39; take, I think those are disgusting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m also very open to being told I&amp;#39;m an asshole and changing my mind, because this one feels like it could be one of those. An honest effort. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But... Cmon. Your teammates worked their asses off their whole lives, gave it all up for years, to have a shot. And in that they are not all at the pinnacle of the sport, I&amp;#39;d imagine that was the best and maybe only shot for an Olympic gold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Silver is still incredible and I take nothing away from that. I also understand (or more accurately, could never understand) the immense pressure of competing as your team leader on the Olympic stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But don&amp;#39;t you owe it to your teammates to &lt;em&gt;at least try&lt;/em&gt;? You&amp;#39;re allowed to have a bad day, you&amp;#39;re allowed to not be perfect, and silver in that instance would have still been an incredible accomplishment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But not trying when it matters?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Individual sport, different story, you only owe it to yourself, and you can make the decision. But in a team sport...? Feels &lt;em&gt;really bad&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reddit, Change My View, please.. I&amp;#39;d much rather be proud of the moment than cringe at it. So so open to being wrong here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果盛装舞步可以被认为是一项奥林匹克运动，那么训犬也应该是。或者两者都不应该是奥林匹克运动。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我看来，盛装舞步只是在训练马匹跳舞。它是关于
骑手确保他们已经尽可能地训练了他们的马，使其能够跟随他们的
以便尽可能准确地完成动作。它并不
似乎并不涉及骑手的身体素质。虽然...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osksnn/cmv_if_dressage_can_be_considered_an_olympic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osksnn/cmv_if_dressage_can_be_considered_an_olympic/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 14:35:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;To me it seems that dressage is just training a horse to dance. It&amp;#39;s about the rider ensuring they have trained their horse as well as they can to follow their commands in order to perform the moves as accurately as possible. It doesn&amp;#39;t seem to involve that much physicality from the rider. Although I&amp;#39;m not contesting whether or not it should be considered a sport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does dog training and taking part in dog agility events, or any other events that require a well trained dog, differ? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems that dressage is included, and dog training isn&amp;#39;t, simply because dressage has it&amp;#39;s roots in the upper classes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果你洗澡时的想法是你最感兴趣的想法，你就没有花足够的时间去思考。]]></title><description><![CDATA[淋浴时的想法是众所周知的，这些奇怪或有趣的想法，你只能在淋浴时想到。
只有在洗澡时才能想到的。我的朋友们在讨论这个问题。
他们一致认为，他们最好的想法是在洗澡时产生的。
洗澡时想到的。甚至有一个子reddit来讨论这些有趣的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oshkkh/cmv_if_your_shower_thoughts_are_your_most/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oshkkh/cmv_if_your_shower_thoughts_are_your_most/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 14:35:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shower thought are known to be these weird or interesting thoughts, that you could only think about about in the shower. My friends were talking about this, and there was a consensus between them that their best thoughts come to them in the shower. There&amp;#39;s even a subreddit for these interesting thoughts and revelations that people had while in the shower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lead me to think about what makes the shower so unique compared to the rest of daily life, and what about the shower allows for thoughts to flow freely. From what my friends&amp;#39; said, the shower is a time where they can just think and do nothing else, so it gives them the place to have thoughts that are more interesting than daily life things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This makes sense to me, but if this is the reason for shower thoughts, it also implies that people don&amp;#39;t take the time to think about things outside the shower. Not only that, but people have to shower, so the reason to set this time aside to think about stuff is because you have to in order to be clean. Meaning that just thinking about things is not the first priority while taking a shower and it&amp;#39;s only a byproduct of needing to stay clean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So since we&amp;#39;ve established that the source for shower thoughts is the fact that the shower is a place where you can just think about whatever, I think this means that if you only have interesting thoughts in the shower, that you&amp;#39;re not taking the time to just think about stuff. Same goes for interesting thoughts before you fall asleep - if that is the only time you can think freely, you&amp;#39;re not investing any time in allowing yourself to think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think thinking is so important, and it&amp;#39;s numbing to think only about daily life during the day. If I don&amp;#39;t have enough time to think during the day I have a hard time falling asleep, since that&amp;#39;s the only other time I have if I can&amp;#39;t find the time during the day. How are you supposed to lead your life if the only time you get to think is your 15 minute shower?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：提出虚假强奸指控的人应该得到与他们指控的人相同的监禁时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[在过去的几年里，虚假的强奸指控似乎到处都在出现，其中包括
被指控的人的生活被毁了，而扮演受害者的人却逍遥法外。
逍遥法外。

我不仅认为他们应该为这些虚假的索赔而入狱，而且要得到
我认为他们不仅应该为这些虚假指控入狱，而且应该得到与被指控者相同的时间...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osmddg/cmv_people_who_make_false_rape_claims_should_get/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/osmddg/cmv_people_who_make_false_rape_claims_should_get/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 14:35:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past years, false rape claims seem to be popping up everywhere with the people being accused having their life ruined while the people playing victim go scot free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only do I believe they should go to prison for these false claim, but get the same amount of time as the accused would have or has already served.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason I think this is because the accused will have their life ruined, rape now being on their permanent record, while the ‘victim’ could get a maximum of a year in jail. That is it. That is all they get for ruining a person who did no wrongs life. That’s fucked up!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They should get the exact same as the person they accused. And that’s why I think so. So, Reddit, Change my mind&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美国激进的医疗改革，如全民医保，将对反疫苗运动产生重大影响。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的想法是这样的。反疫苗情绪背后的一个重要（有机）原因是
对医疗行业的不信任。很多人似乎开始走向
很多人似乎一开始就觉得疫苗只是大药厂赚取更多钱的一种方式，从而走上这条道路。
赚更多的钱。在美国，很多人都有第一手的资料...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oslb6j/cmv_radical_healthcare_reform_in_america_such_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oslb6j/cmv_radical_healthcare_reform_in_america_such_as/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 14:35:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My thoughts go like this: A large (organic) reason behind anti-vax sentiment is a distrust in the medical industry. A lot of people seem to start heading down that road by having a feeling that vaccines are just a way for big pharma to make more money. A lot of people in America have first hand experience with significant hospital bills or at least know several other people who have struggled to pay massive bills. The haphazard middle-man insurance industry allows for-profit medical companies to engage in scams/fraud that wouldn&amp;#39;t be as possible under a system like UK&amp;#39;s NHS. Without these kinds of scandals showing up all the time in the news, I think people would be more trusting of the medical industry as a whole, and there would be less anti-vax sentiment. The UK having universal healthcare as well as less apprehension over vaccines suggests there might be some truth to this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：学术界并不偏向于左翼政治，事实才是。]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，我知道这可能会让一些人不高兴，但请听我说完。

学术界是关于观察现实的--尽可能独立地观察现实
尽可能不受我们可能有的文化和社会期望的影响，然后如果这些事实
如果这些事实与我们之前的想法相矛盾，就放弃我们之前的假设，然后......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oskctm/cmv_academia_isnt_biased_towards_leftwing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oskctm/cmv_academia_isnt_biased_towards_leftwing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 14:35:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay, so I am aware that this may upset some people, but hear me out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Academia is all about observing reality as it is - as indepently as possible from cultural and societal expectations we may have - and then if these facts contradict what we previously thought abandon our previous assumptions and be ready to drastically change both our mindset as well as our actions (in cases such as climate change).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This academic attitude of being willing and often even eager to &amp;quot;throw away&amp;quot; the way we traditionally did things and thought about stuff if there&amp;#39;s new evidence makes it really hard for the right to really embrace science- and evidence-based policies. This means science will most of the times be on the side of the left which naturally embraces change less hesitantly and more willingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：核电虽然有时很危险，但与风能和太阳能一样有用]]></title><description><![CDATA[几十年来，人们一直在推动反对核电站及其带来的危险。
它带来的危险。用切尔诺贝利和福岛核灾难等例子来说明。
但是，虽然这些都是悲剧性的，但这并不代表核安全
以及核电的整体效益。

75%的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/os8pwd/cmv_nuclear_power_while_dangerous_at_times_is_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/os8pwd/cmv_nuclear_power_while_dangerous_at_times_is_as/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 01:47:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s been a push for decades now against nuclear power plants and the dangers that come with it. Using examples such as the Chernobyl and Fukushima nuclear disasters, but while these were tragic, this doesn’t represents nuclear safety and the benefits that nuclear power has as a whole. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;75% of Frances energy comes from nuclear power plants and a lot of Sweden’s power is the same, I don’t know much about European power plants, but I haven’t heard much of any accidents occurring in these areas, at least nowhere near the level of others. And while climate activist have sort of stopped nuclear power plants from being built in European countries it hasn’t stopped other countries from mass producing them, a example would be China that puts a new one on the grid every two to three months, supplying its citizens with plenty of energy, and it’s the same in other countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why do we see nuclear power as so dangerous, this is most likely caused by the mentioned nuclear disasters I said earlier. Fukushima while definitely a disaster, acutely didn’t reach dangerous radiation levels. While there definitely was a spike in radiation, it was actually all under the regular safety limit for most nuclear power plants. It was sadly due to mass panic that led to many deaths that occurred not too long after, helping to bring up suicide and depression rates in that time period during the mass evaluation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chernobyl is another example of a terrible tragedy, and while this is definitely A terrible event with mass radiation everywhere way above the lethal limit in some areas. This was all caused by cutting corners or poor maintenance. The reason the plant cut corners was too please soviet dictators of the time as this was a part of Soviet Russia and we all know their standards were really low. But since the Soviet Union disbanded, The Russian government has tried their best to lower the radiation limits, and in fact you can now stand right outside the big dome that was put over top of the plant, and you will not be susceptible to lethal amounts of radiation. No nuclear reactor today will be built like Chernobyl, it will have some of the highest safety regulations that any can get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even when you include all the deaths from major nuclear power disasters, It comes nowhere near the amount of deaths in other power fields such as Coal, Oil, and Natural Gas. It’s even almost as safe as wind and solar in this regard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another reason why people don’t like nuclear power is the waste that is generated from it. But even if you collected all the nuclear waste from just America’s power plants for 60 years straight, The waste that would be generated would only fill The size of an average Walmart, which is somewhat big, but it is pretty easy to get rid of. Bury it hundreds of miles into the earth, or even just shoot it off into space with a few rockets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cost is another thing that’s actually good about nuclear energy, it’s just as cheap as wind and solar, making it good for costs, and it also helps to manufacture them a lot easier. Though right now with Americans regulations, we can only build a nuclear power plant every 12 to 15 years and it can take up 6 to 7 years just to get permission to start building. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While nuclear power can definitely be dangerous in the wrong circumstances, it is a better alternative to other forms of energy, based on its safety, Energy efficiency, and Low costs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：应将牙科护理纳入医疗保健系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[这场辩论在美国以外的地方更有意义，因为那里有全民免费医疗。
的国家，更确切地说，是拥有强大的医疗保健系统的欧洲国家。
但不包括牙科护理

显然，有人在某个时候决定，嘴巴不是人体的一部分。
人体的一部分（？我是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/os5z4m/cmv_dental_care_should_be_included_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/os5z4m/cmv_dental_care_should_be_included_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 20:34:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This debate is more relevant outside the US where universal free healthcare is a thing, more specifically european countries that have a strong healthcare system that does not include dental care&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently someone at some point decided that the mouth is not a part of the human body (?). I am having a problem in my jaw that causes pain, will only get worse, and has to be fixed with dental care. It is not related to hygiene and there is nothing I could have done to prevent it. I am pissed that I am spending so much money with this. If it was a problem anywhere else in my body, I would have it covered by the universal healthcare system I have access to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can anyone please try to convince me that it is a good idea to not include dental care in the system?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few points that I wanna argue preemptively before anyone tries:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;It is expensive, not even healthcare should be universal!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;no thanks to the american dystopia. I love the healthcare system I have access to, and I want it to be even bigger. I don&amp;#39;t advocate only for myself, but also for poorer people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;People will become careless with their teeth!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&amp;#39;t believe that. Obesity rates in America prove otherwise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;A lot of dental treatment is unnecessary&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;don&amp;#39;t cover these then. Same way the healthcare system does not cover plastic surgery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：作为平民穿着迷彩服并不具有攻击性。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚买了一个小单肩包（Eastpak-Classic-style），因为它在打折。
因为它在打折，我这周要参加一个节日，上面有一个迷彩图案。I
我被告知这可能会引起反感，或者人们可能不喜欢它，它可能会破坏营地的气氛。
例如，在营地的气氛。我对此感到很惊讶，因为我...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/os08cv/cmv_wearing_camopatterns_as_a_civilian_is_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/os08cv/cmv_wearing_camopatterns_as_a_civilian_is_not/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 17:41:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just bought a small shoulder bag (eastpak-classic-style) ,because it was on sale, for a festival i will attend this week and it has a camo pattern on it. I was told this could be offensive or people may dislike it and it could kill the vibe in the camp for example. I was surprised by this as i didnt think this could be this big of a deal and i want to know why this would be offensive to some people. I usually live by &amp;quot;live and let live&amp;quot; and i dont feel like im affecting anyones freedom here. Please explain to me why this could be offensive to some, im open for discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：工作申请中的心理测试弊大于利。他们吓跑了高潜力的员工，并不总是能找到一个合适的团队。]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为一名招聘经理，我一直在考虑这个问题，有一段时间了。我喜欢选择
我喜欢亲自挑选我的团队的候选人，并一直在寻求创建一个平衡的高绩效团队。
表现的团队。我觉得这些测试过于关注潜在的心理学
问题，或是否符合公司的文化政策，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/orvnvw/cmv_psychological_tests_in_job_applications_do/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/orvnvw/cmv_psychological_tests_in_job_applications_do/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a hiring manager I&amp;#39;ve been contemplating this for a while. I enjoy selecting my team&amp;#39;s candidates myself and am always looking to create a well balanced high performing team. I feel these tests focus too much on potential Psychological problems or fits to what the company&amp;#39;s cultural policy is, when those people may actually prove just what the team needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t have any research from HR to back up what the right way of hiring through tests is, but I worry the HR department will overrule my own autonomy in selecting employees through these tests. I want to look at all perspectives so I can prepare myself for potential discussions with HR on their policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美国不应重新实行封锁/限制，而是允许选择不接种疫苗的人按照自己的意愿被感染和/或死亡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[鉴于以下事实。

 * 现在美国几乎所有的COVID死亡都是在未接种疫苗的人中发生的。
   [https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-941fcf43d9731c76c16e7354f5d5e187]
 * 疫苗接种情况与政治派别高度相关
   [https://jahoo.shinyapps.io/vaxpolitics/]
 *...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/orzj99/cmv_the_us_should_not_reimpose/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/orzj99/cmv_the_us_should_not_reimpose/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the Following Facts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-941fcf43d9731c76c16e7354f5d5e187&quot;&gt;Nearly all COVID deaths in US are now among unvaccinated&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jahoo.shinyapps.io/vaxpolitics/&quot;&gt;Vaccination status is highly correlated with political affiliation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/paighowal/viz/TrackingCovidVaccinationsintheUS/CovidVaccinationsintheUS&quot;&gt;Total vaccinations are plateauing, showing no sign of increased growth.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://covid19-projections.com/path-to-herd-immunity/&quot;&gt;Projections show we will only ever reach 65% total Vaccination&lt;/a&gt;, leaving 100+ million people unvaccinated. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obvious Caveats:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Children, Pregnant Women, and those with legitimate medical condition preventing vaccination should be cared for and protected within reason, provided all medical care necessary, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The US should continue to provide vaccines to any and all who want them, and try to reach rural communities who may not have easy access. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Position:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can never eradicate Covid, as it has already become endemic. The vaccines have been proven effective with no long-term side effects, and have been made freely available along with incentives and a massive PR initiative. IE: Covid is an inescapable, but preventable illness at this point. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thus, we should accept the bodily autonomy of the willingly unvaccinated, and allow them to be infected and/or die of coronavirus.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would even go so far as to say we should allow insurance companies to deny them medical coverage. If they want to take their chances with the virus, that&amp;#39;s their right, and we should let them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, if we allowed this population to become infected, that population would build some natural biological immunity to current and future covid variants. It would be better to build that immunity now, while the vaccines are still effective, than hold out trying to prevent transmission until a new variant emerges that the vaccines do not work against. The Devil we know (Delta primarily) is better than the Devil we Don&amp;#39;t know. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please, CMV redditors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：使奥运会本质上成为 "按次收费"，违背了活动的本意。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是以美国为中心的，因为我知道许多国家比我们这里更容易观看到
因为我知道许多国家比我们这里更容易观看奥运会。要想合法地观看奥运会
如果不先支付一些服务费，就不可能合法观看奥运会，这绝对会破坏我对奥运会的任何热情。
我可能对奥运会有任何热情。我明白，训练和...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/orlp6u/cmv_making_the_olympics_essentially_pay_per_view/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/orlp6u/cmv_making_the_olympics_essentially_pay_per_view/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 01:38:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is US-centric since I know many countries have easier access to watching the Olympics than we do here.  It is impossible to legally watch the Olympics without paying for some service first, and that absolutely wrecks any enthusiasm I might have had for the Games.  I get that the training and travel are not free, but why must I line the pockets of NBC and cable companies to watch &amp;quot;team USA&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The greed it illustrates to me is almost comical in nature, and even goes beyond that this year.  I broke down and signed up for Peacock (NBC&amp;#39;s new streaming service) because they advertised that they were streaming coverage, only to find out that paying for yet another service wasn&amp;#39;t good enough for full access.  My wife is a horse person and loves the equestrian events, but those weren&amp;#39;t included.  Why?  Probably because I needed to be punished for not having a cable subscription.  It is so sad and totally unnecessary.  I guess it is pretty American to suck every penny of profit out of something, but when that something is supposed to be &amp;quot;national pride&amp;quot;, I feel that is a step too far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*edit* - typo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：很多旨在帮助支持少数民族的规则/法律/政策只是在宣传他们自己做不到的想法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[例如，Reddit的政策关于他们的第一条规则是没有骚扰，欺凌。
等。该规则的一个规定是，它只适用于那些实际
骚扰的群体，所以不包括白人或男性（这实际上是Reddit的官方立场）。
这实际上是Reddit管理员的官方立场）。)

像这样的规则基本上不是说...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/orj6za/cmv_a_lot_of_ruleslawspolicies_that_are_meant_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/orj6za/cmv_a_lot_of_ruleslawspolicies_that_are_meant_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:34:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit&amp;#39;s policy for example regarding their #1 rule is no harassment, bullying, etc. A stipulation of the rule is that it only applies to groups that actually face harassment, so not white people or men (this is actually the official stance of reddit admins)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do rules like this not basically say that reddit admins believe minority groups cannot take harassment the same way white people can? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There used to be a term that I saw thrown around a lot called the &amp;quot;White Savior Complex&amp;quot;. And I feel like as we&amp;#39;ve moved more and more in the direction of enacting these types of policies, I don&amp;#39;t really see criticism of white saviors anymore. It&amp;#39;s almost like we&amp;#39;ve just accepted it. Change my view?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: This is getting way way more attention than I expected very quickly. I&amp;#39;ll reply as best I can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美国人是发达国家中被宣传得最厉害的人]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，我不是说美国人很愚蠢。我是认真的。

我走过很多地方，在一些国家生活过（包括美国），这是
我一直在想这个问题。很明显，我在这里有一个巨大的选择偏见。
在我这里（这使得这个观点非常容易改变）。

中国，对于...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ork9l0/cmv_americans_are_the_most_heavily_propagandized/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ork9l0/cmv_americans_are_the_most_heavily_propagandized/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 22:34:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First off, I&amp;#39;m not saying that Americans are stupid.  Seriously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve travelled a lot and lived in a few countries (including the US) and this is a thought that I keep coming back to. Obviously there&amp;#39;s a huge selection bias here on my part (which makes this a very changeable view)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China, for example, is a heavily propagandized country but my experience with Chinese people is that they understand that it&amp;#39;s to be taken with a grain of salt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think a disproportionate number of Americans think that they aren&amp;#39;t being subjected to propaganda; that their preferred news source is telling it like it really is; that their preferred politicians genuinely care about their well-being. I&amp;#39;d say this applies to both the right and the left but mainstream American politics doesn&amp;#39;t have a left-wing so let&amp;#39;s say it applies to the right and the far-right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this would be nearly impossible to prove/disprove with data so I&amp;#39;m just looking for opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS - I think the mode of argumentation here is going to be something like &amp;quot;other countries are worse&amp;quot; but that&amp;#39;s exactly the kind of whataboutism that American propaganda specializes in. So maybe don&amp;#39;t do that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：阴谋论横行，因为我们的 "领导人 "众所周知总是在撒谎和气话。]]></title><description><![CDATA[几乎所有的政治权威人物都以撒谎和歪曲事实而闻名。
我不是历史学者，但似乎世世代代都是如此。
我们允许他们对我们撒谎，在我们想相信的时候相信我们想相信的东西。
相信已知的骗子比相信阴谋论的胡说八道更愚蠢，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/orj12f/cmv_conspiracy_theories_run_rampant_because_our/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/orj12f/cmv_conspiracy_theories_run_rampant_because_our/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 21:42:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost every authority figure in politics is known to lie and twist the truth. I&amp;#39;M no historical scholar but it seems that has been the case for generations. We allow them to lie to us and believe what we want to when we want to. Believing known liars is dumber than believing conspiracy nonsense, imo. When the main sources that inform the public are known to be corrupt then people will seek information elsewhere. The constant lies from authority are more to blame for the rise of conspiracies than the people just being dumb and believing whatever nonsense they find online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我们需要核电站或化石燃料电站来进行基荷发电。在目前的技术和经济状况下，>90%的可再生能源是不可能的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好。

这是我希望能改变或更新我的想法的事情。
基本上，这是最古老的反对可再生能源的论点。我认为并且
我认为并且仍然认为这是一个严重的问题，当涉及到改造我们的能源
但在公众面前，这个问题似乎不那么令人关注。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oragxs/cmv_we_need_nuclear_or_fossil_fuel_power_plants/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oragxs/cmv_we_need_nuclear_or_fossil_fuel_power_plants/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 18:30:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;so this is something I would like to have my mind changed or updated about. Basically, this is the oldest argument against renewable energy. I thought and still think this is a serious problem when it comes to transforming our energy generation, but it seems to be less of a concern in public discourse nowadays, so has something changed? Do we have a solution now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me sketch the argument and my assumptions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Power demand varies significantly throughout the day and year, but there is a certain minimum amount of power that has to be available at all times. Baseload power plants are those which put out a constant amount of power, 24 hours of the day, every day. Other sources of energy which are not &amp;quot;baseload&amp;quot; have strongly fluctuating power output.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me list the most common methods of energy generation and if they can serve as baseload power plants:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baseload: oil/coal/gas, nuclear, bio oil and gas, hydro, geothermal&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluctuating: Solar, Wind, more unusual things like tidal power etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, why do you need baseload power plants? If you basically all of your enegry production comes from fluctuating sources then you need to ensure that your energy production does not vary too much from demand. Underproduction is clearly bad, but as I understood overproduction of energy is NOT a trivial problem either: If your power plant produces power that is not needed at the moment then you can not just get rid of it/waste it in some easy way. This is demonstrated by the fact that negative energy prices are a thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what does this mean practically? First of all, as I understood, wind (which may actually be baseload), hydro, bio oil and gas, geothermal and other renewable power sources can NOT replace the amount of power generated cussently by fossil fuels and nuclear, simply on a level of power output. Is this wrong?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most countries usually already use all their opportunities for hydro power plants and even if they don&amp;#39;t, there just isn&amp;#39;t a very high maximum possible power output here. Geothermal is more something for individual home power generation and is highly dependent on your geographical location. Wind is good but you would struggle to get anywhere close to what fossils do at the moment only with wind. Bio oil and gas are not very efficient for power generationa s you have to invest power to grow them, they are more useful to be used as a fuel, so efficient power storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only renewable energy which actually seems great to me in terms of raw power output per price is solar. I am 100% convinced that most countries could generate the amount of power they use with solar, the problem is just that the output varies very very significantly between day and night (and summer and winter).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(EDIT: So nuclear power is supposed to be excluded here, I&amp;#39;m trying to udnerstand how countries want to do this that want to get rid of nuclear power together with fossil fuels).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You would have to overbuild solar to deal with the winter and then have too much generated power in summer. And of course the biggest problem are the nights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The obvious answer is power storage to bridge the nights and generally cushion the fluctuations. But I have never heard a good answer to the fact that we don&amp;#39;t have any technology which could give us power storage on a sufficient scale. Batteries are cool and we are making great progress, but it is already a momentuous task to supply enough batteries just for the future EV fleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hydro energy storage is good but again, the maximum possible capactiy here is just not large enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides that I don&amp;#39;t know of any good ways to store enregy whicha aren&amp;#39;t  sitting in laboratories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sooooo basically how exactly are we going to do this transition to renewable energies? What is the plan?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best I can imagine is that EVs will be connected to the grid and then the battery capacity from cars can be used to power homes at night !? But idk man, it seems like batteries are already in really high demand and it will take many decades before most cars are EVs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alternatively we could invent a new form of power storage, okay, but I don&amp;#39;t know of anything promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：选择同时使用她/他们或他/他们的代名词，但当有人不使用这两种代名词时就会生气，这很可笑。]]></title><description><![CDATA[歌手哈尔西最近宣布，在一家杂志误用她的代名词后，她将不会再做更多的新闻报道。
一家杂志在误用她的代名词后 "故意不尊重 "她。该
该杂志在她的文章封面上提到她使用 "她/他们"，因为她对这两个词都很满意。
但在其余部分只使用了 "她 "的代词。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/or8mye/cmv_choosing_to_use_both_shethey_or_hethey/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/or8mye/cmv_choosing_to_use_both_shethey_or_hethey/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 13:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Singer Halsey has recently declared she will not be doing more press after a magazine “deliberately disrespected” her after misusing her pronouns.  The magazine on the cover of her article referred to her using “she/they” as she is happy with either but then only used the “she”pronoun for the rest of the article. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will always respect people’s pronouns but you can’t have a go at someone for only using one of your preferred pronouns, I feel like this is elitist and is setting up people to feel attacked when they are trying to do the right thing and respect people’s choice of pronouns.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit - I also just noticed I also used only the “she” pronoun when writing this and not out of a place of disrespect so please do not attack me but rather try to CMV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在这一点上，那些声称 "黑人生活重要 "只意味着 "黑人生活重要 "或其某种变体的人是在恶意争辩和/或故意无视。]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好，CMV社区。

我的CMV几乎就是这个题目。我很难相信，那些把BLM理解为只有黑人生命重要或某种变体的人
BLM的意思是只有黑人的生命才重要，或者是一些变种，我很难相信这些人要么是
恶意争论和/或故意无知。我相信，那些
我认为，有这种想法的人是在试图诋毁...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oqy6s6/cmv_at_this_point_people_who_claim_that_black/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oqy6s6/cmv_at_this_point_people_who_claim_that_black/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 07:30:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello, CMV community,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My CMV is pretty much the title. I find it hard to believe that people who take BLM to mean that ONLY Black Lives Matter or some variation of that are either arguing in bad faith and/or are willfully ignorant. I believe that people who think this are attempting to discredit the BLM movement or are refusing to do even a little bit if research into what BLM actually means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interesting part of this discussion, I think, is that proponents of the &amp;quot;counter-movement&amp;quot; (if you want to call it that) -- Blue Lives Matter -- do not seem to insinuate that ONLY blue lives matter. I take this to mean that they know exactly what BLM means and are being hypocritical about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ypu can change my view by showing me how someone might still somehow not understand what BLM means, or by showing how proponents of Blue Lives Matter are NOT being hypocritical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>