<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 04:33:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：压制COVID反疫苗者等并不是打击错误信息的正确方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[在看到许多子版块被私有化，试图迫使Reddit的手，以便
他们禁止诸如NoNewNormal和其他这类社区的分站，这让我开始
这让我开始思考我们如何对待有这些争议性观点的人和社区。
观点，Reddit对回声室一直都很糟糕，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pfbcp1/cmv_silencing_covid_antivaxxers_etc_isnt_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pfbcp1/cmv_silencing_covid_antivaxxers_etc_isnt_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After seeing many subreddits go private in an attempt to force Reddit&amp;#39;s hand so they ban subs such as NoNewNormal and other such communities, it&amp;#39;s made me start to think about how we treat people and communities with these controversial view points, Reddit has always been bad for echo-chambers, however despite that, I think one of the main appeals of the platform for me personally has been the opportunity to see opposing viewpoints and have proper critical discussions that you can&amp;#39;t really get elsewhere, right now everyone&amp;#39;s very much in a Us vs. Them mindset, and if we start silencing communities that spout out misinformation, I&amp;#39;m not entirely sure we&amp;#39;re going to help the problem but rather make it much much worse as people start to internalize their belief that they&amp;#39;re being silenced and further believe in what they believe in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, I guess what I&amp;#39;m trying to say is that to combat misinformation, just shutting it down at this stage does more harm than good, Reddit has always been a free platform, albeit recently it has changed dramatically and it seems the admins pick and choose who gets silenced, but at the end of the day the people on these subreddits are just going to find another outlet, and push them further into the echo chamber, instead, surely we should just let everyone be, and discuss the issues fairly and critically whenever we can, I would love and welcome a good debate on this, and what exactly shutting these communities down will do in the long run?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I should also mention that important subreddits dedicated to discussing Covid are privating themselves for this exact reason, notably &lt;a href=&quot;/r/CoronavirusUK&quot;&gt;/r/CoronavirusUK&lt;/a&gt; have done this, and I&amp;#39;ve always used that sub to get all the important information I need about the state of the pandemic in my country, surely this is counter-intuitive and does more harm than good when it comes to misinformation??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 如果它能使你的生活变得更好，并且不会导致你伤害他人，那么信教就是理性的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我认为有太多关于上帝是否存在的文字了，而关于相信上帝是否合理的文字却不够多。
而关于相信上帝是否合理的文字却不够多。我打算
我打算在假设上帝不存在的情况下写这篇文章，因为我认为这将
与普通的Reddit用户产生更好的共鸣，尽管我并不...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pfamvb/cmv_if_it_makes_your_life_better_and_doesnt_cause/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pfamvb/cmv_if_it_makes_your_life_better_and_doesnt_cause/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:47:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think there are far too many words written about whether God exists and not enough written about whether it is rational to believe in God. I&amp;#39;m going to write this under the assumption that God doesn&amp;#39;t exist because I think that will resonate with the average Reddit user better though I don&amp;#39;t necessarily think that myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We engage in all sorts of useful fictions just because they make life easier. Like that &amp;quot;everything will turn out fine in the end&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;your vote counts.&amp;quot; These are things we all deep down know aren&amp;#39;t necessarily true but they are necessary lies to keep our society functional. We all know that our individual vote will basically have zero impact but we believe that it will have some because if everyone thought realistically, democracy wouldn&amp;#39;t work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think there are many situations in which the same logic can be applied to religion. Even if rationally you know you can&amp;#39;t prove a religion to be true, I think in a lot of cases it could still be useful to believe that it is true. While there are many religious groups that spread more hate than love, there are plenty to choose from that do just the opposite. I am not talking about those religions that are hateful in their message, because I don&amp;#39;t believe those are useful beliefs to have. On the Christian front there are organizations like the United Church of Canada who treat homosexual people as equals. Most North American Mahayana Buddhist groups have done away with any sort of discrimination against women or homosexual people as well. Sikh groups also have a tendency towards acceptance. Those are the types of groups I&amp;#39;m saying can be of use to be a part of and believe in. I think people on Reddit tend to forget that there are more religions than evangelical Protestantism, traditional Catholicism, and fundamentalist Islam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Religious people are statistically happier and are given a community and something to be a part of. Provided the right one is chosen, religion can encourage people to be more empathetic and loving. Some religious groups even mandate charity. Remember, I am only advocating for participation in religious groups that advocate empathy towards all, what I classify as useful beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that if believing in religion causes you to be happier and a better person, then that belief is rational. If you&amp;#39;re a materialist atheist you believe that we only have one chance at this life, is it not rational to spend it in the way that makes you happiest and causes you to increase the happiness of others? I don&amp;#39;t believe in some supreme value of truth above all else, I think sometimes belief in the irrational can be a great benefit. That isn&amp;#39;t to say that truth isn&amp;#39;t very important in many cases, just that sometimes fiction is more useful than truth. I think it&amp;#39;s time to stop asking whether belief in religion is rational, and time to start asking whether it is rational to believe. If we had proof of God, then faith would not be necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：史蒂夫-欧文经常对动物进行愚蠢的冒险，动物杀死他只是时间问题。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我首先要说的是，史蒂夫-欧文似乎是一个真正的好人
有一颗大心脏。他显然热爱动物，并为保护动物奉献了自己的一生。
它们。

这可以理解为使他成为大多数Redditors眼中的英雄。我并不是
试图攻击他这个人。他不应该被...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pey51f/cmv_steve_irwin_regularly_took_stupid_risks_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pey51f/cmv_steve_irwin_regularly_took_stupid_risks_with/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:47:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll start by saying that Steve Irwin seems like he was a genuinely nice guy with a big heart. He clearly loved animals and dedicated his life to protecting them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This has understandably made him a hero in the eyes of most Redditors. I&amp;#39;m not trying to attack him as a person. He didn&amp;#39;t deserve to get hurt, let alone killed. But I think his death serves as a cautionary tale about messing with wild animals, much like &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Timothy_Treadwell&quot;&gt;Timothy Treadwell&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I knew a lot of people working in conservation while Irwin was alive. They were all waiting with dread for the day one of his stunts would kill him. No one expected it to be a stingray - it&amp;#39;s extremely uncommon to be killed by one. But if someone was going to die by stingray, it was going to be the guy who regularly took insane risks with animals - that was the consensus when it happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently made a comment about this on &lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/Damnthatsinteresting/comments/pdaaez/of_course_steve_irwin_shreds_in_khaki_should_have/&quot;&gt;a video showing him draping an extremely venomous wild sea snake over his head, with the snake&amp;#39;s head resting on his eyelid&lt;/a&gt;. As I expected, I received a good dose of downvotes. I was told that deaths from stingrays are extremely rare. My counter to that was - if a person takes enough risks (big and small) with wild animals, eventually something will go wrong. Play with fire long enough and you&amp;#39;ll get burnt. I was told that stingray deaths are rare again. That conversation wasn&amp;#39;t going anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; surprising that it was a stingray that got him. It was more likely that he&amp;#39;d be killed by one of the more dangerous animals he regularly harassed. But anyone who knows wild animals knows that every animal that can defend itself is inherently dangerous - stingrays included. Irwin knew that too. Keep in mind, he wasn&amp;#39;t handling wild animals in a safe way, he was deliberately antagonizing them and taking unnecessary risks to create engaging content (like in the video linked above). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And let&amp;#39;s dig into the stingray thing for a moment. It was a short-tail stingray, which are generally docile. So what made this one attack Irwin? I&amp;#39;ve helped free short-tail stingrays from fishing nets before, and when they feel threatened they&amp;#39;re anything but docile. Another good way to make an animal feel threatened is to sneak up above and behind it. Or to corner it between people. Irwin would have known that too. But, according to Irwin&amp;#39;s cameraman, he did both of those things. And, while threatening the stingray, he positioned himself  in a way that put his exposed chest and abdomen within striking distance. No one should ever be doing that. It would be surprising if it wasn&amp;#39;t consistent with his modus operandi: putting himself in harm&amp;#39;s way to make exciting TV. The cameraman was told to keep filming if he was attacked, no matter how viciously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But let&amp;#39;s say, hypothetically, that he did &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt; right in that situation, my original point stands: dealing wild animals is like Russian Roulette. There are a lot of chambers, and you start with only one bullet. When you antagonize an animal, you add more bullets. Even more if they&amp;#39;re usually dangerous, and more again if you get in their space. But you only need one bullet to lose Russian Roulette. And he loaded a lot of bullets that really didn&amp;#39;t need to be there. Over and over and over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Irwin liked to downplay the danger of wild animals and I think he genuinely believed it to a degree. It&amp;#39;s a dangerous attitude and it&amp;#39;s stupid. Irwin should have known better. But he kept pulling the trigger, and eventually he lost the game. CMV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My sources are the Wikipedia articles on &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Steve_Irwin&quot;&gt;Steve Irwin&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stingray_injury&quot;&gt;stingray injuries&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Short-tail_stingray&quot;&gt;short-tail stingrays&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20140310154552/http://www.independent.co.uk/news/people/news/steve-irwins-final-words-cameraman-present-at-death-opens-up-about-deadly-stingray-attack-for-the-first-time-9181077.html&quot;&gt;this interview with the cameraman&lt;/a&gt; cited in some of those articles, and many hours of watching &lt;em&gt;The Crocodile Hunter&lt;/em&gt; when I was young.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought about posting this in &lt;a href=&quot;/r/unpopularopinion&quot;&gt;r/unpopularopinion&lt;/a&gt; but I really want to understand why most people on Reddit seem to disagree with me. It can&amp;#39;t just be that people don&amp;#39;t want to acknowledge the faults of their hero, can it? I love it when something makes me change my mind. Please tell me what I&amp;#39;m missing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Edit&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I&amp;#39;m not asking you to convince me stingray deaths are absurdly rare. I already know.&lt;/strong&gt; I knew how rare they were before I posted this. I knew before he died. I&amp;#39;ve acknowledged it in my post several times, and explained why that argument doesn&amp;#39;t hold much weight. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/comments/pey51f/cmv_steve_irwin_regularly_took_stupid_risks_with/hb0skg2?context=3&quot;&gt;I&amp;#39;ve said a bit more about it in this comment&lt;/a&gt;. I have experience with this species that I&amp;#39;m betting few here have ever had. The fact that he was killed by such an unlikely animal only further emphasizes my point about how the risks he took.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your point is just some version of &amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s extremely rare&amp;quot; without at least addressing some of the counterpoints I&amp;#39;ve made, you can&amp;#39;t expect to CMV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Edit 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve posted what I think it&amp;#39;s a well-written argument that&amp;#39;s generated a significant amount of comments. I feel like I&amp;#39;m being amicable, articulate, and open minded. My views might be wrong, that&amp;#39;s why I&amp;#39;m here. But it seems people are downvoting this post because they disagree with me. That really doesn&amp;#39;t help CMV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 3. I fixed a typo. The downvotes seem to have slowed right down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: r/AITA是一个让人们的决定得到验证的地方，不管他们是否是真正的混蛋。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到的90%的AITA帖子都是人们在发表道德上有问题的决定/行动。
的决定/行动，然后因为这些行动而被奉承。

我看到很少有帖子真正指出发帖人的行为，甚至更少的帖子试图看到冲突的双方。
试图看到冲突的双方的帖子就更少了。

更有甚者，一些人的行为的后果......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pf7x1g/cmv_raita_is_a_place_for_people_to_get_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pf7x1g/cmv_raita_is_a_place_for_people_to_get_their/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:47:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;90% of the AITA posts I see are people posting morally questionable decisions/actions, then getting fawned over for those actions.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see few posts that actually call out the poster for their actions, and even fewer that try to see both sides of a conflict.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even more, the consequences of some of these actions are out of balance to the offense, the response is out of proportion, and often times refuses to realistically fix an issue.  The entire point is to assign blame and make OP feel better about themselves.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since it&amp;#39;s not trying to see past &amp;quot;OP good, everyone else bad,&amp;quot; it is actively harmful.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：法律/法规的宗教豁免不应成为一种事物]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我看来，宗教豁免可以归结为："如果你有一个坚定的信念，那就是
如果你有坚定的信念，认为你不应该遵守这个规则，那么你就不必
遵循该规则"。但是，只有当你属于一个预先批准的群体，而这些人
他们也强烈认为他们不应该遵守该规则。

I...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pemlsq/cmv_religious_exemptions_to_lawsregulations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pemlsq/cmv_religious_exemptions_to_lawsregulations/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 22:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I see it, religious exemptions boil down to, &amp;quot;If you have a firmly held belief that you should not have to follow this rule, then you don&amp;#39;t have to follow the rule.&amp;quot; But only if you belong to a pre-approved group of people who also feel strongly that they shouldn&amp;#39;t have to follow that rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see no practical difference between, &amp;quot;I really really don&amp;#39;t want to do that&amp;quot; and, &amp;quot;God says I don&amp;#39;t have to do that&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we as a society deem a rule important enough to make it a law, it should apply to everyone equally, regardless of whether or not they want to follow that law. And if we as a society feel like a proposed rule is not so important that absolutely everyone needs to follow it regardless of how they feel about it, then we should not make that rule into a law at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally, this is most commonly about vaccine hesitancy nowadays, but I think that religious exemptions across the board should be abolished. For example, I used to lifeguard at a pool where there were many patrons that practice Islam. Muslim women would come to the pool wearing ankle length flowing dresses, expecting to be able to swim. I lost track of the number of times that I had to tell them that swimming in a large piece of fabric that can wrap them up and limit their mobility in the water is too unsafe to be allowed, only for them to come back with, &amp;quot;But my religion says I have to wear this.&amp;quot; Well, then your religion also implies that you cannot swim in our pool.  (We did sell modesty swim suits, made of swim suit material, that were ankle length and wrist length, with a head covering. They were specifically designed to be safe to swim in while also covering all skin except hands, feet, and face. Some of the women did not feel like the closer (safer) fit of these modesty suits was modest enough to fit with their religious restrictions.) The rule about not wearing loose, flowy clothing while swimming is a safety rule important enough that everyone needs to follow it without exceptions. If it were determined that it&amp;#39;s not so important that there should be no exceptions, then the rule shouldn&amp;#39;t exist in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果你反疫苗是因为你相信 "我的身体我做主"，那么你也一定是支持选择的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这一切都源于我一直从反疫苗阵营中听到的这种反应，"我的身体
我的身体，我的选择"，这听起来非常像我们长期以来从支持选择权运动中听到的东西。
这听起来非常像我们从支持选择权运动中听到的东西，已经有很长一段时间了。我认为，如果你相信这句话
作为反对接种疫苗的论据，你就有...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/percty/cmv_if_youre_antivax_because_you_believe_in_my/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/percty/cmv_if_youre_antivax_because_you_believe_in_my/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 22:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It all stems from this response I keep hearing from the anti-vax camp &amp;quot;my body my choice&amp;quot;, which sounds an awful lot like something we&amp;#39;ve been hearing from the pro-choice movement for a long time. I think that if you believe in that statement as an argument for being anti-vaccination that you have to also be pro-choice. There seems to be a large overlap of people who are anti-vax and evangelical (anti-abortion), which got me thinking...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only argument I&amp;#39;ve been able to come up with being against this line of thinking is that abortion effects a 3rd party (the fetus) where as a vaccination only effects the host. My argument would be that when you choose to not get vaccinated you&amp;#39;re choice doesn&amp;#39;t just effect you. Your choice has the potential to effect countless other people around you including death. If you infect someone with something you&amp;#39;re carrying and they die because of it I&amp;#39;d argue that you caused the death of that person. Sure you could argue it&amp;#39;s not a one-to-one thing and there&amp;#39;s a chance that you might not infect anyone, but ultimately it&amp;#39;s a choice you&amp;#39;re making that has the potential to effect a lot of people who didn&amp;#39;t have a choice in the matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, yeah, I don&amp;#39;t really see how you can be anti-vax and not also pro-choice. Change my view!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美国的教育/劳动系统已经崩溃。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我把教育和劳动结合在一起，因为它们是相辅相成的。
教育的目的不仅是为了教育下一代，使人们变得有知识
知识，而且也是为了让人们能够获得职业，过上有意义的生活。
因此，我将把这个问题分成三部分。

第1部分。K...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pem04k/cmv_the_educationlabor_system_in_the_united/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pem04k/cmv_the_educationlabor_system_in_the_united/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 20:39:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am combining Education and Labor as the same because they go hand in hand, the purpose of education is not only to teach the under generations so people become knowledgeable but also so that people can get careers and live productive lives. So I am going to split this into 3 parts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part 1. K-12&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The issue with the current system is that we teach based on age not based on ability. School should have 3 levels for each subject in each grade. Behind, normal and advanced. Each level should have tests that place a child and allow them to move up at ANY TIME. They should be able to request a test at any time, and all courses should have an online option for those who move faster then the class. If a child is able to test out of their grade they should imminently move up to the next level. Once they are done with all 12 (13) grades they are done with school and can go on to other things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part 2. Higher education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Higher education aka college/university is a terrible system, there are about 3 careers that I would say need University and that is Lawyers, Doctors, and Educators. Because those require a lot of text book learning that can&amp;#39;t be left to individual companies to teach. Other then that, everything else should be taught by the companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies and industries not only should teach their prospective employees though academies or training but they have an incentive to. If people have to go to no cost training/academies for employment you are much more likely to keep the employees you hire for their whole career since switching will be more time then its worth and they will start at a younger age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part 3. At Will Employment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At will employment is one of the biggest frauds committed against the American people ever. In 49 out of 50 states Employment at Will is the law. That means that a company can hire you and fire you for any reason (that is not protected) and you can quit for any reason at any time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hire at will, fire at will, quit at will sounds nice right? Nope that means...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;On call 24/7 oh it says you only have to work for specific hours and yes you do get over time, however if you refuse then they can fire you and you can&amp;#39;t do anything because fire at will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stagnant wages there is no incentive to give you a raise or hell even keep your pay the same because since you aren&amp;#39;t contract they can just fire you and no even give a reason and then hire a different person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;No reason fires you effectively don&amp;#39;t have any rights because they simply just have to make up a reason or say nothing at all and you are gone, try going to HR because of inappropriate or intentional bad behavior meant to try to get you to quit or just take advantage they can say bye.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arbitration the bullshit that removes the courts, that any private sector employee likely signed because of course they can force you to give it up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the law required contracts for employment that would mean that you could only get fired for either directly breaking code of conduct or failure to do your job correctly, and that you would have due process before being fired. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If they fire you for a dumb reason then you get damages, if the employee quits before term is they pay penalties. Basically the way the public sector works. Better pay/benefits (might be slightly lower pay but you get real benefits and pensions) Most have 20-25 year retirement with 60+% of your monthly way pension then you get Social Security check later in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ending at will employment is what must happen for labor standards to go up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit- Retirement savings plan is not a pension, a pension is no cost to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：小费文化是有毒的，需要被废除]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们生活在一个社会中，如果你不给你的服务员或送货司机小费。
你就会立即被打上有权、自私或无礼的烙印。有的服务员
威胁要在食物中吐痰或做手脚，故意提供糟糕的服务。
或者因为不给小费而拒绝交付订单......然而，我们作为...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pelbp2/cmv_tipping_culture_is_toxic_and_needs_to_be_done/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pelbp2/cmv_tipping_culture_is_toxic_and_needs_to_be_done/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 17:37:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We live in a society where if you do not tip your server or delivery driver, you’re immediately branded as entitled, selfish, or rude. There are servers who threaten to spit in or tamper with food, intentionally provide terrible service, or refuse to deliver an order due to non-tipping…yet we as a society have decided that we are okay with this and fall into the pressure of tipping culture to avoid these issues. This is the only industry where workers essentially strong-arm the consumer to pay them extra money and threaten or ridicule them otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How is this okay? The truth of the matter is, if you can afford the cost of the meal and any delivery fees associated with it, you literally CAN afford to eat out per almost every restaurant in America’s policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美国总统应该有年龄限制。75岁。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我感到恶心的是，在过去的几次选举中，我们所有的选择都是超级老的。
而且不能代表我们的县。我认为我们需要一些年轻的血液，大多数
人在65-70岁退休。为什么要让他们来管理这个国家，因为我们已经百分之百的
之前的总统已经开始了他们的认知能力下降......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pe6x4m/cmv_there_should_be_an_age_limit_for_us_president/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pe6x4m/cmv_there_should_be_an_age_limit_for_us_president/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 15:37:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m sick that all our choices the last few elections have all been super old, and not representative of our county.  I think we need some young blood, most people retire at 65-70.  Why should they be running the country, when we’ve 100% had presidents before that had started their cognitive decline while still holding the nuclear football?  I would almost rather at 28 year old in charge then someone that’s 80.  I also don’t think that Supreme Court judges should be appointed for life till either, but that’s another argument.  I’m not being ageist, and I think there’s a million other jobs older people can do, just not this.  I also would still think it would be good if their cabinet didn’t have a age range.  It’s good to hear from people with experience.  For the record, I’m 39, for disclosure.  Credit to &lt;a href=&quot;/u/Tony_Pizza_Guy&quot;&gt;u/Tony_Pizza_Guy&lt;/a&gt; for the idea.  Change my mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 以 "购买 "来推销非永久性购买应该是非法的，而应该使用 "租赁 "等术语。]]></title><description><![CDATA[编辑：由于我可能没有说清楚我的意思，所以我不是针对这些词
词，而是它们所表达的意思。我试着用一个
具体的例子。

一个常用的说法是 "在PLATFORM上获得GAME"。

"在GOG Galaxy上获得《运输狂热2》"意味着我可以得到这个游戏和。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/peh7oq/cmv_it_should_be_illegal_to_market_nonpermanent/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/peh7oq/cmv_it_should_be_illegal_to_market_nonpermanent/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 14:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt; Since I probably wasn&amp;#39;t clear what I mean, I don&amp;#39;t target the words specifically, but the meaning they convey. I&amp;#39;ll try to explain by using a concrete example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A commonly used way of saying stuff is &amp;quot;Get GAME on PLATFORM&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Get Transport Fever 2 on GOG Galaxy&amp;quot; means I can get the game and play it forever, because GOG doesn&amp;#39;t apply DRM, so after the game is on your computer they have no control on what you do with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Get Transport Fever 2 on Steam&amp;quot; means I can get a license to play the game and play it as long as my Steam account is valid, I&amp;#39;m not VAC banned, etc etc etc.
Getting the game on GOG Galaxy means getting it forever, getting the game on Steam has the possibility that at one point I won&amp;#39;t be able to play it anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because of that, Steam saying &amp;quot;Get Transport Fever 2 on Steam&amp;quot; should be illegal (perhaps false advertising), because it could imply permanence (like in the case of GOG), even though the EULA doesn&amp;#39;t give that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is going more and more towards renting stuff rather than owning it, and it is doing so in a misleading way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such, I think that laws should be put in place such that &amp;quot;buying&amp;quot; something can only be used if, after the purchase, that &amp;quot;something&amp;quot;, with all the advertised features, can be used indefinitely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s take the example of the PlayStation 4. After buying the PS4, you can use the hardware forever. You can also play games you have on CD forever. However, you cannot play multiplayer games forever (if PSN goes away so goes multiplayer), and if your PlayStation account is banned (for example if you make a chargeback), you also lose all digital games you bought from the PlayStation Store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such, if Sony wants to advertise the PS4 as something you can buy, it should be illegal to make any reference to the ability to play games multiplayer, play digital games, or download stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similarly, it should be illegal for Sony to say that games obtained through the PlayStation Store can be &amp;quot;bought&amp;quot; or that they &amp;quot;sell&amp;quot; those games. Instead, Sony should only be allowed to say that you can rent those games through the PS Store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems unfair for Sony to be able to permanently erase all your games you bought online if you chargeback a fraudulent payment. Since the chance of preventing that is low, and since that&amp;#39;s not the only issue (once Sony shuts down the PlayStation Store for an old console, all online games are gone too), the distinction between something you buy and keep and something you rent and &lt;strong&gt;will&lt;/strong&gt; disappear at one point should be clearly advertised to consumers so they are at least informed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not just a Sony/PlayStation rant, but the easiest example and first that came to mind. Internet of Things (smart home) stuff is famously becoming paperweight if the company decides to no longer support the product, for example. As such, it seems unfair to advertise features that may be gone anytime as features of the product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I understand that products don&amp;#39;t last forever. For example, the PlayStation 4 or a smart lightbulb might break. However, in these situations, the lifetime of a product is longer than the guaranteed lifetime of stuff that should be labeled as &amp;quot;rented&amp;quot;. If my PS4 breaks, &lt;em&gt;c&amp;#39;est la vie&lt;/em&gt;, I can&amp;#39;t play games anymore, that&amp;#39;s to be expected. But if I &lt;strong&gt;buy&lt;/strong&gt; a game from PlayStation Store, I expect to be able to play it until my PS4 breaks, not until tomorrow (which is when Sony might arbitrarily decide to ban my PSN account and invalidate all my purchases).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And no, I don&amp;#39;t agree that pointing it out in the EULA is even remotely enough. &lt;em&gt;(In an unrelated note, I don&amp;#39;t think EULAs should be enforceable or legally binding if a company can&amp;#39;t prove the user properly read &lt;strong&gt;and understood&lt;/strong&gt; it. This particular opinion is mostly unrelated to the rest of this post, however, and even if you don&amp;#39;t agree with this last opinion, my point in the rest of this post still stands.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：散布疫苗虚假信息的政客应承担法律责任。]]></title><description><![CDATA[政治家被选来领导我们，特别是在重大事件中，如目前的大流行病。
目前的大流行病。无视专家的科学数据，告诉公民不要
要相信疫苗，这简直是在杀人。这些人有影响力
在社会上和他们支持的立法中。我不是在说...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pe3f3c/cmv_politicians_spreading_vaccine_disinformation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pe3f3c/cmv_politicians_spreading_vaccine_disinformation/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:37:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Politicians are elected to lead us especially during major events like the current pandemic. Ignoring scientific data from experts and telling citizens not to trust vaccines is literally killing people. These people have influence socially and in the legislation they support. I’m not talking about your crazy uncle on Facebook. He’s not elected or in a position of leadership. I think politicians that give false medical advice that is refutable by science should face legal consequences. Knowingly giving someone an STD is illegal. Spreading false information from a place of leadership and enacting policies that aren’t supported by science needs to have consequences or they will keep doing it. Next time we might be dealing with a virus with much higher deaths rates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在采访塔利班成员时，派一个女记者去采访是没有意义的。大家都已经知道塔利班不尊重妇女（这很可怕），但在一次重要的采访中用一个妇女来对抗他们，只是为了哗众取宠而自我破坏。]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着所有重要的新闻从阿富汗传出，很多人都在急切地想知道在阿富汗的疏散状况等信息。
很多人急切地想知道在喀布尔进行的疏散等活动的情况。
喀布尔的情况。

英国广播公司（BBC）、美国广播公司（ABC）、半岛电视台（Al-Jazeera）和其他电视台都有女主播在当地采访。
他们正试图采访塔利班领导人，以获取关键信息。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdz4ll/cmv_when_interviewing_members_of_the_taliban_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdz4ll/cmv_when_interviewing_members_of_the_taliban_it/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 19:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;With all the important news coming out of Afghanistan, lots of people are desperate for information on the status of the evacuation, etc, going on in Kabul. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BBC, ABC, Al-Jazeera, and others, all have female lead reporters on the ground who are trying to interview Taliban leaders for critical information, and oftentimes the interview (with the goal of &lt;em&gt;getting critical information&lt;/em&gt;) ends up accomplishing nothing at all because the Taliban don&amp;#39;t respect them. Here is an example I saw this morning on Al Jazeera:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/RiYAmfb.png&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;I asked for information about the situation at the airport, and they refused to talk to me because I was a women and not dressed appropriately&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course they didn&amp;#39;t want to talk to you on camera. What did you expect? &lt;strong&gt;The Taliban don&amp;#39;t respect women.&lt;/strong&gt; We all know that. We all know that is wrong and bigoted. We have known that for decades, so why self sabotage an important information gathering activity by purposefully antagonizing the people you are trying to interview?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would be like sending a blind reporter to give an eye witness report for a newspaper. Or sending a deaf person to review a new music album. Or sending an Amish person who doesn&amp;#39;t use electricity to an press conference about new computer chip designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It just isn&amp;#39;t the right person to send for this one particular activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美国人真的需要坐上坐便器的火车了]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年，当卫生纸出现短缺时，我订购了坐便器，而不是为了争夺纸张。
争夺纸张。结果，我用的卫生纸少了，我的屁眼也干净多了。
我的屁眼也更干净了，而且我触摸屁眼的次数比使用卫生纸时少得多。
纸。

净身盆是一种优越的、可负担得起的和更好的选择...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdyqxj/cmv_americans_really_need_to_get_on_the_bidet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdyqxj/cmv_americans_really_need_to_get_on_the_bidet/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 18:46:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year when there was a run on toilet paper I ordered bidets instead of fighting over paper. As a result, I use less toilet paper, my butthole is much cleaner and I have to touch my butthole far less than when I was using toilet paper. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bidets are superior, affordable and the far better option for a country that can afford them. It&amp;#39;s fairly barbaric that we were cleaning our buttholes with our hands and a thin piece of paper. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Might also make teenage boys smell less like they were fisting their own assholes as well. Probably won&amp;#39;t solve the semen smell though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Just figured I&amp;#39;d add this edit. You&amp;#39;ll probably have an easier time convincing me of logistical issues or environment issues than whether or not it&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;cleaner&amp;#39;. Although you&amp;#39;re welcome to try to convince me it&amp;#39;s not clean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：认为宗教人士有妄想症是没有错的]]></title><description><![CDATA[我个人不相信任何宗教，我是由非常严重的
的基督教徒。我听到的一些论点是："你无法证明上帝
是不真实的。" 好吧，我也不能证明牙仙不是真的，但这并不意味着我
如果你相信它是真实的，我就不能认为你有妄想症。这就像宗教...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdx5hb/cmv_it_is_not_wrong_to_think_religious_people_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdx5hb/cmv_it_is_not_wrong_to_think_religious_people_are/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 17:32:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Personally I do not believe in any religion I was raised by very heavy christians however. Some of the arguments I heard was &amp;quot; you can&amp;#39;t prove god isn&amp;#39;t real.&amp;quot; Well I can&amp;#39;t prove the tooth fairy isn&amp;#39;t real either doesn&amp;#39;t mean I can&amp;#39;t think you&amp;#39;re delusional if you believe it is. It&amp;#39;s like religious people have to completely shut down their brains to continue believing at this point which is nearly identical to a cult. Religion meets the definition of a cult by every definition I can find. Just because the majority people are in some cult doesn&amp;#39;t mean it&amp;#39;s not a cult. &amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s funny how the right religion is always the one you grew up with. &amp;quot; That is such a true statement I really don&amp;#39;t see how anyone can believe knowing all that without being mentally delusional. Truthfully religion seems like a very primitive practice that makes very little sense in modern society and should be classified as a delusion or a mental disorder in the DSM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 如果一个男人发现他不是父亲，就不应该指望他留下来。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在看到这么多不同的Reddit帖子，其中有以下的故事和回应的评论。
的故事和回应的评论，我不确定我是否是那个被这种问题困扰的人。
关于这种问题的屁股。

男子养育孩子

发现女人出轨，谎称自己是父亲

男子问该怎么做

Reddit Hivemind说...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdv8vz/cmv_if_a_man_discovers_he_is_not_the_father_he/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdv8vz/cmv_if_a_man_discovers_he_is_not_the_father_he/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 15:34:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After seeing so many different Reddit Post about stories with the below as the story and the comments in response, I am not sure if I am the one who is being the butt about this kind of issue.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Man raises child&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Discovers woman cheated, lied about paternity&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Man asks what to do&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Reddit Hivemind says he should remain in the child&amp;#39;s life.&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every time, no concerns about what the men must now feel about the child, often the fruit of the infidelity he only recently discovered, but that if he stops caring for said child, he is no longer a &amp;quot;Real Man. It is never said in those words, but that&amp;#39;s the feeling from it, some even saying things like a man should castrate himself if he can&amp;#39;t be a father to a child that isn&amp;#39;t his or if he leaves partway through.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shouldn&amp;#39;t a guy be able to leave? He did nothing wrong, the child isn&amp;#39;t his concern, or at least shouldn&amp;#39;t be if he no longer wishes to do so. That child has a chance to be raises by their real bio-dad or by someone else. But it has to be him, the betrayed, who MUST stay, or at least continue to be in the child&amp;#39;s life.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure, the child themselves didn&amp;#39;t do anything wrong, but that child is still a picture of the hurt, the pain, the cheating, the lies. But, he should swallow all of that because the child might grow up without him there.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In any other kind of relationship, this isn&amp;#39;t expected. If you are married to someone for ten years, then get ill and you find out that they cheated, maybe even that this illness is the reason of them cheating, you can and should still be able to leave that marriage, because why should you be tied to an agreement they didn&amp;#39;t keep? If you worked in a business that was supposed to be yours, but you find out that it wasn&amp;#39;t that it legally belongs to someone else, why on Earth should you be forced to stay, otherwise, you really didn&amp;#39;t care for the business?   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why should the time that passed matter? Why shouldn&amp;#39;t your next move be fore you and you alone? Why is it ok to tell a man that if he doesn&amp;#39;t care for the child that isn&amp;#39;t his, that he never really loved the child or that there is something wrong with him?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am I seeing this issue wrong somehow? Change my Views on this!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：自动禁止参与有争议的子版块的人，弊大于利]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚被一个我已经几年没有参与的子版块禁言了
(/r/pokemongo)，因为我在另一个我不积极参与的子红上发表了一条评论。
积极参与的另一个子版块（/r/conspiracy）发表了一条评论。我偶然路过/r/conspiracy，嘲笑了
的阴谋论。瞬间就被禁止了，因为 "参与...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdr4hy/cmv_automated_banning_of_people_who_participate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdr4hy/cmv_automated_banning_of_people_who_participate/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 12:33:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just got banned from a subreddit I hadn&amp;#39;t participated in for several years (&lt;a href=&quot;/r/pokemongo&quot;&gt;/r/pokemongo&lt;/a&gt;) because I made a single comment in another subreddit I don&amp;#39;t actively participate in (&lt;a href=&quot;/r/conspiracy&quot;&gt;/r/conspiracy&lt;/a&gt;). I happened by &lt;a href=&quot;/r/conspiracy&quot;&gt;/r/conspiracy&lt;/a&gt; and mocked a covid conspiracy theory. Instantly banned for &amp;quot;participating in subreddits that spread covid misinformation&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel like if I was the kind of person they actually wanted to ban... this would only cause me to double down on my beliefs of censorship and fascism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What good is accomplished? Don&amp;#39;t these sort of actions only increase their confidence and passion, causing them to spend more time trying to spread their beliefs? Do they just care about their own subreddit and nothing else?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Thanks for the replies, folks. Deltas awarded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;#39;t realize &amp;quot;Do they just care about their own subreddit and nothing else?&amp;quot; was such a stupid question. But I agree now... it is... modding their own sub is all a mod typically cares about when modding their own sub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still think this is a bad practice that will only create more of the people it tries to remove, but they don&amp;#39;t really care if that happens as long as those people are outside their sub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: "自己做研究 "与社会成功的核心原因是对立的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们拥有今天的社会的主要原因可以归结为
归功于人类可以将工作分门别类的事实。

在某种程度上（古希腊？ 我不知道），我们意识到不是每个人都需要知道所有的事情。
都需要知道每一件事。我们可以将工作专门化，在一个
某个领域的工作...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdjhk3/cmv_do_your_own_research_is_antithetical_to_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdjhk3/cmv_do_your_own_research_is_antithetical_to_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 06:39:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main reason that we have the society we have today can mainly be attributed to the fact that humans can compartmentalize work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At some point (Ancient Greece? Idk), we realized that not every single person needs to know every single thing. We can &lt;em&gt;specialize&lt;/em&gt; and have jobs in a particular space of knowledge, if we don&amp;#39;t &amp;#39;do our own research&amp;#39; and trust that the society will mitigate our other risks. This specialization of skills/knowledge gives rise to economy, social class, professional subcultures, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a short, limited example, the farmer doesn&amp;#39;t need to know how to or actually build or repair their own house. The builder doesn&amp;#39;t need to know how to or actually farm crops. They will exchange their services to each other to mitigate each other&amp;#39;s risk, allowing each of them to become better at their specialization. When you scale this example, you see how you now need an economy to be able to efficiently exchange work between mediums. It gives rise to social class as the ones with the most utility (doctor&amp;#39;s, politicians, judges, etc.) can curry the most favour in exchange for their work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note: We see this property being leveraged across multiple facets of nature (biological sex, multicellular organisms). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, society progressed much faster when we were able to centralize meaningfully differentiated skills and knowledge. Of course this does not mean that this system is immune to the typical challenges of centralization (lack of transparency, trust, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when I hear &amp;#39;do your own research&amp;#39;, my brain translates it to &amp;#39;There is a significant enough risk that this centralized knowledge/skill base is compromised, that I need to mitigate the primary risk myself&amp;#39;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is a fair thing to say, and act on for a lot of contexts (ie. Journalism/media on political events), but the implication above for such key systems such as healthcare or engineering, is the equivalent of basically trying to mitigate the risk of a total societal collapse/revolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is antithetical to, imo, one of the core reasons for society&amp;#39;s success and state today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果吸烟者可以拒绝酗酒者的肺部移植，并被拒绝肝脏移植，那么拒绝接种疫苗的人（没有正当的医疗理由）应该是最后一个获得医疗床的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[医院是如此之满，以至于人们进来后因其他原因而被拒绝治疗。
医疗的东西。一名退伍军人因阑尾炎而死亡，因为病床上挤满了未接种Covid的病人。
未接种疫苗的科维德病人太多。够了！够了 我失去了对
我对那些冒着变异科维德的风险而接种疫苗的人失去了同情。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdon9h/cmv_if_smokers_can_be_refuse_lung_transplants_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdon9h/cmv_if_smokers_can_be_refuse_lung_transplants_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 05:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hospitals are so full that people are coming in and being denied care for other medical stuff. A veteran died because of an appendicitis because the beds were so full of unvaccinated Covid patients. Enough is enough! I lost sympathy for people who are risking a mutant covid that makes vaccinated people at risk of losing immunity. Shame on adults not getting vaccinated and getting sick children who can’t get vaccinated yet! Their choices hurt the rest of us, if they want freedom, they need to take responsibility! Last in line for a bed for unvaccinated people!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：网上辩论更好，因为你不能打断别人的书面文章]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个人摆出一张桌子和一个牌子，上面写着 "支持生命，改变我的观点"。随着
随着越来越多的人加入对话，人群中的成员大喊 "性别歧视的猪"，"我的身体我的权利"，并且一般来说，他们的谩骂更加激烈。
身体是我的权利"，一般来说，他们的谩骂会更加激进。这场对话
辩论的目的是为了真正改变一个人的想法，但它已经...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pddibd/cmv_debates_are_better_online_because_you_cant/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pddibd/cmv_debates_are_better_online_because_you_cant/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 02:00:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A person puts up a table and a sign that says “Pro Life, change my view”. As more people join the conversation, members of the crowd yell “sexist pig”, “my body my rights”, and generally get more aggressive with their heckling. The point of the debate was to truly change a persons mind, but it has now devolved into near physical altercation because two sides can’t agree to let the other side finish their sentences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This scene of debates goes back as old as ancient Greece all the way to modern democratic parliaments. Humans are simply too emotional to put them aside for the sake of truth seeking. Angers rise when words can no longer be found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Edit]: Thanks guys. What I like about this thread is that it both proved and disproved my argument. I learned a lot via online opinions but I also learned that online makes debates very disjointed and lose interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：大学招生的平权行动应该基于社会经济地位，而不是种族。]]></title><description><![CDATA[标题。我以自己为例来开始。我是伦比族印第安人
(Card-carrying)，因此，许多机构对我来说，大学是免费的。

问题是，我并不住在北卡罗来纳州的罗伯逊县，而我的大部分家人都住在那里。
卡罗来纳州的罗伯逊县，我的大部分家人都住在那里，而那里的伦比人往往比白人更穷
伦比人往往比白人更穷......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pddz0n/cmv_affirmative_action_for_college_admissions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pddz0n/cmv_affirmative_action_for_college_admissions/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 18:45:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title. I&amp;#39;ll use myself as an example to start. I&amp;#39;m Lumbee Indian (card-carrying), and thus college is free for me from many instutions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The issue arises from the fact that I don&amp;#39;t live in Robeson County, North Carolina, where much of my family does, and where the Lumbee tend to be poorer than white people, on average. I live in Minnesota, am moderately well-off, and have never faced racial discrimination, (mostly because my dad is white and I got his genes.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I still get free college, despite my grades being average at best. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why I believe that college admissions shouldn&amp;#39;t look at you&amp;#39;re race, but at the wealth of your family. Race doesn&amp;#39;t generally cause people to get poor grades and test scores, but the wealth of their parents can. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A white kid with a single mother who works as a janitor, but has a 3.8 GOA and a 30 on the ACT would be more qualified for university than Malia Obama, if she had the same numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Race can be a factor, but it isn&amp;#39;t always a factor, and colleges should recognize that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果明确表示他们从来不想要孩子，就不应该强迫男人抚养他们的孩子]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个女人可以决定不做母亲，并在受孕后承担所有的责任。
在受孕后的所有责任。她们可以选择（在我居住的地方）进行
堕胎或将他们的孩子送去收养。她们可以决定自己是否
想在受孕后成为父母。男人则没有选择，在...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdcacs/cmv_men_should_not_be_forced_to_support_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pdcacs/cmv_men_should_not_be_forced_to_support_their/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 17:30:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman can decide not to be a mother and have all the responsibilities that come with it after conception. They can choose (where i live) to have an abortion or put their kid up for adoption. They can decide whether or not they want to be a parent after conception. A man has no choice, after conception whether or not he wants to he could be made a father. My view is that if the man makes it clear to the woman that he does not want this baby (with ample time for the woman to consider her options) then he should not be forced to support the child. I think morally this should be a very black and white issue, if women can choose to be or not to be a parent after conception so should men. In the sense that they should not be compelled to support or acknowledge the babies existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果蚊子🦟灭绝，世界将变得更好--它们没有任何有益的用途]]></title><description><![CDATA[夏天快结束了，幸好是蚊子季节的结束。每年
年过去了，我不得不在自己身上涂抹除虫剂，以避免大量的叮咬，并且
天知道是什么疾病。

蚊子存在于地球上，只是为了成为寄生虫和传播...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pd8kuo/cmv_the_world_would_be_better_off_if_mosquitoes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pd8kuo/cmv_the_world_would_be_better_off_if_mosquitoes/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 16:39:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s towards the end of summer and thankfully the end of mosquito season. Every year goes by and I have to slather myself in deet, to avoid tons of bites, and god knows what disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mosquitoes exist on planet earth, simply to be parasites and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/topics/outdoor/mosquito-borne/default.html&quot;&gt;spread disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And we’re talking things like West Nile Virus, Zika Virus, Malaria. Diseases that have life altering consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried reading the arguments of why they should exist: they feed bats and birds, they keep humans out of sensitive natural environments like the rainforests. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But humans are going into the rainforests anyway and chopping them down, so not much of a deterrent if you ask me. And surely there’s enough OTHER kinds of bugs that could feed bats and birds. I’d like for them to eat more spiders please.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway I’m convinced the world would be better off if mosquitos would just go extinct. Change my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV："朋友圈 "是一些地狱般的噩梦的概念绝对是荒谬的，坦率地说，为它感到不安是不成熟的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我认为被拒绝和其他人一样糟糕，但这是你决定向你的朋友，特别是向你的朋友求爱时所承担的风险。
当你决定对你的朋友，特别是你最好的朋友进行预付时，你要承担风险。
最好的朋友。你知道当你这样做时，有什么在等着你。你应该知道
你是否能处理好与一个人做朋友的问题......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pd58lk/cmv_the_concept_of_the_friendzone_being_some/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pd58lk/cmv_the_concept_of_the_friendzone_being_some/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 09:41:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think getting rejected sucks just as much as the next person, but it’s the risk you take when you decide to make an advance on your friend, especially your best friend. You know what lies in wait for you when you do it. You should know whether or not you can handle being friends with someone who rejected you, or whether or not you can handle separating from them entirely if need be. If you’re unsure, err on the side of caution. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t have issue with people who understand the risks and decide to move forward anyway, I have issue with the people who do it, get rejected, and ostentatiously whine about it afterward because they’ve been put in the accursed “friendzone.” If it bothers you so much, why not be straightforward and tell them you need to break away from their friendship for some time (maybe even forever) instead of hiding behind an awkward mask while continuing to stick by their side with feelings you haven’t dealt with? Or better yet, do some self-reflection, grow up, and understand that your love for them is a testament to your enjoyment of their company, therefore you should be content with having at least their friendship. Don’t ruin a good platonic relationship by thinking it’s the end of the world to be put in the friendzone. The friendzone is a beautiful place, and if you give it a chance you’ll come to understand that it’s worth the temporary pain you get from rejection. Being friends is more important than (the idea of) being lovers, at least if you truly care about that person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：蓝莓是最好的浆果。]]></title><description><![CDATA[多样性

馅饼、果酱、冰沙、松饼等等，我想不出有哪种浆果的用途比不起眼的蓝莓更多。
我想不出有哪种浆果的用途比卑微的蓝莓更多。草莓的优势在于
但你上次看到草莓松饼是什么时候？I
我想没有。我想小红莓汁是相当不错的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcz5to/cmv_blueberries_are_the_best_berry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcz5to/cmv_blueberries_are_the_best_berry/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 04:31:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Versatility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pies, jams, smoothies, muffins and more, I can&amp;#39;t think of a single berry with more uses than the humble blueberry. Strawberries do have the advantage of making a sick ice cream but when&amp;#39;s the last time you saw a strawberry muffin? I thought not. I suppose cranberry juice is pretty nice but I think blueberry smoothies offset that too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ease of use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some berries like strawberries require removing a green thing before they&amp;#39;re eaten and pretty much need to be cut up. Blueberries just need a quick rinse before they can be chomped down upon. Wanna eat just one blueberry? Have a quick, tiny snack! Wanna ingest a giant spoonful of blue and round goodness? Enjoy that as well! Blueberries work great with both a fork and a spoon too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best bush&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raspberry bushes are covered in spikes and are very scary in general. 0/5, not family friendly at all, my kids were very scared. Blueberry bushes, on the other hand, are inviting, gentle creatures. They are a bit more of a pain to take care of (I accidentally mowed a part of a baby one, oops), but I think the benefits make it well worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not gonna sit here and pretend that blueberries are the cheapest berry, they aren&amp;#39;t. But is that really what we should be looking at when it comes to price? A GT 1030 is cheap, but does that make it the best graphics card? Of course not. What really matters is price to performance, and on that front I don&amp;#39;t think you can fault the blueberry even slightly. Sure, it might cost a bit more per calorie but given all the aforementioned uses for the blueberry I think it&amp;#39;s well worth the price of admission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I think has been thoroughly demonstrated, the blueberry is the berry to reign superior over all other berries. I look forward to seeing what others have to say on the matter...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：企业应该使用滚动期来计算奖金/目标/配额，而不是任意的时期，因为这造成了员工对数字的不正当刺激。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，例如，如果你是一个汽车经销商的员工，你可能有一个目标
一个月卖出30辆车，如果你卖得更多，你会得到奖金，比如说每卖出30辆车就有500美元的奖金。
每辆车超过30辆，你会得到500美元的奖金。我相信这种事情鼓励员工和
损害业务的方式行事，并且......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcqisj/cmv_businesses_should_use_rolling_periods_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcqisj/cmv_businesses_should_use_rolling_periods_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:44:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So for example, if you are an employee of a car dealership, you may have a goal to sell, say, 30 cars a month and if you sell more, you get a bonus of, say $500 per car above 30. I believe this kind of things encourages employees and customers to act in ways that are damaging to the business and that these  negative behaviors could be reduced if bonuses/quotas were instead calculated on a trailing rolling basis. So for example, in the above example you would get a daily bonus calculated by the formula: (Average cars sold per day for past 30 days - target cars sold per day)*$500. Yes, this is slightly more complicated, but in the days of automated tracking the added complexity is negligible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By going to this system, it would stop the employee from doing things like offering price discounts, etc. in order to game the numbers in an arbitrary accounting period provided the commission they lost from being negotiable on price was less than their volume bonus. It might also cause an employee to try to shift sales in to a later month if they were below the bonus quota (so they would have a better chance of making bonus next month) and risk losing the deal as a result of the delay. Furthermore, if customers knew they no longer could get pricing power by coming in on the last day of the month/year, they would stop trying and stop expecting a discount from doing so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have personally seen time and again, companies and individuals making horrible business decisions because they want to close deals or achieve certain goals within an arbitrary accounting period. Employees sloppily finishing a project by an arbitrary deadline, or cutting scope out of a job so they can book/complete it by a certain date. I once literally saw a team in my company find a BS reason to cut $30M of scope out of a job so they could get the contract signed by the end of the bonus period. Every time I see this, I think to myself that this most of this could be fixed by just having incentive structures that was based on trailing averages and not based arbitrary hard deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I acknowledge that the reason for using arbitrary accounting periods is also because reporting periods for public companies are also based on arbitrary periods, I feel that this is circular reasoning. If companies moved away from arbitrary accounting periods to using better thought out incentive periods, so might their investors take a longer view at financial results. I would also say that only a tiny fraction of companies are publicly traded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 用 "decimate "这个词作为 "destroy "的同义词是可以的]]></title><description><![CDATA[当我们把12月称为第12个月时，没有人不高兴，尽管12月的字面意思是 "第十个月"。
字面意思是 "第十个月"。那么，为什么其他人会对
"decimate "被用来描述已经被消灭到很厉害的东西
程度？

语言随着时间而变化。例如，"鹿 "这个词曾经...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcvcn5/cmv_its_ok_to_use_the_word_decimate_as_a_synonym/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcvcn5/cmv_its_ok_to_use_the_word_decimate_as_a_synonym/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:44:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one gets upset when we call December the 12th month even tho December literally means &amp;quot;tenth month&amp;quot;. So why do others get so pissed off over &amp;quot;decimate&amp;quot; being used to describe something that has been vanquished to a great degree?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Language changes over time. The word &amp;quot;deer&amp;quot; for instance once referred to any kind of animal. Then it narrowed to just one.  The word &amp;quot;silly&amp;quot; once had the definition of &amp;quot;innocent&amp;quot;. The word &amp;quot;loft&amp;quot; once referred to the sky (and &amp;quot;heavens&amp;quot; in the plural also could be substituted for such).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stop being smug bastards and accept that &amp;quot;decimate&amp;quot; is perfectly fine when someone says &amp;quot;Did you see the game last night? The Raiders got decimated!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：年轻人最好能发生轻微的（但足够痛苦的）伤害，这样他们就能更好地掌握死亡率。]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近看到很多年轻司机像疯子一样在交通中开车的视频。
疯了一样在交通中行驶，其中很多都以火爆的、有时是致命的车祸而告终。作为一个
15岁时由于自己的愚蠢而被卡车撞倒，这让我更加意识到
事实上，只要发生一次事故就能彻底...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcl3rj/cmv_its_desirable_for_youth_to_incur_minor_but/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcl3rj/cmv_its_desirable_for_youth_to_incur_minor_but/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:44:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Been seeing a lot of videos lately of younger drivers driving like lunatics thru traffic, a lot of them ending in fiery, sometimes deadly crashes.  As someone who was hit by a truck at 15 due to my own stupidity, it made me much more aware of the fact that it only takes one accident to thoroughly fuck your world up.  I feel like if more kids experienced even a fraction of the pain and suffering I did (or anyone who has been in a serious accident) they would have an entirely different approach when it came to behavior that had the potential for serious injury/death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我看到很多人在reddit上谈论twitter如何糟糕，但我也看到twitter的截图经常被张贴出来，并得到大量的支持。我开始认为，人们不喜欢的其实不是twitter，而是有不同观点的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[每当讨论到twitter的时候，人们似乎都非常讨厌那个
网站。然而，现在首页上有几条推文，更不用说
更不用说专门关于发布twitter截图的subreddits了。我不
我不经常使用twitter，所以我很困惑，人们在...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcrynf/cmv_i_see_lots_of_people_on_reddit_talk_about_how/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcrynf/cmv_i_see_lots_of_people_on_reddit_talk_about_how/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 21:31:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whenever discussions about twitter comes up, people seem to absolutely hate that site. And yet, there are several tweets on the front page right now, not to mention the subreddits specifically about posting twitter screenshots. I don&amp;#39;t use twitter frequently, so I&amp;#39;m confused about what people on reddit mean when they say twitter is awful. Sure, it&amp;#39;s possible that there&amp;#39;s two different groups of people who like or dislike twitter, but then you&amp;#39;d think only one of either criticisms of twitter or twitter screenshots would be highly upvoted, not both.  Is it twitter occasionally having a good content thing, and being bad the rest of the times?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：把鸡蛋放在碗边而不是放在台面上，是完全可以的，甚至是更好的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在YouTube上看了很多烹饪视频，似乎厨师们总是在台面上打鸡蛋。
似乎厨师们总是在台面上打鸡蛋，而且有些人会直接说这是正确的方法。
这是正确的方法。也许他们的做法与我的做法不同，但
但我每次尝试都会得到一个更糟糕的结果。

柜台裂缝。我得到一个...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcpxvu/cmv_its_perfectly_fine_better_even_to_crack_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcpxvu/cmv_its_perfectly_fine_better_even_to_crack_an/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 19:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I watch a lot of cooking videos on YouTube, and it seems that the chefs always crack their eggs on the countertop, and some will come right out and say that it&amp;#39;s the right way. Maybe they&amp;#39;re doing it differently from how I do it, but every time I try I get a worse result. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Counter crack: I get a flattening of the round surface, maybe it goes concave instead of convex, with some spider-web cracks emanating from the point of impact. I still have to pierce the egg with my thumb, usually making contact with the white. Often the membrane underneath the shell is still intact. When I do get the shell apart, it is often uneven, which if I&amp;#39;m trying to separate the white and yolk using the &amp;quot;back-and-forth&amp;quot; method, is less useful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bowl crack: the edge of the bowl cuts into the egg, leaving a gash at the point of impact. If the break is insufficient, I can go back for another shot. At that point I can turn the egg so the break is at the top, letting the white move down so that I touch little or no white when I complete the crack. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what am I not seeing that makes cracking them on the counter better?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：孩子们长大后对他们的父母完全没有义务。]]></title><description><![CDATA[很多父母[尤其是在亚洲文化中（我是亚洲人）]，父母期望他们的子女在他们年老时能照顾他们，并抛出借口。
他们的子女在他们年老的时候要照顾他们，并抛出各种借口
诸如 "我们为你遮风挡雨，让你吃饱穿暖，所以你需要在我们年老时做同样的事。
我们老了也要这样做。"

是的，我绝对不相信，....]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pclw4n/cmv_children_have_absolutely_no_obligation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pclw4n/cmv_children_have_absolutely_no_obligation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 15:39:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of parents [especially in Asian culture (I am Asian)] where parents expect their children to take care of them when they are old, and throw around excuses such as “We sheltered you, fed you, clothed you, so you need to do the same when we are older.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yea I absolutely do not believe in that. I’m referring to all kinds of parents. Children aren’t obligated to take care of them in old age. 
Even if you  did a good job as a parent and treat your children well, your children aren’t obligated to take care of you. Parents decide to bring children into this world, they have no say in this, so if they choose to not take care of you when you are older, then you can’t blame them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m mostly trying to talk about toxic and abusive parents where they treat their children like shit and expect to be treated well in return. Fuck that. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why I even posted this CMV is because there are actually some people in the world who believe that “&lt;em&gt;you need to take care of parents regardless of how they treated you / brought you up&lt;/em&gt;” and to me that is a BS fallacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV："呼吁 "Reddit删除公然的错误信息，这只是在为N8的账户添砖加瓦而已。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit作为一个整体，倾向于允许有争议的甚至是完全不正确的
信息在这个网站上。这一点在以下子版块中得到了一次又一次的证明
如Sino，它认为/相信天安门大屠杀从未发生。
这可以说是很危险的，因为这又给了他们更多的弹药。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcjmrq/cmv_calling_upon_reddit_to_delete_blatant/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcjmrq/cmv_calling_upon_reddit_to_delete_blatant/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 15:39:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit as a whole tends to allow controversial or even downright incorrect information on this site. This is demonstrated time and time again within subreddits such as sino, which argues/believes tianmen massacre never happened. This is arguably dangerous as well as it gives them more ammo again the USA being against China and creating lies to hurt them. While I completely disagree with antivaxxers and think vaccines are both safe and important, just like any social media there will be people who disagree with you. The information they post is no different to Facebook or Instagram or even tiktok. Is Reddit allowing them to broadcast it more? Of course, but Reddit is not exactly breeding this misinformation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The misinformation is killing people but that is not the fault of Reddit. It is the fault of those who choose to believe it despite the overwhelming scientific evidence that proves what they fear most; the vaccine is effective and safe. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Reddit does step in and remove these subreddits they are only beginning the process of converting Reddit into an echo chamber/circle jerk social media. It is not nor should it be Reddit’s responsibility to protect antivaxxers from their own information. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand this is a controversial take but I struggle with understanding why some subreddits with blatant and somewhat harmful misinformation are allowed to stay and other subreddits cannot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：安乐死的辅助自杀应该是合法的（我知道我不会拼写）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果一个人患有严重的精神或身体疾病，并且不能过上幸福的生活
如果一个人患有严重的精神或身体疾病，不能过上幸福的生活，他们应该选择和平的辅助自杀，他们自己的条件。
让这些人活着是很自私的，唯一反对的人是那些从未见过这些人的人。
反对的人是那些从来没有见过这些人的人，或者是......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcba0l/cmv_assisted_suicide_by_euthanasia_should_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcba0l/cmv_assisted_suicide_by_euthanasia_should_be/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 11:32:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;if a person is suffering from a serious mental or physical illness and cant live a happy life they should have the choice of peaceful assisted suicide  their own terms. its selfish to keep these people alive and the only people who are against it are people who have never met these people before or people who have never wanted to commit suicide. this also includes depressed people who got help but it dident work. life just isent for everyone a lot of people are alone their entire lives and im not talking about the fake &amp;quot;covid loneliness&amp;quot; im talking about actual loneliness and no one should deal with that for 60 plus years&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：Onlyfans并不是因为色情内容而令人厌恶，而是因为一些用户通过提供 "消息 "服务来剥削孤独的男人，从而创造出一种不健康的寄生社会关系。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据我所知，说寄生社会关系并没有什么争议
是破坏性的。
[https://www.pbs.org/wgbh/nova/article/parasocial-relationships/]

这些关系往往采取名人崇拜或极端迷信的形式。
其中一个人将会迷恋上一个公众人物......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcfkev/cmv_onlyfans_is_not_distasteful_because_of_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcfkev/cmv_onlyfans_is_not_distasteful_because_of_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 10:33:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As far as I know, it&amp;#39;s not controversial to say that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pbs.org/wgbh/nova/article/parasocial-relationships/&quot;&gt;parasocial relationships are destructive.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These relationships often take the form of celebrity worship or extreme fandom, wherein a person will become obsessed with a public figure to an unhealthy degree. This causes them to neglect and eventually completely ignore other aspects of their lives, especially their social lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my view, the OnlyFans messaging &amp;quot;services&amp;quot; are the worst form of parasocial relationships. It takes men who are already clearly suffering from extreme loneliness and sexlessness and sells them a bizarre fantasy wherein they have a &amp;quot;girlfriend experience&amp;quot; which is completely hollow and disingenuous. This causes them not only to neglect their relationships with people face to face, but it intertwines complex and deep-rooted feelings of loneliness and desire for love and sex. I imagine it&amp;#39;s a delicate &amp;quot;carrot and stick&amp;quot; dynamic where the idea of the girl actually caring about the subscriber must be dangled just out of reach in a perpetual manner in order to keep the money coming in. This is extremely destructive and this practice should be shamed in society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, it&amp;#39;s also bad when this happens digitally on Twitch, or in any other context. But at least in this case the relationship is more distant and clearly less &amp;quot;personal&amp;quot;, since there are dozens or even hundreds of other lonely men who are vying for a girl&amp;#39;s attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, it&amp;#39;s also bad when &amp;quot;sex workers&amp;quot; offer this service in reality, face to face - but at least it&amp;#39;s face to face. In that sense the men might at least incidentally pick up some social skills, even if the interaction is completely artificial. The digital, text-based aspect of the Onlyfans messaging services is about as distant as you can get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/confessions/comments/mazkok/onlyfans_girls_arent_personally_messaging_you/&quot;&gt;hard to confirm&lt;/a&gt;, but there&amp;#39;s also the idea that some of the users who offer these services &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/some-influencers-have-ghostwriters-to-respond-to-onlyfan-messages-2020-12&quot;&gt;aren&amp;#39;t even the ones the subscribers are talking to&lt;/a&gt;. They may be outsourcing/delegating this service to others, probably men. I can&amp;#39;t imagine what kind of intense psychological break might occur if one of these subscribers learned that this was going on. Can you imagine? They might even do &lt;em&gt;something really stupid&lt;/em&gt; in a fit of rage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made this post because I strangely never hear talk about this aspect of Onlyfans &amp;quot;culture&amp;quot;, which in my opinion is the most harmful. But maybe there&amp;#39;s a reason others don&amp;#39;t seem very concerned about it. Change my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：应该禁止酒店的强制性度假费。]]></title><description><![CDATA[度假村费是你在酒店开房时需要支付的额外费用。
理论上，你有权享受酒店提供的某些设施。我认为这种
我认为这种费用应该被禁止，因为它是一种诱饵和转换策略，任何强制性费用
任何强制性费用都应该包含在所有的广告价格中。我是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcbc52/cmv_mandatory_resort_fees_at_hotels_should_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcbc52/cmv_mandatory_resort_fees_at_hotels_should_be/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 05:31:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Resort fees are an additional fee you are required to pay for a room at a hotel which in theory entitles you to certain amenities the hotel offers. I think this sort of fee should be banned as a bait and switch tactic, and any mandatory fee whatsoever should be built into all advertised prices. I am thinking of this along the lines of airline price regulations in the US, which require that advertised fares include all taxes and fees that are mandatory to travel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the fee is optional, then I think it&amp;#39;s fine to not include it in the price, much like a checked bag fee is not included in advertised prices. But a mandatory fee is just an increased room rate, and advertising a rate at a hotel of $X, when in fact the rate is $X+40 is just false advertising and should be banned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m reposting from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/comments/oi9ojb/cmv_mandatory_resort_fees_at_hotels_should_be/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, since none of the replies made any good points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：现在说民主是否是最好的政府形式可能还为时尚早。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国被看作是民主成功的典范，但实际上美国在大部分时间里是非常不民主的。
在其大部分历史中，美国是非常不民主的。事实上，妇女只能从
投票是在20世纪20年代。根据当地的政策，对谁可以投票有更多的限制。
政策。我们也都知道，早期的美国只有（白人）男性...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcd4u5/cmv_it_may_still_be_too_early_to_say_whether/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcd4u5/cmv_it_may_still_be_too_early_to_say_whether/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 04:36:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is looked as an example of a success of democracy, but US was actually very undemocratic for most of its history. In fact, women could only start voting in the 1920s. There were more limits on who could vote depending on local policy. As we all know also, early America only (white) male landowners could vote, and there was a slow democratization over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The US is not a pure democracy but it is democratizing more over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, most Western countries are relatively new to democracy as we know it today compared to the size of human history. Democracy as a concept was considered very early on. Historically, throughout much of human history it was treated with disdain because of the unrealibility of the averge voter. Aristotle for example thought that a better alternative would be an enlightened monarch or an enlightened aristocracy purely focused on studying and governing to improve the nation--I don&amp;#39;t prescribe to this view necessarily, this is an example of people&amp;#39;s views on democracy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 西方国家与沙特进行贸易并支持沙特，同时又声称要与恐怖主义开战，这是一种虚伪的行为。]]></title><description><![CDATA[沙特阿拉伯是中东地区乃至全世界最大的恐怖主义资助者和支持者。
也可能是全世界的。他们创建了ISIS，并资助该恐怖组织。
沙特的钱资助了伊斯兰国家，沙特公民为他们大规模作战，而
瓦哈比主义政府视而不见，因为他们的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcd1ml/cmv_its_hypocritical_for_western_nations_to_trade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcd1ml/cmv_its_hypocritical_for_western_nations_to_trade/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 04:36:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia is the biggest funder and supporter of terrorism in the Middle east and likely around the world. They created ISIS and fund the terrorist group. Saudi Money funds the Islamic state, Saudi citizens fight for them in mass, and the Wahhabism government turns a blind eye because their ideology is almost identical to ISIS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How we can claim to be against terrorism yet economically and militarily support the most religiously radical state in the world is sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of punishments that Saudi Arabia and ISIS use. Lets see if you can tell the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Group 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by death- Blasphemy, Acts of Homosexuality, Treason, and Murder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Following is punishable by an undetermined number of lashes- Slander and Drinking Alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by death by stoning - Adulatory if married.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by 100 lashes- Adulatory if unmarried&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by cutting off ones right hand- Stealing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by cutting off one foot and one hand- Banditry theft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by death- Banditry murder and theft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Group 2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by death- Blasphemy, Acts of Homosexuality, Treason, and Murder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Following is punishable by 80 lashes- Slander and Drinking Alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by death by stoning - Adulatory if married.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by 100 lashes and exile for a year- Adulatory if unmarried&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by cutting off one hand- Stealing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by cutting off one foot and one hand- Banditry theft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following is punishable by crucifixion- Banditry murder and theft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am leaving the name of which one is ISIS and which one is Saudi Arabia to make a point. Both are barbaric, murderous groups the only difference is one took over a state and got legitimately recognized. Removing all support from Saudi Arabia ends a lot of Terrorism because the money source would be cut off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：社交媒体正在毁掉我们这一代人]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一个20岁的男性，我认为社交媒体对我们这一代人来说是弊大于利。
请听我说。他们不教人包容，因为有几个种族被排除在外
因为一些种族被排除在外，还有较瘦/正常的体型。他们帮助美化了
他们帮助美化性工作，并鼓励性工作，这是有辱人格的......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcawwd/cmv_social_media_are_ruining_my_generation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pcawwd/cmv_social_media_are_ruining_my_generation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 03:36:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a 20 years old male and I think social media are more bad than good for my generation, hear me out.
They don&amp;#39;t teach inclusivity cause several races are left out from the equation and also thinner/normal body types. 
They help glorify sex work  in an ill way and encourage it, which is degrading and has several mental effect on women and men of all ages.
They push women to be slutty to feel empowered confusing the two concepts and push men to be too masculine and to view women as objects and to not respect them. Also don&amp;#39;t get me started on the body dysmorphia.
Also reaserch show that seeing your friends always posting their best self on social media and comparing yourself to them makes u depressed and unsatisfied with your life, and no, the &amp;quot;remember social media is fake&amp;quot; trend is like pissing into a fire  trying to estinguish it, it does t solve the problem. 
the only thing they&amp;#39;re good is to keep in touch with poeple but the posting part is totally useless and it&amp;#39;s just a way to get validation for a generation that is willing to do the dumbest shit to get it. 
Also tik tok should be canceled. It is basically a p*do/horny guys/creeps dream come true where they can see underage girls dressing and acting in revealing &amp;quot;clothes &amp;quot;  desperate for likes but they don&amp;#39;t know where they come from. Also it is a Chinese company that doesn&amp;#39;t give a shut about your privacy just saying... 
They are also the worst source to get information from cause 90 percent of the time reaserch and statistics is manipulated or not cited(like this post lol) and fake news are spread like crazy 
Hope someone will change my point of view since I have the sin to still using them daily and I need to feel good about myself even tho we all know  these things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：有6英尺0英寸以上的身高偏好，甚至是一种要求，并没有什么错，只要你不因为自己的偏好而贬低别人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一个5英尺9英寸的男性，所以我不符合这个标准，但并没有什么问题。
的问题。身体上的吸引力是一段关系的重要组成部分，而且是非常重要的。
很重要（外表确实很重要）。任何时候一个女人说她更喜欢或只愿意和
6'0以上的男人，矮个子男人就会生气，并表现得像她是......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc8t95/cmv_theres_nothing_wrong_with_having_a_60_height/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc8t95/cmv_theres_nothing_wrong_with_having_a_60_height/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 23:37:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a 5’9 male, so I don’t fit the bill for that standard, but don’t have an issue with it. Physical attraction is a huge part of a relationship and is very important (looks do matter). Anytime a woman says she prefers or will only date 6’0+ men, short men will get pissed and act like she’s the biggest bitch in the world (which is an obvious projection of their insecurities). If you’re not attracted to men below 6’0, then you shouldn’t have to date them, the same way a man shouldn’t have to date an obese woman if he doesn’t find her attractive. People can have whatever preference they want, even if it’s ridiculous, as long as you aren’t shallow towards people who don’t fit your preference. It’s not just easy to “look past it” and find other things thst make up for it, it’s ok to have things you’re solely attracted to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：现场表演的专辑是所有世界中最糟糕的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这并不是说录音室的专辑比演出好，或者反之亦然。两者都是
惊人，给音乐带来不同的方面。

工作室专辑提供了高度抛光和制作的歌曲版本，这是
很好。如果一个乐队要使用效果器或让成员演奏多种乐器
乐器，它允许...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc20ch/cmv_albums_of_live_performances_are_the_worst_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc20ch/cmv_albums_of_live_performances_are_the_worst_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 19:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not about studio albums being better than gigs or vice versa. Both are amazing and bring different aspects to music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studio albums provide highly polished and produced versions of songs, which is great. If a band whats to use effects or have members playing multiple instruments it allows them to do so. This is good. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Live shows can provide an amazing atmosphere and performance, at their best creating an almost religious experience for those attending, as well as bonding experiences for friends going together. This is also most excellent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;However&lt;/em&gt;, my issue is that with an album of a live recording, you lose what is best about both. Getting neither the production quality of studio albums, nor the raw experience of being at a mindblowing performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can kind of understand having a recording of a gig you went to, for posterity&amp;#39;s sake, but even then, it isn&amp;#39;t going to match the experience of actually &lt;em&gt;being&lt;/em&gt; there. There is perhaps an accessibility argument, but even then, I&amp;#39;d suggest watching a video of the gig, to get the full AV show, instead of just an audio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT&lt;/strong&gt;: I didn&amp;#39;t think I&amp;#39;d have to write this, but can you explain &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; a certain recording of a live show is not worse than either seeing it live or a studio version, instead of just listing your favourite recording.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT 2&lt;/strong&gt;: After a few responses, I&amp;#39;ve hit on the crux of this CMV; &amp;quot;what does a live recording bring that neither IRL gigs or studio albums do?&amp;quot;. Answer that, and I&amp;#39;ll be putty in your hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美国的监狱系统是破碎的，对任何人都没有帮助]]></title><description><![CDATA[让我们把这个问题说清楚，监狱的目的是为了惩罚一个人，因为
他们的行为，并教导他们不要再犯。美国的监狱系统并没有
实现这些，它甚至没有接近。看看欧洲的
(特别是挪威/斯堪的纳维亚半岛）的监狱，他们对待囚犯就像...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc2l9d/cmv_the_us_prison_system_is_broken_and_doesnt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc2l9d/cmv_the_us_prison_system_is_broken_and_doesnt/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 19:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s get this out of the way, the purpose of a prison is to punish someone for their actions and teach them not to repeat it. The US prison system does not accomplish any of this, it doesn&amp;#39;t even come close. Look at the European (specifically Norway/Scandinavia) prisons, they treat prisoners like humans and provide them with in-demand skills, and their recidivism rate is just 20%, compared to the US&amp;#39; massive 70% recidivism rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not surprising, given how the US system is basically throw them in a shithole, treat them like shit and slaves, force them to disclose the fact that they&amp;#39;re a felon on job applications, then going all suprised pikachu face when they can&amp;#39;t find employment and turn back to crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I should clarify, what I mean, is that prisons do help people, just not the prisoners. Instead, they line the pockets of the  contractors who build and maintain them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我们应该让男性在托儿所和学前教育中工作正常化]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的侄子最近开始上学前班，我只是顺便想了一下，我不认为
我从来没有见过一个男的学前班老师。如果一个男人不被信任能照顾好孩子，他怎么能在需要照顾孩子的领域中发挥作用呢？
如果他不被信任去做儿童的基本护理工作，他怎么能在需要照顾儿童的领域发挥作用呢？
父亲经常给孩子换尿布，帮助孩子上厕所，并把...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc318e/cmv_we_should_normalize_males_working_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc318e/cmv_we_should_normalize_males_working_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 18:37:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My nephew recently started pre-k and I just had a passing thought, I don’t think I’ve ever seen a male pre-k teacher. How can a man have a role in a field requiring care for children if he is not trusted with children’s basic care? Fathers often change diapers, help children use the toilet, and put children down for naps. And maybe that’s what distinguishes early childhood education from other female-dominated professions. Declaring men unfit to provide such care is not only about sexism against men, it’s also about sexism against women. The greater the fear of men in caring professions, the more women are left to shoulder the responsibility of care work. If women experienced equality in all professions, then perhaps they wouldn’t regard child care as their exclusive domain, and wouldn’t feel threatened by the participation of men. How can we teach U.S. children not to regard early childhood education as the exclusive domain of women, when they see only women caring for them? What message are we sending today’s youth when we glorify involved fathers and stay-at-home dads but vilify male child-care workers? We should encourage more men to enter this field, and celebrate them rather than fear them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：黑水公司以6500美元一个人的价格从阿富汗撤走人是一件好事。]]></title><description><![CDATA[很多人都在为黑水公司撤离阿富汗难民而大吵大闹。
愿意并能够支付6,500美元的阿富汗难民。我明白，这似乎
黑水公司的邪恶暴利行为，也许是这样，但事实是
但事实是，他们这样做，世界会变得更美好。他们并不打算...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc1eam/cmv_blackwater_evacuating_people_from_afghanistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pc1eam/cmv_blackwater_evacuating_people_from_afghanistan/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 17:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of people in an uproar because Blackwater is evacuating Afghan refugees who are willing and able to pay $6,500. I understand that this seems like evil profiteering by Blackwater, and maybe it is, but the truth is the world is a better place for them doing this. They are not going to do it for free, and this way more people who want to leave, can. If Blackwater did not evacuate these people, some of them will end up stuck and some of them will even end up on free flights, taking the seat of others. Who is worse off for Blackwater doing this? The constraint on evacuations is a lack of planes, not a lack of runway time (to be clear, some flights did have to divert, but it was because no one could land because refugees had taken over the runways). Blackwater is solving that problem, albeit it a profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Several commenters have made great points that ultimately boil down to how one defines &amp;quot;good,&amp;quot; which is a very nebulous concept. So let me briefly define good as I used it in my title: Good is the absence of bad. We should stop people from doing bad things. We should not stop Blackwater from evacuating people for a price, so long as the constraint on evacuations is planes and not runway time. Blackwater is doing a good thing under my (admittedly binary) definition of good and bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在审议公共政策的范围内，如果不援引神性就不能为一个论点辩护，那么这个论点就是无效的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在这个国家，即美国，据说有一堵故意的墙
教会和国家之间。国家能够在公民的公共和私人生活中挥舞巨大的权力和
对公民的公共和私人生活产生影响。教会与国家之间的分离
是为了保护每个机构不受对方的影响。国家...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbzkp5/cmv_within_the_scope_of_deliberations_on_public/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbzkp5/cmv_within_the_scope_of_deliberations_on_public/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:35:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this country, the United States, there is supposedly an intentional wall between church and state. The state is capable of wielding enormous power and influence in public and private lives of citizens. The separation between church and state is to protect each body from the other. The state should not be able to reach into the church and dictate except in extreme cases. Similarly, the church isn’t the government. It doesn’t have the same writ as the government and shouldn’t be allowed to reach into the government or lives of non-followers—ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why I believe decisions based on religion (especially the predominate monotheist versions) are invalid in discourse over public policy comes down to consent and feedback mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every citizen* has access to the franchise and is subject to the government. The government draws its authority from the governed and there are ways to participate, have your voice heard, change policy, and be represented. Jaded as some may be there are mechanisms in place to question, challenge, and influence policy in the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not every citizen follows a religion—further, not even all the followers in America are of the same religion, sect, or denomination. Even IF there was a majority bloc of believers, that is a choice to follow an organization based on faith which demands obedience and eschews feedback/reform. The rules and proclamations are not democratically decided; they are derived, divined, and interpreted by a very small group which does not take requests from the congregation. Which is fine if you’re allowing that to govern your own life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arguments about public policy must allow conversation, debate, introduction of objective facts, challenges to authority, accountability of everyone (top to bottom), and evolution/growth/change with introduction and consideration of new information—all things which theist organizations don’t seem to prioritize. Public policy must be defensible with sound logic and reason. Public policy cannot be allowed to be made on the premise of faith or built upon a foundation of a belief. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aside from leaving the country, we do not have a choice in being subject to the government. Following a faith is a choice. If the government is going to limit my actions, I have few options but to comply and if I disagree then exercise rights. If a church is going to limit my actions and I do not agree, then I can walk away. The church can not be allowed to make rules for those outside the church.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When defending a position on public policy, any defense which falls back on faith, conforming to a religion, or other religious dogma is invalid. If you cannot point to anything more tangible than your own choice in faith or what some parson or clergy dictates, then it should not apply to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any form of, “the law should be X because my faith believes X” is nothing more than forcing your faith on others. CMV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Yes, I’m aware of people under 18, felons, and others denied the right to vote. That isn’t the scope of this conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：种族灭绝并不比其他种族灭绝 "糟糕"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[没有所谓的种族灭绝的等级。对土著人的灭绝。
宗教、同胞等等，都是一样可怕的。大屠杀
大屠杀并不比美洲的种族灭绝事件 "好 "或 "坏"。

柬埔寨人、卢旺达人、希腊人，以及这么多的人都有种族灭绝。

我不会...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pby7dy/cmv_genocides_arent_worse_than_other_genocides/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pby7dy/cmv_genocides_arent_worse_than_other_genocides/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 14:30:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s no such thing as ranked genocides. The extermination of natives, religions, countrymen, etc., are all just as horrible as the other. The Holocaust was not &amp;quot;better&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;worse&amp;quot; than the genocides of the Americas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cambodians, Rwandans, Greeks, and so many more have genocides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wouldn&amp;#39;t be surprised if all countries committed or have been apart of a genocide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If these people were capable of completely erasing a civilization, they would. The lack of the killer&amp;#39;s capabilities, supplies, and logistics are the ONLY reasons that some aren&amp;#39;t completely destroyed. It&amp;#39;s because they literally can&amp;#39;t sustain or prolong it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, numbers and speed can be devastatingly different, but in my opinion, the &amp;quot;idea&amp;quot; of genocide is completely disgusting, evil, hateful, gross, and so much more. You can&amp;#39;t compare one to another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I genuinely love how we&amp;#39;re having adult conversations about something so serious. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在这一点上，审查和禁止社交媒体上的反疫苗社区，将创造更多的反疫苗者]]></title><description><![CDATA[将antivaxx定义为反对所有疫苗的人。真正的原始
在COVID发生之前的真正原始定义。

我真的相信，我们已经过了审查直言不讳的人到不知名的
平台，因为他们现在无处不在。这不仅仅是reddit，或Facebook。
或推特。它是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbontx/cmv_censoring_and_banning_social_media_antivaxx/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbontx/cmv_censoring_and_banning_social_media_antivaxx/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 04:30:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Defining antivaxx as people who are against all vaccines. The true original definition before COVID ever happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I truly believe that we&amp;#39;re past the point of censoring the outspoken to unknown platforms, because they are now everywhere. It&amp;#39;s not just reddit, or Facebook, or Twitter. It&amp;#39;s Instagram and NextDoor and I saw it in descriptions and feedback on Airbnb. It is now everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think various people dropped the ball. I think that it was very unwise of various politicians and news companies to &amp;quot;raise a concern about the vaccine being rushed to help Trump&amp;quot;, and I think that it was unwise for platforms like reddit and Facebook not to foresee this exact thing happening and nipping it in the bud when it started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, your next door neighbor heard something about something, and more people than ever have become truly &amp;quot;vaccine hesitant&amp;quot;. Not just COVID vaccines; all vaccines. The same people I was trying so hard to understand before all of this happened, are now all around me eager to share their thoughts, even in person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think at this point, the only way out is to combat the misinformation, not pretend it doesn&amp;#39;t exist. Reddit and other platforms can ban subreddits, but it&amp;#39;s been complicit in letting it get here, and I don&amp;#39;t think there are too many people left who have no opinion at all. A true crowd-sourced campaign to explain why misinformation is misinformation, including in the communities that are anti-authority--which really, these communities are--is the only way forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply banning them and assuming that they&amp;#39;ll at least go elsewhere is helping the rest of the reddit community feel good about ourselves, but addresses no issues, makes no strides forward to change the narrative, and may even hinder the potential progress. Everyone has heard of the COVID vaccines. Some people are hesitant. Removing any platforms that say anything but positive views, will drive them toward more &amp;quot;research&amp;quot; that will create more hardcore antivaxxers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我们在大流行期间学到的东西导致了这样的结论：即将发生的气候灾难是不可避免的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，这对我来说是一个很大的问题，但我想尽量客观地对待
尽可能地客观和合理。我还想指出的是，我最希望的是
我最希望的是在这里被说服，我的观点是错误的，因为我想更多的
充满希望。

的观点。

 1. 这是大多数专家的观点，在...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbhj3v/cmv_what_we_learned_during_the_pandemic_leads_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbhj3v/cmv_what_we_learned_during_the_pandemic_leads_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 04:30:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, this is a big one for me emotionally, but I want to try to be as objective and reasonable as possible. Also I&amp;#39;d like to point out that I&amp;#39;d like nothing more than to be convinced here that my view is wrong, because I want to be more hopeful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The View:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is the opinion of most experts on the matter that we&amp;#39;re heading towards a serious climate disaster if we do nothing to reverse certain trends. Essentially we&amp;#39;re releasing too much carbon and methane from our industrialization/food production/garment industry/etc. and are causing a serious warming trend, more extreme weather and the like.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Those same experts tend to agree that there &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; things we can still do to avert disaster, but in general they seem to me like fairly major changes for most (or at least some) people. For instance, meat production results in a lot of methane emission, which is a worse greenhouse gas than CO2, so if everyone were vegetarian that could be a big help. Also there&amp;#39;s plenty of talk about basically planting a billion trees to store the carbon that would otherwise be in the atmosphere. I don&amp;#39;t know &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the big-picture solutions, nor how much a person&amp;#39;s day-to-day impacts the bigger picture, but it does seem that there are things we &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The pandemic has shown us that there&amp;#39;s a segment of the population that are unwilling to do even something &lt;em&gt;small&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;obviously helpful&lt;/em&gt;, such as wear a mask during a pandemic, or maintain social distancing. I know there&amp;#39;s definitely a loud minority making this segment seem probably larger than it is, but basically my takeaway from it has been that even if you give people something fairly small to do to avert an &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;obviously real and serious&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; risk (Covid), there will still be people who play the &amp;quot;personal freedom&amp;quot; card or science-denial, or some combination of them. So essentially, if you try to get a very large subset of the population to do something &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;even more major&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and to avert a crisis that&amp;#39;s a bit more invisible (i.e. there&amp;#39;s still doubt in the minds of many people that they should or even can do anything to avert the climate disaster) I am of the belief that it&amp;#39;s unreasonable to expect that it would happen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve broken this down into the three distinct points that I feel comprise the whole view as I recognize that any part of the three could have logical holes or problems, or even my notion that they follow in this progression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I said earlier, I&amp;#39;d really love to turn out to be wrong on this one, so let&amp;#39;s have a discussion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt; After posting, I realized that of course there&amp;#39;s more to the climate disaster beyond just the actions of us as individuals. However, I feel that it is a separate discussion to dive into the &amp;quot;who&amp;#39;s at fault&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;corporations vs. individuals&amp;quot; and all of that. My view here is more about individuals and modifying their behavior as individuals. If you feel corporations are more to blame, then I &lt;em&gt;still&lt;/em&gt; blame the individuals who have voted (or not voted) and led to the power and size of our largest corporations who are doing most of the damage. It&amp;#39;s still about people and their choices as far as I&amp;#39;m concerned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：经济拮据时生孩子是不负责任的做法]]></title><description><![CDATA[我并不是说这很可怕。它只是不负责任。如果财政紧张，那么生孩子会使财政更紧张。
那么生孩子会使财政更加紧张。如果你住在农村地区。
我认为当整个家庭的收入超过8万/年时，生孩子会更好。
(两个人的收入都是4万/年)，如果你住在一个昂贵的地方，我认为最好在整个家庭收入超过8万/年的时候生孩子。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbfchx/cmv_it_is_irresponsible_to_have_children_when/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbfchx/cmv_it_is_irresponsible_to_have_children_when/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:30:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m not saying it’s horrible. It’s just irresponsible. If finances are tight, then having kids will make finances tighter. If you are living in a rural area, I’d say it’s better to have kids when the entire household income exceeds 80k/yr (both people making 40k/yr) if you are living in an expensive city, the household income should be higher. The same people who have kids when finances are tight are the same people who complain that they have nothing in savings. No savings for retirement. No savings for emergencies. No savings for their children’s college.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：主要社交媒体平台上缺乏不喜欢/反对的按钮，使得反疫苗的观点能够更有效地传播。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的看法。西方最流行的社交媒体平台，即Facebook。
Instagram和Twitter，都缺乏相当于 "降票 "的反应。正如
在过去十年多的时间里，Reddit已经向我们展示了收到更多的
的内容在算法中的排名会上升，并且是...。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbepyr/cmv_the_lack_of_a_dislikedownvote_button_on_major/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbepyr/cmv_the_lack_of_a_dislikedownvote_button_on_major/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 21:30:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My view&lt;/strong&gt;: The most popular social media platforms in the West, namely Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter, all lack the equivalent of a &amp;quot;downvote&amp;quot; reaction. As Reddit has shown us over the past decade+, content which receives far more upvotes than downvotes moves up in the algorithm&amp;#39;s ranking and is more likely to be seen. Additionally, from a psychosocial standpoint, humans &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; to be viewed as agreeable, and tend towards views and behavior that the masses consider good. On reddit this often leads to a positive feedback loop, where highly-upvoted content receives even more upvotes because, well, it&amp;#39;s already been upvoted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the aforementioned platforms only have positive reactions for posts and comments (outside of Facebook which has angry/laugh reactions) there&amp;#39;s no true way for a person to tell the relative popularity of a person&amp;#39;s post. This means content that only a small minority of people agree with can end up looking very popular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This leads me to my opinion that beliefs which are truly on the fringe, or at least used to be - such as anti-vaccine or anti-mask - appear more socially acceptable than they really are, and leads people down that path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What I&amp;#39;m not saying:&lt;/strong&gt; The content ranking algorithm on platforms which feature a downvote button, such as Reddit, are &amp;quot;ideal&amp;quot;. I&amp;#39;m only stating my view in the context of enabling and unintentionally promoting false information surrounding vaccines, specifically the COVID-19 vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：女权主义应该改名为性别平等主义]]></title><description><![CDATA[好的，所以请忍受我。让我把这个问题说出来。我认为自己是一个
我认为自己是一名女权主义者（我使用这个词的意思是，支持妇女应
根据牛津词典，"拥有与男性相同的权利和机会"）。)
但是，我更喜欢使用性别平等主义这个词......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbcmt1/cmv_feminism_should_be_renamed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbcmt1/cmv_feminism_should_be_renamed/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 20:39:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay so bear with me.  Let me get this out of the way: I consider myself a feminist (I&amp;#39;m using this term to mean a supporter of the idea that women should &amp;#39;have the same rights and opportunities as men&amp;#39; as per the Oxford dictionary).  HOWEVER, I much prefer to use the term Gender-Egalitarianism because I think it&amp;#39;s a title that better represents feminism&amp;#39;s central message and thus better promotes the movement&amp;#39;s agenda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I see often on the Internet (and sometimes in real life too) is people being reluctant to identify as a feminist because they see feminism as being about getting more things (rights, freedoms, opportunities, political power, etc.) for women FULL STOP.  What I mean by this is, they see feminism as being about lifting up women, with little to no regard to how this leaves men off at the end of the day.  Now, true feminism of course rejects this and takes the issues that disproportionately affect men (like being far less likely to receive custody of their children in divorce, for example) as real problems that need to be solved if men and women are going to be equal in society (of course, this doesn&amp;#39;t mean that a feminist needs to say that men and women have it equally hard, as long as a feminist is willing to admit that both &amp;#39;female&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;male&amp;#39; issues are legitimate issues and deserve addressing, then they&amp;#39;re free to think whatever they want about the current balance of hardship between the sexes).  SO, because feminism is looked at by many people as a women&amp;#39;s power movement, rather than a movement about achieving equality with respect to gender/sex, there a great number of people who have negative connotations with the term feminism, and are far less likely to hear out feminist thinkers/arguments with an open mind.  The is evidenced by the fact that (and I don&amp;#39;t have the stat to point to but it shouldn&amp;#39;t be hard to find) that the discrepancy between people who believe the sexes should be equal and people who self-identify as feminists is massive in the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SO, in order to get more people in a state where they can hear the feminist message with an open mind, we need to ditch the (frankly) shitty name &amp;#39;Feminism&amp;#39;.  It simply does not reflect its core message as well as Gender-Egalitarianism does, and this is costing the movement its ability to be heard out by many potential allies.  Imagine if Racial-Egalitarianism (the idea that the races should have the same rights and opportunities) was called &amp;#39;Blackism&amp;#39;.  You&amp;#39;d probably think, well, that&amp;#39;s a shitty name, not only because there&amp;#39;s a lot of disenfranchised races and it&amp;#39;s weird to pick out one, but because it just SOUNDS like a black power movement full stop, which is bound to turn off many potential allies before they have a chance to dig into the movement and see that its core message is something that is actually very desirable.  How could &amp;#39;Feminism&amp;#39; be any different?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a note, I&amp;#39;m not suggesting that Feminism would become universally accepted overnight if it had the name change I&amp;#39;m advocating for, I&amp;#39;m saying that it would make it easier for at least some people who currently view Feminism in a negative light to be more open minded to the movement.  If it would help to recruit at least some more supporters (whether they be people alive today or future persons who might have been turned off the movement by the name &amp;#39;Feminism&amp;#39;), then why wouldn&amp;#39;t we want to do it?  What would be the countervailing harm the name change would or might cause that could justify us keeping the name &amp;#39;Feminism&amp;#39;?  Also, if you&amp;#39;re tempted to respond that &amp;#39;those who are stupid enough to view Feminism as a women&amp;#39;s power movement shouldn&amp;#39;t be our concern&amp;#39;, or &amp;#39;people who make that mistake should educate themselves&amp;#39;, then I would respond that 1) one of the central goals of Feminism is the widespread acceptance of the core Feminist message, and to do this we’ll need to get comfortable marketing the movement to people who view the movement in ways people who support the movement might find &amp;#39;stupid&amp;#39;. 2) why wait for uneducated people to educate themselves, when you can do something right now (that is very easy to do I might add) that makes them less likely to make the mistake you consider to be so stupid in the first place?  It seems very arrogant and even reckless to prefer to sit back and wait for others to see the light, so to speak - especially when leaving gender inequality unresolved has real consequences that are measured in human suffering!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I know there is no central organization to the feminist movement, so I know that there is no governing body that can unilaterally decide on the name change I&amp;#39;m advocating for.  However, if feminists started referring to themselves as Gender-Egalitarians and said that they were moved to this name change out of a concern that the name alienates many people who they hope to one day call allies, I think the movement could for all intents and purposes be considered renamed in fairly short amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m very curious to see what people think are good reasons for resisting the name change I&amp;#39;m advocating for! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果我们真的关心结构性不平等问题，我们的首要重点应该是降低生活成本。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大多数围绕不平等的讨论往往集中在收入方面。在我看来
在我看来，在一个像住房、医疗和教育这样的基本东西的成本正以极高的速度膨胀的世界里，这意义是有限的。
住房、医疗和教育的成本正以极高的速度膨胀。真正解决
真正解决这个问题的更好方法是利用技术知识。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbd8xk/cmv_if_we_really_care_about_structural_inequality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/pbd8xk/cmv_if_we_really_care_about_structural_inequality/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 19:34:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the discussions around inequality tends to focus on income. In my opinion this has limited meaning in a world where cost of basic stuff like Shelter, Healthcare and Education are inflating at extremely high rates. The better way to genuinely tackle the issue is to utilize technological know how and planning to deflate the costs of these basic things along with food and clothing down to a very low level. Example: like how TVs and computers have gotten cheaper while also becoming much better. In such a world it would be much harder to exploit people and even if there would be inequality, it would not hurt as much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>